<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<resources>
    <string name="AIModeSettingsDesc">This policy controls Google's AI Mode integrations in the address bar and the New Tab page search box. To access this feature, Google must be set as the user's default search engine. 0/unset = The feature will be available to users. 1 = The feature will not be available to users. If the policy is unset, its behavior is determined by the GenAiDefaultSettings policy.</string>
    <string name="AIModeSettingsTitle">Settings for Google's AI Mode integrations in the address bar and New Tab page search box.</string>
    <string name="AccessControlAllowMethodsInCORSPreflightSpecConformantDesc">This policy controls whether request methods are uppercased when matching with Access-Control-Allow-Methods response headers in CORS preflight. If the policy is Disabled, request methods are uppercased. This is the behavior on or before Google Chrome 108. If the policy is Enabled or not set, request methods are not uppercased, unless matching case-insensitively with DELETE, GET, HEAD, OPTIONS, POST, or PUT. This would reject fetch(url, {method: 'Foo'}) + "Access-Control-Allow-Methods: FOO" response header, and would accept fetch(url, {method: 'Foo'}) + "Access-Control-Allow-Methods: Foo" response header. Note: request methods "post" and "put" are not affected, while "patch" is affected. This policy is intended to be temporary and will be removed in the future.</string>
    <string name="AccessControlAllowMethodsInCORSPreflightSpecConformantTitle">Make Access-Control-Allow-Methods matching in CORS preflight spec conformant</string>
    <string name="AccessibilityPerformanceFilteringAllowedDesc">A policy to control whether the accessibility engine is allowed to dynamically compute a filter for the accessibility tree in Google Chrome to improve performance. When the policy is either set to Enabled or not set, the accessibility engine is allowed to dynamically compute filter modes for the accessibility tree in Google Chrome, which may lead to a performance improvement. When the policy is set to Disabled, the accessibility engine is not allowed to dynamically compute filter modes for the accessibility tree.</string>
    <string name="AccessibilityPerformanceFilteringAllowedTitle">Allow Accessibility Performance Filtering.</string>
    <string name="AdditionalDnsQueryTypesEnabledDesc">This policy controls whether Google Chrome may query additional DNS record types when making insecure DNS requests. This policy has no effect on DNS queries made via Secure DNS, which may always query additional DNS types. If this policy is unset or set to Enabled, additional types such as HTTPS (DNS type 65) may be queried in addition to A (DNS type 1) and AAAA (DNS type 28). If this policy is set to Disabled, DNS will only be queried for A (DNS type 1) and/or AAAA (DNS type 28). This policy is a temporary measure and will be removed in future versions of Google Chrome. After removal of the policy, Google Chrome will always be able to query additional DNS types.</string>
    <string name="AdditionalDnsQueryTypesEnabledTitle">Allow DNS queries for additional DNS record types</string>
    <string name="AllHttpAuthSchemesAllowedForOriginsDesc">Setting the policy specifies for which origins to allow all the HTTP authentication schemes Google Chrome supports regardless of the AuthSchemes policy. Format the origin pattern according to this format (https://support.google.com/chrome/a?p=url_blocklist_filter_format). Up to 1,000 exceptions can be defined in AllHttpAuthSchemesAllowedForOrigins. Wildcards are allowed for the whole origin or parts of the origin, either the scheme, host, port.</string>
    <string name="AllHttpAuthSchemesAllowedForOriginsTitle">List of origins allowing all HTTP authentication</string>
    <string name="AllowBackForwardCacheForCacheControlNoStorePageEnabledDesc">This policy controls if a page with Cache-Control: no-store header can be stored in back/forward cache. The website setting this header may not expect the page to be restored from back/forward cache since some sensitive information could still be displayed after the restoration even if it is no longer accessible. If the policy is enabled or unset, the page with Cache-Control: no-store header might be restored from back/forward cache unless the cache eviction is triggered (e.g. when there is HTTP-only cookie change to the site). If the policy is disabled, the page with Cache-Control: no-store header will not be stored in back/forward cache.</string>
    <string name="AllowBackForwardCacheForCacheControlNoStorePageEnabledTitle">Allow pages with Cache-Control: no-store header to enter back/forward cache</string>
    <string name="AllowWebAuthnWithBrokenTlsCertsDesc">If set to Enabled, Google Chrome will allow Web Authentication requests on websites that have TLS certificates with errors (i.e. websites considered not secure). If the policy is set to Disabled or left unset, the default behavior of blocking such requests will apply.</string>
    <string name="AllowWebAuthnWithBrokenTlsCertsTitle">Allow Web Authentication requests on sites with broken TLS certificates.</string>
    <string name="AllowedDomainsForAppsDesc">Setting the policy turns on Chrome's restricted sign-in feature in Google Workspace and prevents users from changing this setting. Users can only access Google tools using accounts from the specified domains (to allow gmail or googlemail accounts, add consumer_accounts to the list of domains). This setting prevents users from signing in and adding a Secondary Account on a managed device that requires Google authentication, if that account doesn't belong to one of the explicitly allowed domains. Leaving this setting empty or unset means users can access Google Workspace with any account. Users cannot change or override this setting. Note: This policy causes the X-GoogApps-Allowed-Domains header to be appended to all HTTP and HTTPS requests to all google.com domains, as described in https://support.google.com/a/answer/1668854.</string>
    <string name="AllowedDomainsForAppsTitle">Define domains allowed to access Google Workspace</string>
    <string name="AlternateErrorPagesEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to True means Google Chrome uses alternate error pages built into (such as "page not found"). Setting the policy to False means Google Chrome never uses alternate error pages. If you set the policy, users can't change it. If not set, the policy is on, but users can change this setting.</string>
    <string name="AlternateErrorPagesEnabledTitle">Enable alternate error pages</string>
    <string name="AuthAndroidNegotiateAccountTypeDesc">Setting the policy specifies the type of accounts provided by the Android authentication app that supports HTTP Negotiate authentication (such as Kerberos authentication). This information should be available from the supplier of the authentication app. For details, see The Chromium Projects ( https://goo.gl/hajyfN ) Leaving the policy unset turns off HTTP Negotiate authentication on Android.</string>
    <string name="AuthAndroidNegotiateAccountTypeTitle">Account type for HTTP Negotiate authentication</string>
    <string name="AuthNegotiateDelegateAllowlistDesc">Setting the policy assigns servers that Google Chrome may delegate to. Separate multiple server names with commas. Wildcards, *, are allowed. Leaving the policy unset means Google Chrome won't delegate user credentials, even if a server is detected as intranet.</string>
    <string name="AuthNegotiateDelegateAllowlistTitle">Kerberos delegation server allowlist</string>
    <string name="AuthSchemesDesc">Setting the policy specifies which HTTP authentication schemes Google Chrome supports. Leaving the policy unset employs all 4 schemes. Valid values: * basic * digest * ntlm * negotiate Note: Separate multiple values with commas.</string>
    <string name="AuthSchemesTitle">Supported authentication schemes</string>
    <string name="AuthServerAllowlistDesc">Setting the policy specifies which servers should be allowed for integrated authentication. Integrated authentication is only on when Google Chrome gets an authentication challenge from a proxy or from a server in this permitted list. Leaving the policy unset means Google Chrome tries to detect if a server is on the intranet. Only then will it respond to IWA requests. If a server is detected as internet, then Google Chrome ignores IWA requests from it. Note: Separate multiple server names with commas. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="AuthServerAllowlistTitle">Authentication server allowlist</string>
    <string name="AutofillAddressEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to True or leaving it unset gives users control of Autofill for addresses in the UI. Setting the policy to False means Autofill never suggests or fills address information, nor does it save additional address information that users submit while browsing the web.</string>
    <string name="AutofillAddressEnabledTitle">Enable AutoFill for addresses</string>
    <string name="AutofillCreditCardEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to True or leaving it unset means users can control autofill suggestions for credit cards in the UI. Setting the policy to False means autofill never suggests or fills credit card information, nor will it save additional credit card information that users might submit while browsing the web.</string>
    <string name="AutofillCreditCardEnabledTitle">Enable AutoFill for credit cards</string>
    <string name="Automatically_recover_to_background">Restore to background</string>
    <string name="BackForwardCacheEnabledDesc">When enabled the BackForwardCache feature allows the use of the back-forward cache. When navigating away from a page, its current state (document tree, script, etc.) may be preserved in the back-forward cache. If the browser navigates back to the page, the page may be restored from the back-forward cache and displayed in the state it was in before being cached. This feature might cause issues for some websites that do not expect this caching. In particular, some websites depend on the "unload" event being dispatched when the browser navigates away from the page. The "unload" event will not be dispatched if the page enters the back-forward cache. If this policy is set to enabled or not set, the BackForwardCache feature will be enabled. If this policy is set to disabled then the feature will be force disabled.</string>
    <string name="BackForwardCacheEnabledTitle">Control the BackForwardCache feature.</string>
    <string name="BlockThirdPartyCookiesDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled prevents webpage elements that aren't from the domain that's in the browser's address bar from setting cookies. Setting the policy to Disabled lets those elements set cookies and prevents users from changing this setting. Leaving it unset allows third-party cookies, but users can change this setting. Note: This policy doesn't apply in Incognito mode, where third-party cookies are blocked and can only be allowed at the site level. To allow cookies at the site level, use the CookiesAllowedForUrls policy.</string>
    <string name="BlockThirdPartyCookiesTitle">Block third party cookies</string>
    <string name="BrowserSigninDesc">This policy controls the sign-in behavior of the browser. It allows you to specify if the user can sign in to Google Chrome with their account and use account related services like Google Chrome Sync. If the policy is set to "Disable browser sign-in" then the user cannot sign in to the browser and use account-based services. In this case browser-level features like Google Chrome Sync cannot be used and will be unavailable. On iOS, if the user was signed in and the policy is set to "Disabled" they will be signed out immediately. On other platforms, they will be signed out the next time they run Google Chrome. On all platforms, their local profile data like bookmarks, passwords etc. will be preserved and still usable. The user will still be able to sign into and use Google web services like Gmail. If the policy is set to "Enable browser sign-in," then the user is allowed to sign in to the browser. On all platforms except iOS, the user is automatically signed in to the browser when signed in to Google web services like Gmail. Being signed in to the browser means the user's account information will be kept by the browser. However, it does not mean that Google Chrome Sync will be turned on by default; the user must separately opt-in to use this feature. Enabling this policy will prevent the user from turning off the setting that allows browser sign-in. To control the availability of Google Chrome Sync, use the SyncDisabled policy. If the policy is set to "Force browser sign-in" the user is presented with an account selection dialog and has to choose and sign in to an account to use the browser. This ensures that for managed accounts the policies associated with the account are applied and enforced. The default value of BrowserGuestModeEnabled will be set to disabled. Note that existing unsigned profiles will be locked and inaccessible after enabling this policy. For more information, see help center article: https://support.google.com/chrome/a/answer/7572556 . This option is not supported on Linux nor Android, where it will fall back to "Enable browser sign-in" if used. If this policy is not set then the user can decide if they want to enable browser sign-in in the Google Chrome settings and use it as they see fit.</string>
    <string name="BrowserSigninTitle">Browser sign in settings</string>
    <string name="BrowsingDataLifetimeDesc">Configures browsing data lifetime settings for Google Chrome. This policy allows admins to configure (per data-type) when data is deleted by the browser. This is useful for customers that work with sensitive customer data. Warning: Setting this policy can impact and permanently remove local personal data. It is recommended to test your settings before deploying to prevent accidental deletion of personal data. The available data types are 'browsing_history', 'download_history', 'cookies_and_other_site_data', 'cached_images_and_files', 'password_signin', 'autofill', 'site_settings' and 'hosted_app_data'. 'download_history' and 'hosted_app_data' are not supported on Android. The browser will automatically remove data of selected types that is older than 'time_to_live_in_hours'. The minimum value that can be set is 1 hour. The deletion of expired data will happen 15 seconds after the browser starts then every 30 minutes while the browser is running. The user will stay signed into their Google account when deleting cookies. Until Chrome 114, this policy required the SyncDisabled policy to be set to true. Starting Chrome 115, setting this policy will disable sync for the respective data types if neither `Chrome Sync` is disabled by setting the SyncDisabled policy nor BrowserSignin is disabled.</string>
    <string name="BrowsingDataLifetimeTitle">Browsing Data Lifetime Settings</string>
    <string name="BuiltInDnsClientEnabledDesc">This policy controls which software stack is used to communicate with the DNS server: the Operating System DNS client, or Google Chrome's built-in DNS client. This policy does not affect which DNS servers are used: if, for example, the operating system is configured to use an enterprise DNS server, that same server would be used by the built-in DNS client. It also does not control if DNS-over-HTTPS is used; Google Chrome will always use the built-in resolver for DNS-over-HTTPS requests. Please see the DnsOverHttpsMode policy for information on controlling DNS-over-HTTPS. If this policy is set to Enabled or is left unset, the built-in DNS client will be used. If this policy is set to Disabled, the built-in DNS client will only be used when DNS-over-HTTPS is in use.</string>
    <string name="BuiltInDnsClientEnabledTitle">Use built-in DNS client</string>
    <string name="CACertificatesDesc">A list of TLS certificates that should be trusted by Google Chrome for server authentication. Certificates should be base64-encoded.</string>
    <string name="CACertificatesTitle">TLS certificates that should be trusted by Google Chrome for server authentication</string>
    <string name="CACertificatesWithConstraintsDesc">A list of TLS certificates that should be trusted by Google Chrome for server authentication, with constraints added outside the certificate. If no constraint of a certain type is present, then any name of that type is allowed. Certificates should be base64-encoded. At least one constraint must be specified for each certificate.</string>
    <string name="CACertificatesWithConstraintsTitle">TLS certificates that should be trusted by Google Chrome for server authentication with constraints</string>
    <string name="CADistrustedCertificatesDesc">A list of certificate public keys that should be distrusted by Google Chrome for TLS server authentication. The policy value is a list of base64-encoded X.509 certificates. Any certificate with a matching SPKI (SubjectPublicKeyInfo) will be distrusted.</string>
    <string name="CADistrustedCertificatesTitle">TLS certificates that should be distrusted by Google Chrome for server authentication</string>
    <string name="CAHintCertificatesDesc">A list of certificates that are not trusted or distrusted in Google Chrome but can be used as hints for path-building. Certificates should be base64-encoded.</string>
    <string name="CAHintCertificatesTitle">TLS certificates that are not trusted or distrusted but can be used in path-building for server authentication</string>
    <string name="CAPlatformIntegrationEnabledDesc">If enabled(or not set), user-added TLS certificates from platform trust stores will be used in path-building for TLS server authentication. If disabled, user-added TLS certificates from platform trust stores will not be used in path-building for TLS server authentication.</string>
    <string name="CAPlatformIntegrationEnabledTitle">Use user-added TLS certificates from platform trust stores for server authentication</string>
    <string name="CORSNonWildcardRequestHeadersSupportDesc">Configures support of CORS non-wildcard request headers. Google Chrome version 97 introduces support for CORS non-wildcard request headers. When scripts make a cross-origin network request via fetch() and XMLHttpRequest with a script-added Authorization header, the header must be explicitly allowed by the Access-Control-Allow-Headers header in the CORS preflight response. "Explicitly" here means that the wild card symbol "*" doesn't cover the Authorization header. See https://chromestatus.com/feature/5742041264816128 for more detail. If this policy is not set, or set to True, Google Chrome will support the CORS non-wildcard request headers and behave as described above. When this policy is set to False, chrome will allow the wildcard symbol ("*") in the Access-Control-Allow-Headers header in the CORS preflight response to cover the Authorization header. This Enterprise policy is temporary; it's intended to be removed in the future.</string>
    <string name="CORSNonWildcardRequestHeadersSupportTitle">CORS non-wildcard request headers support</string>
    <string name="CertificateTransparencyEnforcementDisabledForCasDesc">Setting the policy turns off enforcement of Certificate Transparency disclosure requirements for a list of subjectPublicKeyInfo hashes. Enterprise hosts can keep using certificates that otherwise wouldn't be trusted (because they weren't properly publicly disclosed). To turn off enforcement, the hash must meet one of these conditions: * It's of the server certificate's subjectPublicKeyInfo. * It's of a subjectPublicKeyInfo that appears in a Certificate Authority (CA) certificate in the certificate chain. That CA certificate is constrained through the X.509v3 nameConstraints extension, one or more directoryName nameConstraints are present in the permittedSubtrees, and the directoryName has an organizationName attribute. * It's of a subjectPublicKeyInfo that appears in a CA certificate in the certificate chain, the CA certificate has one or more organizationName attributes in the certificate Subject, and the server's certificate has the same number of organizationName attributes, in the same order, and with byte-for-byte identical values. Specify a subjectPublicKeyInfo hash by linking the hash algorithm name, a slash, and the Base64 encoding of that hash algorithm applied to the DER-encoded subjectPublicKeyInfo of the specified certificate. Base64 encoding format matches that of an SPKI Fingerprint. The only recognized hash algorithm is sha256; others are ignored. Leaving the policy unset means that if certificates requiring disclosure through Certificate Transparency aren't disclosed, then Google Chrome doesn't trust those certificates.</string>
    <string name="CertificateTransparencyEnforcementDisabledForCasTitle">Disable Certificate Transparency enforcement for a list of subjectPublicKeyInfo hashes</string>
    <string name="CertificateTransparencyEnforcementDisabledForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy turns off Certificate Transparency disclosure requirements for the hostnames in the specified URLs. While making it harder to detect misissued certificates, hosts can keep using certificates that otherwise wouldn't be trusted (because they weren't properly publicly disclosed). Leaving the policy unset means that if certificates requiring disclosure through Certificate Transparency aren't disclosed, then Google Chrome doesn't trust those certificates. A URL pattern follows this format ( https://support.google.com/chrome/a?p=url_blocklist_filter_format ). However, because the validity of certificates for a given hostname is independent of the scheme, port, or path, Google Chrome only considers the hostname portion of the URL. Wildcard hosts aren't supported.</string>
    <string name="CertificateTransparencyEnforcementDisabledForUrlsTitle">Disable Certificate Transparency enforcement for a list of URLs</string>
    <string name="ChromeForTestingAllowedDesc">Controls whether users may use Chrome for Testing. If this policy is set to Enabled or not set, users may install and run Chrome for Testing. If this policy is set to Disabled, users are not allowed to run Chrome for Testing. Users will still be able to install Chrome for Testing, however it will not run with the profiles where this policy is set to Disabled.</string>
    <string name="ChromeForTestingAllowedTitle">Allow Chrome for Testing</string>
    <string name="ChromeVariationsDesc">Configuring this policy allows to specify which variations are allowed to be applied in Google Chrome. Variations provide a means for offering modifications to Google Chrome without shipping a new version of the browser by selectively enabling or disabling already existing features. See https://support.google.com/chrome/a?p=Manage_the_Chrome_variations_framework for more information. Setting the VariationsEnabled (value 0), or leaving the policy not set allows all variations to be applied to the browser. Setting the CriticalFixesOnly (value 1), allows only variations considered critical security or stability fixes to be applied to Google Chrome. Setting the VariationsDisabled (value 2), prevent all variations from being applied to the browser. Please note that this mode can potentially prevent the Google Chrome developers from providing critical security fixes in a timely manner and is thus not recommended.</string>
    <string name="ChromeVariationsTitle">Determine the availability of variations</string>
    <string name="ClearHistory">Clean up history</string>
    <string name="ClipboardAllowedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify sites that can use the clipboard site permission. This does not include all clipboard operations on origins matching the patterns. For instance, users will still be able to paste using keyboard shortcuts as this isn't gated by the clipboard site permission. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultClipboardSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="ClipboardAllowedForUrlsTitle">Allow clipboard on these sites</string>
    <string name="ClipboardBlockedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify sites that can't use the clipboard site permission. This does not include all clipboard operations on origins matching the patterns. For instance, users will still be able to paste using keyboard shortcuts as this isn't gated by the clipboard site permission. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultClipboardSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="ClipboardBlockedForUrlsTitle">Block clipboard on these sites</string>
    <string name="CloudManagementEnrollmentTokenDesc">Setting the policy means Google Chrome tries to register itself with Chrome Enterprise Core browser management. The value of this policy is an enrollment token you can retrieve from the Google Admin console. See https://support.google.com/chrome/a/answer/9301891 for details.</string>
    <string name="CloudManagementEnrollmentTokenTitle">The enrollment token of cloud policy</string>
    <string name="CloudPolicyOverridesPlatformPolicyDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled means cloud policy takes precedence if it conflicts with platform policy. Setting the policy to Disabled or leaving it unset means platform policy takes precedence if it conflicts with cloud policy. This mandatory policy affects machine scope cloud policies. This policy is specific to Google Chrome and does not affect Google Update because they are independent applications. Google Update has a separate policy with the same name.</string>
    <string name="CloudPolicyOverridesPlatformPolicyTitle">Google Chrome cloud policy overrides Platform policy.</string>
    <string name="CloudUserPolicyMergeDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled allows policies associated with a managed account to be merged into machine-level policies. Setting the policy to Disabled or leaving it unset prevents user-level cloud policies from being merged with policies from any other sources. Only policies originating from secure users can take precedence. A secure user is affiliated with the organization that manages their browser using Chrome Enterprise Core. All other user-level policies will have default precedence. Policies that need to be merged also need to be set in either PolicyListMultipleSourceMergeList or PolicyDictionaryMultipleSourceMergeList. This policy will be ignored if neither of the two aforementioned policies is configured.</string>
    <string name="CloudUserPolicyMergeTitle">Enables merging of user cloud policies into machine-level policies</string>
    <string name="CloudUserPolicyOverridesCloudMachinePolicyDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled allows policies associated with a managed account to take precedence if they conflict with Chrome Enterprise Core browser policies. Setting the policy to Disabled or leaving it unset causes user-level cloud policies to have default priority. Only policies originating from secure users can take precedence. A secure user is affiliated with the organization that manages their browser using Chrome Enterprise Core. All other user-level policies will have default precedence. The policy can be combined with CloudPolicyOverridesPlatformPolicy. If both policies are enabled, user cloud policies will also take precedence over conflicting platform policies.</string>
    <string name="CloudUserPolicyOverridesCloudMachinePolicyTitle">Allow user cloud policies to override Chrome Browser Cloud Management policies.</string>
    <string name="ComponentUpdatesEnabledDesc">Enables component updates for all components in Google Chrome when not set or set to enabled. If set to disabled, updates to components are disabled. However, some components are exempt from this policy: updates to any component that does not contain executable code and is critical for the security of the browser will not be disabled. Examples of such components include the certificate revocation lists and subresource filters.</string>
    <string name="ComponentUpdatesEnabledTitle">Enable component updates in Google Chrome</string>
    <string name="ContextualSearchEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to True or leaving it unset makes Touch to Search available to the user, and they can turn the feature on or off. Setting the policy to False turns Touch to Search off completely.</string>
    <string name="ContextualSearchEnabledTitle">Enable Touch to Search</string>
    <string name="CookiesAllowedForUrlsDesc">Allows you to set a list of url patterns that specify sites which are allowed to set cookies. URL patterns may be a single URL indicating that the site may use cookies on all top-level sites. Patterns may also be two URLs delimited by a comma. The first specifies the site that should be allowed to use cookies. The second specifies the top-level site that the first value should be applied on. If you use a pair of URLs, the first value in the pair supports * but the second value does not. Using * for the first value indicates that all sites may use cookies when the second URL is the top-level site. If this policy is left not set the global default value will be used for all sites either from the DefaultCookiesSetting or BlockThirdPartyCookies policies if they are set, or the user's personal configuration otherwise. See also policies CookiesBlockedForUrls and CookiesSessionOnlyForUrls. Note that there must be no conflicting URL patterns between these three policies - it is unspecified which policy takes precedence. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. * is not an accepted value for this policy.</string>
    <string name="CookiesAllowedForUrlsTitle">Allow cookies on these sites</string>
    <string name="CookiesBlockedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you make a list of URL patterns that specify sites that can't set cookies. Leaving the policy unset results in the use of DefaultCookiesSetting for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. While no specific policy takes precedence, see CookiesAllowedForUrls and CookiesSessionOnlyForUrls. URL patterns among these 3 policies must not conflict. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. * is not an accepted value for this policy.</string>
    <string name="CookiesBlockedForUrlsTitle">Block cookies on these sites</string>
    <string name="CookiesSessionOnlyForUrlsDesc">Unless the RestoreOnStartup policy is set to permanently restore URLs from previous sessions, then setting CookiesSessionOnlyForUrls lets you make a list of URL patterns that specify sites that can and can't set cookies for one session. Leaving the policy unset results in the use of DefaultCookiesSetting for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. URLs not covered by the patterns specified also result in the use of defaults. While no specific policy takes precedence, see CookiesBlockedForUrls and CookiesAllowedForUrls. URL patterns among these 3 policies must not conflict. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. * is not an accepted value for this policy.</string>
    <string name="CookiesSessionOnlyForUrlsTitle">Limit cookies from matching URLs to the current session</string>
    <string name="DataURLWhitespacePreservationEnabledDesc">This policy provides a temporary opt-out for changes to how Chrome handles whitepsace in data URLS. Previously, whitespace would be kept only if the top level media type was text or contained the media type string xml. Now, whitespace will be preserved in all data URLs, regardless of media type. If this policy is left unset or is set to True, the new behavior is enabled. When this policy is set to False, the old behavior is enabled.</string>
    <string name="DataURLWhitespacePreservationEnabledTitle">DataURL Whitespace Preservation for all media types</string>
    <string name="DataUrlInSvgUseEnabledDesc">This policy enables Data URL support for SVGUseElement, which will be disabled by default starting in M119. If this policy is set to Enabled, Data URLs will continue to work in SVGUseElement. If this policy is set to Disabled or not set, Data URLs won't work in SVGUseElement.</string>
    <string name="DataUrlInSvgUseEnabledTitle">Data URL support for SVGUseElement.</string>
    <string name="DefaultClipboardSettingDesc">Setting the policy to 2 blocks sites from using the clipboard site permission. Setting the policy to 3 or leaving it unset lets the user change the setting and decide if the clipboard APIs are available when a site wants to use one. This policy can be overridden for specific URL patterns using the ClipboardAllowedForUrls and ClipboardBlockedForUrls policies. This policy only affects clipboard operations controlled by the clipboard site permission, and does not affect sanitized clipboard writes or trusted copy and paste operations.</string>
    <string name="DefaultClipboardSettingTitle">Default clipboard setting</string>
    <string name="DefaultCookiesSettingDesc">Unless the RestoreOnStartup policy is set to permanently restore URLs from previous sessions, then setting CookiesSessionOnlyForUrls lets you make a list of URL patterns that specify sites that can and can't set cookies for one session. Leaving the policy unset results in the use of DefaultCookiesSetting for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. URLs not covered by the patterns specified also result in the use of defaults. While no specific policy takes precedence, see CookiesBlockedForUrls and CookiesAllowedForUrls. URL patterns among these 3 policies must not conflict.</string>
    <string name="DefaultCookiesSettingTitle">Default cookies setting</string>
    <string name="DefaultGeolocationSettingDesc">Setting the policy to 1 lets sites track the users' physical location as the default state. Setting the policy to 2 denies this tracking by default. You can set the policy to ask whenever a site wants to track the users' physical location. Leaving the policy unset means the AskGeolocation policy applies, but users can change this setting.</string>
    <string name="DefaultGeolocationSettingTitle">Default geolocation setting</string>
    <string name="DefaultJavaScriptJitSettingDesc">Allows you to set whether Google Chrome will run the v8 JavaScript engine with JIT (Just In Time) compiler enabled or not. Disabling the JavaScript JIT will mean that Google Chrome may render web content more slowly, and may also disable parts of JavaScript including WebAssembly. Disabling the JavaScript JIT may allow Google Chrome to render web content in a more secure configuration. This policy can be overridden for specific URL patterns using the JavaScriptJitAllowedForSites and JavaScriptJitBlockedForSites policies. If this policy is left not set, JavaScript JIT is enabled.</string>
    <string name="DefaultJavaScriptJitSettingTitle">Control use of JavaScript JIT</string>
    <string name="DefaultJavaScriptOptimizerSettingDesc">Allows you to set whether Google Chrome will run the v8 JavaScript engine with more advanced JavaScript optimizations enabled. Disabling JavaScript optimizations (by setting this policy's value to 2) will mean that Google Chrome may render web content more slowly. This policy can be overridden for specific URL patterns using the JavaScriptOptimizerAllowedForSites and JavaScriptOptimizerBlockedForSites policies. If this policy is left not set, JavaScript optimizations are enabled.</string>
    <string name="DefaultJavaScriptOptimizerSettingTitle">Control use of JavaScript optimizers</string>
    <string name="DefaultJavaScriptSettingDesc">Setting the policy to 1 lets websites run JavaScript. Setting the policy to 2 denies JavaScript. Leaving it unset allows JavaScript, but users can change this setting.</string>
    <string name="DefaultJavaScriptSettingTitle">Default JavaScript setting</string>
    <string name="DefaultNotificationsSettingDesc">Setting the policy to 1 lets websites display desktop notifications. Setting the policy to 2 denies desktop notifications. Leaving it unset means AskNotifications applies, but users can change this setting.</string>
    <string name="DefaultNotificationsSettingTitle">Default notification setting</string>
    <string name="DefaultPopupsSettingDesc">Setting the policy to 1 lets websites display pop-ups. Setting the policy to 2 denies pop-ups. Leaving it unset means BlockPopups applies, but users can change this setting.</string>
    <string name="DefaultPopupsSettingTitle">Default pop-ups setting</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderAlternateURLsDesc">If DefaultSearchProviderEnabled is on, then setting DefaultSearchProviderAlternateURLs specifies a list of alternate URLs for extracting search terms from the search engine. The URLs should include the string '{searchTerms}'. Leaving DefaultSearchProviderAlternateURLs unset means no alternate URLs are used to extract search terms.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderAlternateURLsTitle">List of alternate URLs for the default search provider</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled means a default search is performed when a user enters non-URL text in the address bar. To specify the default search provider, set the rest of the default search policies. If you leave those policies empty, the user can choose the default provider. Setting the policy to Disabled means there's no search when the user enters non-URL text in the address bar. The Disabled value is not supported by the Google Admin console. If you set the policy, users can't change it in Google Chrome. If not set, the default search provider is on, and users can set the search provider list. On Microsoft® Windows®, this policy is only available on instances that are joined to a Microsoft® Active Directory® domain, joined to Microsoft® Azure® Active Directory® or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core. On macOS, this policy is only available on instances that are managed via MDM, joined to a domain via MCX or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderEnabledTitle">Enable the default search provider</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderEncodingsDesc">If DefaultSearchProviderEnabled is on, setting DefaultSearchProviderEncodings specifies the character encodings supported by the search provider. Encodings are code page names such as UTF-8, GB2312, and ISO-8859-1. They're tried in the order provided. Leaving DefaultSearchProviderEncodings unset puts UTF-8 in use.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderEncodingsTitle">Default search provider encodings</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderImageURLDesc">If DefaultSearchProviderEnabled is on, then setting DefaultSearchProviderImageURL specifies the URL of the search engine used for image search. (If DefaultSearchProviderImageURLPostParams is set, then image search requests use the POST method instead.) Leaving DefaultSearchProviderImageURL unset means no image search is used. If image search uses the GET method, then the URL must specify image parameters using a valid combination of the following placeholders: '{google:imageURL}', '{google:imageOriginalHeight}', '{google:imageOriginalWidth}', '{google:processedImageDimensions}', '{google:imageSearchSource}', '{google:imageThumbnail}', '{google:imageThumbnailBase64}'.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderImageURLPostParamsDesc">If DefaultSearchProviderEnabled is on, then setting DefaultSearchProviderImageURLPostParams specifies the parameters during image search with POST. It consists of comma-separated, name-value pairs. If a value is a template parameter, such as {imageThumbnail}, real image thumbnail data replaces it. Leaving DefaultSearchProviderImageURLPostParams unset means image search request is sent using the GET method. The URL must specify the image parameter using a valid combination of the following placeholders depending on what the search provider supports: '{google:imageURL}', '{google:imageOriginalHeight}', '{google:imageOriginalWidth}', '{google:processedImageDimensions}', '{google:imageSearchSource}', '{google:imageThumbnail}', '{google:imageThumbnailBase64}'.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderImageURLPostParamsTitle">Parameters for image URL which uses POST</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderImageURLTitle">Parameter providing search-by-image feature for the default search provider</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderNameDesc">If DefaultSearchProviderEnabled is on, then setting DefaultSearchProviderName specifies the default search provider's name. Leaving DefaultSearchProviderName unset means the hostname specified by the search URL is used.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderNameTitle">Default search provider name</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderSearchURLDesc">If DefaultSearchProviderEnabled is on, then setting DefaultSearchProviderSearchURL specifies the URL of the search engine used during a default search. The URL should include the string '{searchTerms}', replaced in the query by the user's search terms. You can specify Google's search URL as: '{google:baseURL}search?q={searchTerms}&amp;amp;{google:RLZ}{google:originalQueryForSuggestion}{google:assistedQueryStats}{google:searchFieldtrialParameter}{google:searchClient}{google:sourceId}ie={inputEncoding}'.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderSearchURLPostParamsDesc">If DefaultSearchProviderEnabled is on, then setting DefaultSearchProviderSearchURLPostParams specifies the parameters when searching a URL with POST. It consists of comma-separated, name-value pairs. If a value is a template parameter, such as '{searchTerms}', real search terms data replaces it. Leaving DefaultSearchProviderSearchURLPostParams unset means search requests are sent using the GET method.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderSearchURLPostParamsTitle">Parameters for search URL which uses POST</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderSearchURLTitle">Default search provider search URL</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderSuggestURLDesc">If DefaultSearchProviderEnabled is on, then setting DefaultSearchProviderSuggestURL specifies the URL of the search engine to provide search suggestions. The URL should include the string '{searchTerms}', replaced in the query by the user's search terms. You can specify Google's search URL as: '{google:baseURL}complete/search?output=chrome&amp;amp;q={searchTerms}'.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderSuggestURLPostParamsDesc">If DefaultSearchProviderEnabled is on, then setting DefaultSearchProviderSuggestURLPostParams specifies the parameters during suggestion search with POST. It consists of comma-separated, name-value pairs. If a value is a template parameter, such as '{searchTerms}', real search terms data replaces it. Leaving DefaultSearchProviderSuggestURLPostParams unset unset means suggest search requests are sent using the GET method.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderSuggestURLPostParamsTitle">Parameters for suggest URL which uses POST</string>
    <string name="DefaultSearchProviderSuggestURLTitle">Default search provider suggest URL</string>
    <string name="DefaultSensorsSettingDesc">Setting the policy to 1 lets websites access and use sensors such as motion and light. Setting the policy to 2 denies access to sensors. Leaving it unset means AllowSensors applies, but users can change this setting.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSensorsSettingTitle">Default sensors setting</string>
    <string name="DefaultSerialGuardSettingDesc">Setting the policy to 3 lets websites ask for access to serial ports. Setting the policy to 2 denies access to serial ports. Leaving it unset lets websites ask for access, but users can change this setting.</string>
    <string name="DefaultSerialGuardSettingTitle">Control use of the Serial API</string>
    <string name="DefaultWebBluetoothGuardSettingDesc">Setting the policy to 3 lets websites ask for access to nearby Bluetooth devices. Setting the policy to 2 denies access to nearby Bluetooth devices. Leaving the policy unset lets sites ask for access, but users can change this setting.</string>
    <string name="DefaultWebBluetoothGuardSettingTitle">Control use of the Web Bluetooth API</string>
    <string name="DefaultWebUsbGuardSettingDesc">Setting the policy to 3 lets websites ask for access to connected USB devices. Setting the policy to 2 denies access to connected USB devices. Leaving it unset lets websites ask for access, but users can change this setting.</string>
    <string name="DefaultWebUsbGuardSettingTitle">Control use of the WebUSB API</string>
    <string name="DisableAuthNegotiateCnameLookupDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled skips CNAME lookup. The server name is used as entered when generating the Kerberos SPN. Setting the policy to Disabled or leaving it unset means CNAME lookup determines the canonical name of the server when generating the Kerberos SPN.</string>
    <string name="DisableAuthNegotiateCnameLookupTitle">Disable CNAME lookup when negotiating Kerberos authentication</string>
    <string name="DisableSafeBrowsingProceedAnywayDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled prevents users from proceeding past the warning page the Safe Browsing service shows to the malicious site. This policy only prevents users from proceeding on Safe Browsing warnings such as malware and phishing, not for SSL certificate-related issues such as invalid or expired certificates. Setting the policy to Disabled or leaving it unset means users can choose to proceed to the flagged site after the warning appears. See more about Safe Browsing ( https://developers.google.com/safe-browsing ).</string>
    <string name="DisableSafeBrowsingProceedAnywayTitle">Disable proceeding from the Safe Browsing warning page</string>
    <string name="DnsOverHttpsModeDesc">Controls the mode of the DNS-over-HTTPS resolver. Please note that this policy will only set the default mode for each query. The mode may be overridden for special types of queries such as requests to resolve a DNS-over-HTTPS server hostname. The "off" mode will disable DNS-over-HTTPS. The "automatic" mode will send DNS-over-HTTPS queries first if a DNS-over-HTTPS server is available and may fallback to sending insecure queries on error. The "secure" mode will only send DNS-over-HTTPS queries and will fail to resolve on error. On Android Pie and above, if DNS-over-TLS is active, Google Chrome will not send insecure DNS requests. If this policy is unset, for managed devices DNS-over-HTTPS queries will not be sent. Otherwise, the browser may send DNS-over-HTTPS requests to a resolver associated with the user's configured system resolver.</string>
    <string name="DnsOverHttpsModeTitle">Controls the mode of DNS-over-HTTPS</string>
    <string name="DnsOverHttpsTemplatesDesc">The URI template of the desired DNS-over-HTTPS resolver. To specify multiple DNS-over-HTTPS resolvers, separate the corresponding URI templates with spaces. If the DnsOverHttpsMode is set to "secure" then this policy must be set and not empty. On Google ChromeOS only, either this policy or the DnsOverHttpsTemplatesWithIdentifiers must be set, otherwise the DNS resolution will fail. If the DnsOverHttpsMode is set to "automatic" and this policy is set then the URI templates specified will be used; if this policy is unset then hardcoded mappings will be used to attempt to upgrade the user's current DNS resolver to a DoH resolver operated by the same provider. If the URI template contains a dns variable, requests to the resolver will use GET; otherwise requests will use POST. Incorrectly formatted templates will be ignored.</string>
    <string name="DnsOverHttpsTemplatesTitle">Specify URI template of desired DNS-over-HTTPS resolver</string>
    <string name="DomainReliabilityAllowedDesc">If this policy is set false, domain reliability diagnostic data reporting is disabled and no data is sent to Google. If this policy is set true or not set, domain reliability diagnostic data reporting will follow the behavior of MetricsReportingEnabled for Google Chrome or DeviceMetricsReportingEnabled for Google ChromeOS.</string>
    <string name="DomainReliabilityAllowedTitle">Allow reporting of domain reliability related data</string>
    <string name="DownloadRestrictionsDesc">Setting the policy means users can't bypass download security decisions. There are many types of download warnings within Chrome, which roughly break down into these categories (learn more about Safe Browsing verdicts https://support.google.com/chrome/?p=ib_download_blocked): * Malicious, as flagged by the Safe Browsing server * Uncommon or unwanted, as flagged by the Safe Browsing server * A dangerous file type (e.g. all SWF downloads and many EXE downloads) Setting the policy blocks different subsets of these, depending on it's value: 0: No special restrictions. Default. 1: Blocks malicious files flagged by the Safe Browsing server AND Blocks all dangerous file types. Only recommended for OUs/browsers/users that have a high tolerance for False Positives. 2: Blocks malicious files flagged by the Safe Browsing server AND Blocks uncommon or unwanted files flagged by the Safe Browsing server AND Blocks all dangerous file types. Only recommended for OUs/browsers/users that have a high tolerance for False Positives. 3: Blocks all downloads. Not recommended, except for special use cases. 4: Blocks malicious files flagged by the Safe Browsing server, does not block dangerous file types. Recommended. Note: These restrictions apply to downloads triggered from webpage content, as well as the Download link… menu option. They don't apply to the download of the currently displayed page or to saving as PDF from the printing options. Read more about Safe Browsing ( https://developers.google.com/safe-browsing ).</string>
    <string name="DownloadRestrictionsTitle">Allow download restrictions</string>
    <string name="EditBookmarksEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to True or leaving it unset lets users add, remove, modify, or upload bookmarks. Setting the policy to False means users can't add, remove, modify or upload bookmarks. They can still use existing bookmarks.</string>
    <string name="EditBookmarksEnabledTitle">Enable or disable bookmark editing</string>
    <string name="EnableExperimentalPoliciesDesc">Allows Google Chrome to load experimental policies. WARNING: Experimental policies are unsupported and subject to change or be removed without notice in future version of the browser! An experimental policy may not be finished or still have known or unknown defects. It may be changed or even removed without any notification. By enabling experimental policies, you could lose browser data or compromise your security or privacy. If a policy is not in the list and it's not officially released, its value will be ignored on Beta and Stable channel. If a policy is in the list and it's not officially released, its value will be applied. This policy has no effect on already released policies.</string>
    <string name="EnableExperimentalPoliciesTitle">Enables experimental policies</string>
    <string name="EnableMediaRouterDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled or leaving it unset turns on Google Cast, which users can launch from the app menu, page context menus, media controls on Cast-enabled websites, and (if shown) the Cast toolbar icon. Setting the policy to Disabled turns off Google Cast.</string>
    <string name="EnableMediaRouterTitle">Enable Google Cast</string>
    <string name="EncryptedClientHelloEnabledDesc">Encrypted ClientHello (ECH) is an extension to TLS to encrypt sensitive fields of the ClientHello and improve privacy. If this policy is not configured, or is set to enabled, Google Chrome will follow the default rollout process for ECH. If it is disabled, Google Chrome will not enable ECH. When the feature is enabled, Google Chrome may or may not use ECH depending on server support, availability of the HTTPS DNS record, or rollout status. ECH is an evolving protocol, so Google Chrome's implementation is subject to change. As such, this policy is a temporary measure to control the initial experimental implementation. It will be replaced with final controls as the protocol finalizes.</string>
    <string name="EncryptedClientHelloEnabledTitle">Enable TLS Encrypted ClientHello</string>
    <string name="EnterpriseAuthenticationAppLinkPolicyDesc">Allows you to specify configs for authentication urls in Android WebView. These Authentication urls would be treated special by Android WebView, such that during authentication when webpage in Android WebView is navigated to authentication urls, corresponding Identity providers authenticator app that can handle this authentication URL would be launched. This flow of launching the Identity providers authenticator app would be used by the Identity providers to enable use cases like providing SSO across apps or provide better security by collecting zero trust device signals to understand device posture during authentication. If there is no valid app installed to handle authentication url on the device, navigation will continue in Android WebView. Authentication URL pattern has to be formatted according to https://support.google.com/chrome/a?p=url_blocklist_filter_format.</string>
    <string name="EnterpriseAuthenticationAppLinkPolicyTitle">External authentication app launch URLs</string>
    <string name="EnterpriseHardwarePlatformAPIEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to True lets extensions installed by enterprise policy use the Enterprise Hardware Platform API. Setting the policy to False or leaving it unset prevents extensions from using this API. Note: This policy also applies to component extensions, such as the Hangout Services extension.</string>
    <string name="EnterpriseHardwarePlatformAPIEnabledTitle">Enables managed extensions to use the Enterprise Hardware Platform API</string>
    <string name="ErrorProxyInternetNotReachable">Web cannot accesse Web through the specified proxy server</string>
    <string name="ErrorProxyServerNotReachable">The proxy server cannot be accessed</string>
    <string name="ErrorProxySettingsNotValid">Invalid proxy Settings</string>
    <string name="ExplicitlyAllowedNetworkPortsDesc">There is a list of restricted ports built into Google Chrome. Connections to these ports will fail. This setting permits bypassing that list. The value is a comma-separated list of zero or more ports that outgoing connections will be permitted on. Ports are restricted to prevent Google Chrome being used as a vector to exploit various network vulnerabilities. Setting this policy may expose your network to attacks. This policy is intended as a temporary workaround for errors with code "ERR_UNSAFE_PORT" while migrating a service running on a blocked port to a standard port (ie. port 80 or 443). Malicious websites can easily detect that this policy is set, and for what ports, and use that information to target attacks. Each port here is labelled with a date that it can be unblocked until. After that date the port will be restricted regardless of this setting. Leaving the value empty or unset means that all restricted ports will be blocked. If there is a mixture of valid and invalid values, the valid ones will be applied. This policy overrides the "--explicitly-allowed-ports" command-line option.</string>
    <string name="ExplicitlyAllowedNetworkPortsTitle">Explicitly allowed network ports</string>
    <string name="FeedbackSurveysEnabledDesc">Google Chrome in-product surveys collect user feedback for the browser. Survey responses are not associated with user accounts. When this policy is Enabled or not set, in-product surveys may be shown to users. When this policy is Disabled, in-product surveys are not shown to users. This policy has no effect if MetricsReportingEnabled is set to Disabled, which disables in-product surveys as well.</string>
    <string name="FeedbackSurveysEnabledTitle">Specifies whether in-product Google Chrome surveys are shown to users.</string>
    <string name="FileChooserPrompt">Select File</string>
    <string name="FirstPartySetsEnabledDesc">This policy is provided as a way to opt-out of the First-Party Sets feature. When this policy is unset or set to Enabled, the First-Party Sets feature is enabled. When this policy is set to Disabled, the First-Party Sets feature is disabled. It controls whether Chrome supports First-Party Sets related integrations. This is the equivalent of the RelatedWebsiteSetsEnabled policy. Either policy may be used, but this one will be deprecated soon so the RelatedWebsiteSetsEnabled policy is preferred. They both have the same effect on the browser's behavior.</string>
    <string name="FirstPartySetsEnabledTitle">Enable First-Party Sets.</string>
    <string name="FirstPartySetsOverridesDesc">This policy provides a way to override the list of sets the browser uses for First-Party Sets features. Each set in the browser's list of First-Party Sets must meet the requirements of a First-Party Set. A First-Party Set must contain a primary site and one or more member sites. A set can also contain a list of service sites that it owns, as well as a map from a site to all of its ccTLD variants. See https://github.com/WICG/first-party-sets for more information on First-Party Sets are used by Google Chrome. All sites in a First-Party Set must be a registrable domain served over HTTPS. Each site in a First-Party Set must also be unique, meaning a site cannot be listed more than once in a First-Party Set. When this policy is given an empty dictionary, the browser uses the public list of First-Party Sets. For all sites in a First-Party Set from the replacements list, if a site is also present on a First-Party Set in the browser's list, then that site will be removed from the browser's First-Party Set. After this, the policy's First-Party Set will be added to the browser's list of First-Party Sets. For all sites in a First-Party Set from the additions list, if a site is also present on a First-Party Set in the browser's list, then the browser's First-Party Set will be updated so that the new First-Party Set can be added to the browser's list. After the browser's list has been updated, the policy's First-Party Set will be added to the browser's list of First-Party Sets. The browser's list of First-Party Sets requires that for all sites in its list, no site is in more than one set. This is also required for both the replacements list and the additions list. Similarly, a site cannot be in both the replacements list and the additions list. Wildcards (*) are not supported as a policy value, nor within any First-Party Set in these lists. All sets provided by the policy must be valid First-Party Sets, if they aren't then an appropriate error will be outputted. On Microsoft® Windows®, this policy is only available on instances that are joined to a Microsoft® Active Directory® domain, joined to Microsoft® Azure® Active Directory® or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core. On macOS, this policy is only available on instances that are managed via MDM, joined to a domain via MCX or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core. This is the equivalent of the RelatedWebsiteSetsOverrides policy. Either policy may be used, but this one will be deprecated soon so the RelatedWebsiteSetsOverrides policy is preferred. They both have the same effect on the browser's behavior.</string>
    <string name="FirstPartySetsOverridesTitle">Override First-Party Sets.</string>
    <string name="ForceGoogleSafeSearchDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled means SafeSearch in Google Search is always active, and users can't change this setting. Setting the policy to Disabled or leaving it unset means SafeSearch in Google Search is not enforced.</string>
    <string name="ForceGoogleSafeSearchTitle">Force Google SafeSearch</string>
    <string name="ForcePermissionPolicyUnloadDefaultEnabledDesc">unload event handlers are being deprecated. Whether they fire depends on the unload Permissions-Policy. Currently, they are allowed by policy by default. In the future they will gradually move to being disallowed by default and sites must explicitly enable them using Permissions-Policy headers. This enterprise policy can be used to opt out of this gradual deprecation by forcing the default to remain as enabled. Pages may depend on unload event handlers to save data or signal the end of a user session to the server. This is not recommended as it is unreliable and impacts performance by blocking use of BackForwardCache. Recommended alternatives exist, however the unload event has been used for a long time. Some applications may still rely on them. If this policy is set to false or not set, then unload events handlers will be gradually deprecated in-line with the deprecation rollout and sites which do not set Permissions-Policy header will stop firing `unload` events. If this policy is set to true then unload event handlers will continue to work by default. NOTE: This policy had an incorrectly documented default of `true` in M117. The unload event did and will not change in M117, so this policy has no effect in that version.</string>
    <string name="ForcePermissionPolicyUnloadDefaultEnabledTitle">Controls whether unload event handlers can be disabled.</string>
    <string name="ForceYouTubeRestrictDesc">Setting the policy enforces a minimum Restricted mode on YouTube and prevents users from picking a less restricted mode. If you set it to: * Strict, Strict Restricted mode on YouTube is always active. * Moderate, the user may only pick Moderate Restricted mode and Strict Restricted mode on YouTube, but can't turn off Restricted mode. * Off or if no value is set, Restricted mode on YouTube isn't enforced by Chrome. External policies such as YouTube policies might still enforce Restricted mode.</string>
    <string name="ForceYouTubeRestrictTitle">Force minimum YouTube Restricted Mode</string>
    <string name="GenAILocalFoundationalModelSettingsDesc">Configure how Google Chrome downloads the foundational GenAI model and uses for inference locally. When the policy is set to Allowed (0) or not set, the model is downloaded automatically, and used for inference. When the policy is set to Disabled (1), the model will not be downloaded. On desktop platforms, model downloading can also be disabled by ComponentUpdatesEnabled.</string>
    <string name="GenAILocalFoundationalModelSettingsTitle">Settings for GenAI local foundational model</string>
    <string name="GloballyScopeHTTPAuthCacheEnabledDesc">This policy configures a single global per profile cache with HTTP server authentication credentials. If this policy is unset or disabled, the browser will use the default behavior of cross-site auth, this behavior will be to scope HTTP server authentication credentials by top-level site, so if two sites use resources from the same authenticating domain, credentials will need to be provided independently in the context of both sites. Cached proxy credentials will be reused across sites. If the policy is enabled, HTTP auth credentials entered in the context of one site will automatically be used in the context of another. Enabling this policy leaves sites open to some types of cross-site attacks, and allows users to be tracked across sites even without cookies by adding entries to the HTTP auth cache using credentials embedded in URLs. This policy is intended to give enterprises depending on the legacy behavior a chance to update their login procedures, and will be removed in the future.</string>
    <string name="GloballyScopeHTTPAuthCacheEnabledTitle">Enable globally scoped HTTP auth cache</string>
    <string name="HSTSPolicyBypassListDesc">Setting the policy specifies a list of hostnames that bypass preloaded HSTS upgrades from http to https. Only single-label hostnames are allowed in this policy, and this policy only applies to "static" HSTS-preloaded entries (for instance, "app", "new", "search", "play"). This policy does not prevent HSTS upgrades for servers that have "dynamically" requested HSTS upgrades using a Strict-Transport-Security response header. Supplied hostnames must be canonicalized: Any IDNs must be converted to their A-label format, and all ASCII letters must be lowercase. This policy only applies to the specific single-label hostnames specified, not to subdomains of those names.</string>
    <string name="HSTSPolicyBypassListTitle">List of names that will bypass the HSTS policy check</string>
    <string name="HappyEyeballsV3EnabledDesc">This feature enables the Happy Eyeballs V3 algorithm to make connection attempts. See https://datatracker.ietf.org/doc/draft-pauly-happy-happyeyeballs-v3 for details. Setting the policy to Enabled means Google Chrome will use the Happy Eyeballs V3 algorithm for connection attempts. Setting the policy to Disabled turns off the Happy Eyeballs V3 algorithm. Not setting the policy, Google Chrome will turn on or off the Happy Eyeballs V3 algorithm based on chrome://flags/#happy-eyeballs-v3. This policy supports dynamic refresh. This policy is a temporary measure and will be removed in future versions of Google Chrome.</string>
    <string name="HappyEyeballsV3EnabledTitle">Use the Happy Eyeballs V3 algorithm</string>
    <string name="HistoryClustersVisibleDesc">This policy controls the visibility of the Chrome history page organized into groups of pages. If the policy is set to Enabled, a Chrome history page organized into groups will be visible at chrome://history/grouped. If the policy is set to Disabled, a Chrome history page organized into groups will not be visible at chrome://history/grouped. If the policy is left unset, a Chrome history page organized into groups will be visible at chrome://history/grouped by default. Please note, if ComponentUpdatesEnabled policy is set to Disabled, but HistoryClustersVisible is set to Enabled or unset, a Chrome history page organized into groups will still be available at chrome://history/grouped, but may be less relevant to the user.</string>
    <string name="HistoryClustersVisibleTitle">Show a view of Chrome history with groups of pages</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_Background_color">Background anti-color</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_Eye_protection">Eye protection barrier</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_addtodownload">Add to download</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_all">Clean all</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_all_history">All Histoty Records</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_clear_success">Clean successfully</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_clear_video_cache">Clean video Cache</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_cookies_cache">Clean Cookies</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_custom1_cache">CustomUA-1</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_custom2_cache">CustomUA-2</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_custom3_cache">CustomUA-3</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_daohang_settles">Navigation page settings</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_download_file">Download</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_edittype">such as https://www.baidu.com/s?wd=yjbrowser , then type https://www.baidu.com/s?wd=</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_fullscreenmode_settles">Hide Status Bar</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_havecopy">Copied to clipboard</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_havecopyo">
Copy the password and open Taobao</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_havefind">Start testing coupons</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_history_cache">Clean history</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_if_candownload">Download may currently be supported</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_if_openapp">Open app?</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_inputhead">please enter the engine prefix</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_inputua">Please enter customUA</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_mobile_iphone_cache">Mobile-Iphone-UA</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_mobile_ua">Default mobileUA</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_music">Music Box</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_network_error">network is unavailable, open the data network orWifi!</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_new_msg">Is already the latest version!</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_nightmode_settle">Night mode settings</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_pc_chrome_ua">PC-Chrome-UA</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_pic_cannot_download">Download is not supported for this picture</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_read_cache">Clean browsing Cache</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_reedit">long press to edit again</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_rule_chain_fail">Failed to get advertising rule chain!</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_scrollauto">Automatic rolling</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_search_cache">Clean search records</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_start">Start testing coupons</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_sys_core">System Kernel</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_taobaoquan">Coupon</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_video_lib">Movie</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_vip">Higharea</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_wangpan">Resources</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_windows">FloatWeb</string>
    <string name="HomeActivity_x5_core">X5 Kernel</string>
    <string name="HomepageLocationDesc">Setting the policy sets the default homepage URL in Google Chrome. You open the homepage using the Home button. On desktop, the RestoreOnStartup policies control the pages that open on startup. If the homepage is set to the New Tab Page, by the user or HomepageIsNewTabPage, this policy has no effect. The URL needs a standard scheme, such as http://example.com or https://example.com. When this policy is set, users can't change their homepage URL in Google Chrome. Leaving both HomepageLocation and HomepageIsNewTabPage unset lets users choose their homepage. On Microsoft® Windows®, this policy is only available on instances that are joined to a Microsoft® Active Directory® domain, joined to Microsoft® Azure® Active Directory® or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core. On macOS, this policy is only available on instances that are managed via MDM, joined to a domain via MCX or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core.</string>
    <string name="HomepageLocationTitle">Configure the home page URL</string>
    <string name="HttpAllowlistDesc">Setting the policy specifies a list of hostnames or hostname patterns (such as '[*.]example.com') that will not be upgraded to HTTPS and will not show an error interstitial if HTTPS-First Mode is enabled. Organizations can use this policy to maintain access to servers that do not support HTTPS, without needing to disable HTTPS Upgrades and/or HTTPS-First Mode. Supplied hostnames must be canonicalized: Any IDNs must be converted to their A-label format, and all ASCII letters must be lowercase. Blanket host wildcards (i.e., "*" or "[*]") are not allowed. Instead, HTTPS-First Mode and HTTPS Upgrades should be explicitly disabled via their specific policies. Note: This policy does not apply to HSTS upgrades.</string>
    <string name="HttpAllowlistTitle">HTTP Allowlist</string>
    <string name="HttpsOnlyModeDesc">This policy controls whether users can enable HTTPS-Only Mode (Always Use Secure Connections) in Settings. HTTPS-Only Mode upgrades all navigations to HTTPS. If this setting is not set or set to allowed, users will be allowed to enable HTTPS-Only Mode. If this setting is set to disallowed, users will not be allowed to enable HTTPS-Only Mode. If this setting is set to force_enabled, HTTPS-Only Mode will be enabled in Strict mode and users will not be able to disable it. If this setting is set to force_balanced_enabled, HTTPS-Only Mode will be enabled in Balanced mode and users will not be able to disable it. force_enabled is supported from M112 onwards, force_balanced_enabled is supported from M129 onwards. If you set this policy to a value that is not supported by the version of Chrome that receives the policy, Chrome will default to the allowed setting. The separate HttpAllowlist policy can be used to exempt specific hostnames or hostname patterns from being upgraded to HTTPS by this feature.</string>
    <string name="HttpsOnlyModeTitle">Allow HTTPS-Only Mode to be enabled</string>
    <string name="HttpsUpgradesEnabledDesc">Google Chrome attempts to upgrade some navigations from HTTP to HTTPS, when possible. This policy can be used to disable this behavior. If set to "true" or left unset, this feature will be enabled by default. The separate HttpAllowlist policy can be used to exempt specific hostnames or hostname patterns from being upgraded to HTTPS by this feature. See also the HttpsOnlyMode policy.</string>
    <string name="HttpsUpgradesEnabledTitle">Enable automatic HTTPS upgrades</string>
    <string name="IPv6ReachabilityOverrideEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to true overrides the IPv6 reachability check. This means that the system will always query AAAA records when resolving host names. It applies to all users and interfaces on the device. Setting the policy to false or leaving it unset does not overrides the IPv6 reachability check. The system only queries AAAA records when it is reachable to a global IPv6 host.</string>
    <string name="IPv6ReachabilityOverrideEnabledTitle">Enable IPv6 reachability check override</string>
    <string name="ImportBookMarkActivity_tip4">app loading has a problem, clean up the cache</string>
    <string name="IncognitoModeAvailabilityDesc">Specifies whether the user may open pages in Incognito mode in Google Chrome. If 'Enabled' is selected or the policy is left unset, pages may be opened in Incognito mode. If 'Disabled' is selected, pages may not be opened in Incognito mode. If 'Forced' is selected, pages may be opened ONLY in Incognito mode. Note that 'Forced' does not work for Android-on-Chrome Note: On iOS, if the policy is changed during a session, it will only take effect on relaunch.</string>
    <string name="IncognitoModeAvailabilityTitle">Incognito mode availability</string>
    <string name="IntensiveWakeUpThrottlingEnabledDesc">When enabled the IntensiveWakeUpThrottling feature causes JavaScript timers in background tabs to be aggressively throttled and coalesced, running no more than once per minute after a page has been backgrounded for 5 minutes or more. This is a web standards compliant feature, but it may break functionality on some websites by causing certain actions to be delayed by up to a minute. However, it results in significant CPU and battery savings when enabled. See https://bit.ly/30b1XR4 for more details. If this policy is set to enabled then the feature will be force enabled, and users will not be able to override this. If this policy is set to disabled then the feature will be force disabled, and users will not be able to override this. If this policy is left unset then the feature will be controlled by its own internal logic, which can be manually configured by users. Note that the policy is applied per renderer process, with the most recent value of the policy setting in force when a renderer process starts. A full restart is required to ensure that all loaded tabs receive a consistent policy setting. It is harmless for processes to be running with different values of this policy.</string>
    <string name="IntensiveWakeUpThrottlingEnabledTitle">Control the IntensiveWakeUpThrottling feature.</string>
    <string name="IsolateOriginsAndroidDesc">Setting the policy means each of the named origins in a comma-separated list runs in a dedicated process on Android. Each named origin's process will only be allowed to contain documents from that origin and its subdomains. For example, specifying https://a1.example.com/ allows https://a2.a1.example.com/ in the same process, but not https://example.com or https://b.example.com. Note that Android isolates certain sensitive sites by default starting in Google Chrome version 77, and this policy extends that mode to isolate specific additional origins. Since Google Chrome 77, you can also specify a range of origins to isolate using a wildcard. For example, specifying https://[*.]corp.example.com will give every origin underneath https://corp.example.com its own dedicated process, including https://corp.example.com itself, https://a1.corp.example.com, and https://a2.a1.corp.example.com. Note that origins isolated by this policy will be unable to script other origins in the same site, which is otherwise possible if two same-site documents modify their document.domain values to match. Administrators should confirm this uncommon behavior is not used on an origin before isolating it. Setting the policy to Disabled turns off any form of site isolation, including isolation of sensitive sites and field trials of IsolateOriginsAndroid, SitePerProcessAndroid, and other site isolation modes. Users can still turn on IsolateOrigins manually, through the command line flag. Leaving the policy unset lets users change this setting. Note: Isolating too many sites on Android may cause performance problems, especially on low-memory devices. This policy applies only to Chrome on Android running on devices with strictly more than 1 GB of RAM. To apply the policy on non-Android platforms, use IsolateOrigins.</string>
    <string name="IsolateOriginsAndroidTitle">Enable Site Isolation for specified origins on Android devices</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptAllowedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify the sites that can run JavaScript. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultJavaScriptSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptAllowedForUrlsTitle">Allow JavaScript on these sites</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptBlockedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify the sites that can't run JavaScript. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultJavaScriptSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed. Note that this policy blocks JavaScript based on whether the origin of the top-level document (usually the page URL that is also displayed in the address bar) matches any of the patterns. Therefore this policy is not appropriate for mitigating web supply-chain attacks. For example, supplying the pattern "https://[*.]foo.com/" will not prevent a page hosted on, say, https://example.com from running a script loaded from https://www.foo.com/example.js. Furthermore, supplying the pattern "https://example.com/" will not prevent a document from https://example.com from running scripts if it is not the top-level document, but embedded as a sub-frame into a page hosted on another origin, say, https://www.bar.com.</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptBlockedForUrlsTitle">Block JavaScript on these sites</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptJitAllowedForSitesDesc">Allows you to set a list of site url patterns that specify sites which are allowed to run JavaScript with JIT (Just In Time) compiler enabled. For detailed information on valid site url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed. JavaScript JIT policy exceptions will only be enforced at a site granularity (eTLD+1). A policy set for only subdomain.site.com will not correctly apply to site.com or subdomain.site.com since they both resolve to the same eTLD+1 (site.com) for which there is no policy. In this case, policy must be set on site.com to apply correctly for both site.com and subdomain.site.com. This policy applies on a frame-by-frame basis and not based on top level origin url alone, so e.g. if site-one.com is listed in the JavaScriptJitAllowedForSites policy but site-one.com loads a frame containing site-two.com then site-one.com will have JavaScript JIT enabled, but site-two.com will use the policy from DefaultJavaScriptJitSetting, if set, or default to JavaScript JIT enabled. If this policy is not set for a site then the policy from DefaultJavaScriptJitSetting applies to the site, if set, otherwise Javascript JIT is enabled for the site.</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptJitAllowedForSitesTitle">Allow JavaScript to use JIT on these sites</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptJitBlockedForSitesDesc">Allows you to set a list of site url patterns that specify sites which are not allowed to run JavaScript JIT (Just In Time) compiler enabled. Disabling the JavaScript JIT will mean that Google Chrome may render web content more slowly, and may also disable parts of JavaScript including WebAssembly. Disabling the JavaScript JIT may allow Google Chrome to render web content in a more secure configuration. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed. JavaScript JIT policy exceptions will only be enforced at a site granularity (eTLD+1). A policy set for only subdomain.site.com will not correctly apply to site.com or subdomain.site.com since they both resolve to the same eTLD+1 (site.com) for which there is no policy. In this case, policy must be set on site.com to apply correctly for both site.com and subdomain.site.com. This policy applies on a frame-by-frame basis and not based on top level origin url alone, so e.g. if site-one.com is listed in the JavaScriptJitBlockedForSites policy but site-one.com loads a frame containing site-two.com then site-one.com will have JavaScript JIT disabled, but site-two.com will use the policy from DefaultJavaScriptJitSetting, if set, or default to JavaScript JIT enabled. If this policy is not set for a site then the policy from DefaultJavaScriptJitSetting applies to the site, if set, otherwise JavaScript JIT is enabled for the site.</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptJitBlockedForSitesTitle">Block JavaScript from using JIT on these sites</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptOptimizerAllowedForSitesDesc">Allows you to set a list of site url patterns that specify sites for which advanced JavaScript optimizations are enabled. For detailed information on valid site url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed. JavaScript optimization policy exceptions will only be enforced at a site granularity (eTLD+1). A policy set for only subdomain.site.com will not correctly apply to site.com or subdomain.site.com since they both resolve to the same eTLD+1 (site.com) for which there is no policy. In this case, policy must be set on site.com to apply correctly for both site.com and subdomain.site.com. This policy applies on a frame-by-frame basis and not based on top level origin url alone, so e.g. if site-one.com is listed in the JavaScriptOptimizerAllowedForSites policy but site-one.com loads a frame containing site-two.com then site-one.com will have JavaScript optimizations enabled, but site-two.com will use the policy from DefaultJavaScriptOptimizerSetting, if set, or default to JavaScript optimizations enabled. Blocklist entries have higher priority than allowlist entries, which in turn have higher priority than the configured default value. If this policy is not set for a site then the policy from DefaultJavaScriptOptimizerSetting applies to the site, if set, otherwise Javascript optimization is enabled for the site.</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptOptimizerAllowedForSitesTitle">Allow JavaScript optimization on these sites</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptOptimizerBlockedForSitesDesc">Allows you to set a list of site url patterns that specify sites for which advanced JavaScript optimizations are disabled. Disabling JavaScript optimizations will mean that Google Chrome may render web content more slowly. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed. JavaScript optimization policy exceptions will only be enforced at a site granularity (eTLD+1). A policy set for only subdomain.site.com will not correctly apply to site.com or subdomain.site.com since they both resolve to the same eTLD+1 (site.com) for which there is no policy. In this case, policy must be set on site.com to apply correctly for both site.com and subdomain.site.com. This policy applies on a frame-by-frame basis and not based on top level origin url alone, so e.g. if site-one.com is listed in the JavaScriptOptimizerBlockedForSites policy but site-one.com loads a frame containing site-two.com then site-one.com will have JavaScript optimizations disabled, but site-two.com will use the policy from DefaultJavaScriptOptimizerSetting, if set, or default to JavaScript optimizations enabled. Blocklist entries have higher priority than allowlist entries, which in turn have higher priority than the configured default value. If this policy is not set for a site then the policy from DefaultJavaScriptOptimizerSetting applies to the site, if set, otherwise JavaScript optimization is enabled for the site.</string>
    <string name="JavaScriptOptimizerBlockedForSitesTitle">Block JavaScript optimizations on these sites</string>
    <string name="LastMonth">Last month</string>
    <string name="LastSevenDays">Past Seven Days</string>
    <string name="LensCameraAssistedSearchEnabledDesc">Leaving the policy unset or setting it to Enabled allows users to search with their cameras using Google Lens. Setting the policy to Disabled means users can't see the Google Lens button in the search box when Google Lens camera assisted search is supported.</string>
    <string name="LensCameraAssistedSearchEnabledTitle">Allow Google Lens camera assisted search</string>
    <string name="ListenToThisPageEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to be true allows users to have eligible web pages read aloud using text-to-speech. This is achieved by server side content distillation and audio synthesis. Setting to false disables this feature. If this policy is set to default or unset, read aloud is enabled.</string>
    <string name="ListenToThisPageEnabledTitle">Enable read aloud (text distillation and text-to-speech synthesis) for web pages</string>
    <string name="LocalNetworkAccessAllowedForUrlsDesc">List of URL patterns. Requests initiated from websites served by matching origins are not subject to Local Network Access checks. If an origin is covered by both this policy and by LocalNetworkAccessBlockedForUrls, LocalNetworkAccessBlockedForUrls takes precedence. For origins not covered by the patterns specified here, the user's personal configuration will apply. For detailed information on valid URL patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. See https://wicg.github.io/local-network-access/ for Local Network Access restrictions.</string>
    <string name="LocalNetworkAccessAllowedForUrlsTitle">Allow sites to make requests to local network endpoints.</string>
    <string name="LocalNetworkAccessBlockedForUrlsDesc">List of URL patterns. Requests initiated from websites served by matching origins are blocked from issuing Local Network Access requests. If an origin is covered by both this policy and by LocalNetworkAccessAllowedForUrls, this policy takes precedence. Depending on the stage of the rollout of Local Network Access, LocalNetworkAccessRestrictionsEnabled may also need to be enabled for this policy to block Local Network Access requests. For origins not covered by the patterns specified here, the user's personal configuration will apply. For detailed information on valid URL patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. See https://wicg.github.io/local-network-access/ for Local Network Access restrictions.</string>
    <string name="LocalNetworkAccessBlockedForUrlsTitle">Block sites from making requests to local network endpoints.</string>
    <string name="LocalNetworkAccessRestrictionsEnabledDesc">When this policy is set to Enabled, any time when a warning is supposed to be displayed in Chrome DevTools due to Local Network Access checks failing, the main request will be blocked instead. When this policy is set to Disabled or unset, Local Network Access requests will use the default handling of these requests. See https://wicg.github.io/local-network-access/ for Local Network Access restrictions.</string>
    <string name="LocalNetworkAccessRestrictionsEnabledTitle">Specifies whether to apply restrictions to requests to local network endpoints</string>
    <string name="LocalNetworkAccessRestrictionsTemporaryOptOutDesc">When this policy is set to Enabled, Local Network Access requests will only display warnings in Chrome DevTools due to Local Network Access checks failing. When this policy is set to Disabled or unset, Local Network Access requests will use the default handling of these requests. See https://wicg.github.io/local-network-access/ for Local Network Access restrictions. This enterprise policy is temporary, and will be removed after M146. Long term, the policy LocalNetworkAccessAllowedForUrls can be used to allowlist URL patterns that should be automatically granted the Local Network Access permission. Note that if the policy LocalNetworkAccessRestrictionsEnabled is enabled, it will take precedence over this policy.</string>
    <string name="LocalNetworkAccessRestrictionsTemporaryOptOutTitle">Specifies whether to (temporarily) opt out of Local Network Access restrictions</string>
    <string name="LoginActivity_tip1">ArouseQQ</string>
    <string name="LoginActivity_tip2">Login Failed</string>
    <string name="LookalikeWarningAllowlistDomainsDesc">This policy prevents the display of lookalike URL warnings on the sites listed. These warnings are typically shown on sites that Google Chrome believes might be trying to spoof another site the user is familiar with. If the policy is enabled and set to one or more domains, no lookalike warnings pages will be shown when the user visits pages on that domain. If the policy is not set, or set to an empty list, warnings may appear on any site the user visits. A hostname can be allowed with a complete host match, or any domain match. For example, a URL like "https://foo.example.com/bar" may have warnings suppressed if this list includes either "foo.example.com" or "example.com".</string>
    <string name="LookalikeWarningAllowlistDomainsTitle">Suppress lookalike domain warnings on domains</string>
    <string name="Main_MenuCopyLinkUrl">Copy Link</string>
    <string name="Main_MenuOpenNewTab">Open in New Page</string>
    <string name="Main_MenuShareLinkUrl">Share Link</string>
    <string name="ManagedBookmarksDesc">Setting the policy sets up a list of bookmarks where each one is a dictionary with the keys "name" and "url". These keys hold the bookmark's name and target. Admins can set up a subfolder by defining a bookmark without a "url" key, but with an additional "children" key. This key also has a list of bookmarks, some of which can also be folders. Chrome amends incomplete URLs as if they were submitted through the address bar. For example, "google.com" becomes "https://google.com/". Users can't change the folders the bookmarks are placed in (though they can hide it from the bookmark bar). The default folder name for managed bookmarks is "Managed bookmarks" but it can be changed by adding a new sub-dictionary to the policy with a single key named "toplevel_name" with the desired folder name as its value. Managed bookmarks are not synced to the user account and extensions can't modify them.</string>
    <string name="ManagedBookmarksTitle">Managed Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="MetricsReportingEnabledDesc">When this policy is Enabled, anonymous reporting of usage and crash-related data about Google Chrome to Google is recommended to be enabled by default. Users will still be able to change this setting. When this policy is Disabled, anonymous reporting is disabled and no usage or crash data is sent to Google. Users won't be able to change this setting. When this policy is not set, users can choose the anonymous reporting behavior at installation or first run, and can change this setting later. On Microsoft® Windows®, this policy is only available on instances that are joined to a Microsoft® Active Directory® domain, joined to Microsoft® Azure® Active Directory® or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core. On macOS, this policy is only available on instances that are managed via MDM, joined to a domain via MCX or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core. (For Google ChromeOS, see DeviceMetricsReportingEnabled.)</string>
    <string name="MetricsReportingEnabledTitle">Enable reporting of usage and crash-related data</string>
    <string name="NTPContentSuggestionsEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to True or leaving it unset displays autogenerated content suggestions on the New Tab page, based on the user's browsing history, interests, or location. Setting the policy to False prevents autogenerated content suggestions from appearing on the New Tab page.</string>
    <string name="NTPContentSuggestionsEnabledTitle">Show content suggestions on the New Tab page</string>
    <string name="NetworkPredictionOptionsDesc">This policy controls network prediction in Google Chrome. It controls DNS prefetching, TCP, and SSL preconnection and prerendering of webpages. If you set the policy, users can't change it. Leaving it unset turns on network prediction, but the user can change it.</string>
    <string name="NetworkPredictionOptionsTitle">Enable network prediction</string>
    <string name="NoUndoMessage">Unable to control, confirm shutdown?</string>
    <string name="NotificationsAllowedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify the sites that can display notifications. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultNotificationsSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="NotificationsAllowedForUrlsTitle">Allow notifications on these sites</string>
    <string name="NotificationsBlockedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify the sites that can't display notifications. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultNotificationsSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="NotificationsBlockedForUrlsTitle">Block notifications on these sites</string>
    <string name="NtlmV2EnabledDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled or leaving it unset turns NTLMv2 on. Setting the policy to Disabled turns NTLMv2 off. All recent versions of Samba and Microsoft® Windows® servers support NTLMv2. This should only be turned off for backward compatibility as it reduces the security of authentication.</string>
    <string name="NtlmV2EnabledTitle">Enable NTLMv2 authentication.</string>
    <string name="Older">Past</string>
    <string name="OutOfProcessSystemDnsResolutionEnabledDesc">Setting this policy to true causes system DNS resolution (getaddrinfo()) to possibly run outside of the network process, depending on system configuration and feature flags. Setting this policy to false causes system DNS resolution (getaddrinfo()) to run in the network process rather than the browser process. This may force the network service sandbox to be disabled, degrading the security of Google Chrome. If this policy is not set, system DNS resolution may run in the network service, outside of the network service, or partially inside and partially outside, depending on system configuration and feature flags.</string>
    <string name="OutOfProcessSystemDnsResolutionEnabledTitle">Enable system DNS resolution outside of the network service</string>
    <string name="OverrideSecurityRestrictionsOnInsecureOriginDesc">Setting the policy specifies a list of origins (URLs) or hostname patterns (such as *.example.com) for which security restrictions on insecure origins won't apply. Patterns are only accepted for hostnames; URLs/origins with schemes must be exact strings. Organizations can specify origins for legacy applications that can't deploy TLS or set up a staging server for internal web development, so developers can test out features requiring secure contexts without having to deploy TLS on the staging server. This policy also prevents the origin from being labeled "Not Secure" in the address bar. Setting a list of URLs in this policy amounts to setting the command-line flag --unsafely-treat-insecure-origin-as-secure to a comma-separated list of the same URLs. The policy overrides the command-line flag and UnsafelyTreatInsecureOriginAsSecure, if present. For more information on secure contexts, see Secure Contexts ( https://www.w3.org/TR/secure-contexts ).</string>
    <string name="OverrideSecurityRestrictionsOnInsecureOriginTitle">Origins or hostname patterns for which restrictions on insecure origins should not apply</string>
    <string name="PUBLIC_PRIVACE">https://gw.yujianpay.com/privacy_main.html</string>
    <string name="PUBLIC_PRIVACE_RAIN">https://gw.yujianpay.com/privacy_main.html</string>
    <string name="PartitionedBlobUrlUsageDesc">This policy controls whether Blob URLs are partitioned during fetching and navigation. If this policy is set to Enabled or not set, Blob URLs will be partitioned. If this policy is set to Disabled, Blob URLs won't be partitioned. If storage partitioning is disabled for a given top-level origin by either ThirdPartyStoragePartitioningBlockedForOrigins or DefaultThirdPartyStoragePartitioningSetting, then Blob URLs will also not be partitioned. If you must use the policy, please file a bug at Google Chrome explaining your use case. The policy is scheduled to be offered through Google Chrome version 143, after which the old implementation will be removed. NOTE: Only newly-started renderer processes will reflect changes to this policy while the browser is running. For detailed information on third-party storage partitioning, please see https://developers.google.com/privacy-sandbox/cookies/storage-partitioning.</string>
    <string name="PartitionedBlobUrlUsageTitle">Choose whether Blob URLs are partitioned during fetching and navigations</string>
    <string name="PasswordLeakDetectionEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled lets users have Google Chrome check whether usernames and passwords entered were part of a leak. Setting the policy to Disabled does not let users have this functionality. If the policy is set, users can't change it in Google Chrome. If not set, credential leak checking is allowed, but the user can turn it off.</string>
    <string name="PasswordLeakDetectionEnabledTitle">Enable leak detection for entered credentials</string>
    <string name="PasswordManagerEnabledDesc">This policy controls the browser's ability to automatically remember passwords on websites and save them in the built-in password manager. It does not limit access or change the contents of passwords saved in the password manager and possibly synchronized to the Google account profile and Android. Setting the policy to Enabled means users have Google Chrome remember passwords and provide them the next time they sign in to a site. Setting the policy to Disabled means users can't save new passwords, but previously saved passwords will still work. If the policy is set, users can't change it in Google Chrome. If not set, the user can turn off password saving.</string>
    <string name="PasswordManagerEnabledTitle">Enable saving passwords to the password manager</string>
    <string name="PasswordSharingEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled lets users send to and receive from family members (according to Family Service) their passwords. When the policy is Enabled or not set, there is a button in the Password Manager allowing to send a password. The received passwords are stored into user's account and are available in the Password Manager. Setting the policy to Disabled means users can't send passwords from Password Manager to other users, and can't receive passwords from other users. The feature is not available if synchronization of Passwords is turned off (either via user settings or SyncDisabled policy is Enabled). Managed accounts aren't eligible to join or create a family group and therefore cannot share passwords.</string>
    <string name="PasswordSharingEnabledTitle">Enable sharing user credentials with other users</string>
    <string name="PaymentMethodQueryEnabledDesc">Allows you to set whether websites are allowed to check if the user has payment methods saved. If this policy is set to disabled, websites that use PaymentRequest.canMakePayment or PaymentRequest.hasEnrolledInstrument API will be informed that no payment methods are available. If the setting is enabled or not set then websites are allowed to check if the user has payment methods saved.</string>
    <string name="PaymentMethodQueryEnabledTitle">Allow websites to query for available payment methods.</string>
    <string name="Pdf_output_settings">Pdf output</string>
    <string name="PolicyAtomicGroupsEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled means policies coming from an atomic group that don't share the source with the highest priority from that group get ignored. Setting the policy to Disabled means no policy is ignored because of its source. Policies are ignored only if there's a conflict, and the policy doesn't have the highest priority. If this policy is set from a cloud source, it can't target a specific user.</string>
    <string name="PolicyAtomicGroupsEnabledTitle">Enables the concept of policy atomic groups</string>
    <string name="PolicyDictionaryMultipleSourceMergeListDesc">Setting the policy allows merging of selected policies when they come from different sources, with the same scopes and level. This merging is in the first level keys of the dictionary from each source. The key coming from the highest priority source takes precedence. Use the wildcard character '*' to allow merging of all supported dictionary policies. If a policy is in the list and there's conflict between sources with: * The same scopes and level: The values merge into a new policy dictionary. * Different scopes or level: The policy with the highest priority applies. If a policy isn't in the list and there's conflict between sources, scopes, or level, the policy with the highest priority applies.</string>
    <string name="PolicyDictionaryMultipleSourceMergeListTitle">Allow merging dictionary policies from different sources</string>
    <string name="PolicyListMultipleSourceMergeListDesc">Setting the policy allows merging of selected policies when they come from different sources, with the same scopes and level. Use the wildcard character '*' to allow merging of all list policies. If a policy is in the list and there's conflict between sources with: * The same scopes and level: The values merge into a new policy list. * Different scopes or level: The policy with the highest priority applies. If a policy isn't in the list and there's conflict between sources, scopes, or level, the policy with the highest priority applies.</string>
    <string name="PolicyListMultipleSourceMergeListTitle">Allow merging list policies from different sources</string>
    <string name="PopupsAllowedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify the sites that can open pop-ups. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultPopupsSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="PopupsAllowedForUrlsTitle">Allow pop-ups on these sites</string>
    <string name="PopupsBlockedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify the sites that can't open pop-ups. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultPopupsSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="PopupsBlockedForUrlsTitle">Block pop-ups on these sites</string>
    <string name="PostQuantumKeyAgreementEnabledDesc">This policy configures whether Google Chrome will offer a post-quantum key agreement algorithm in TLS, using the ML-KEM NIST standard. Prior to Google Chrome 131, the algorithm was Kyber, an earlier draft iteration of the standard. This allows supporting servers to protect user traffic from being later decrypted by quantum computers. If this policy is Enabled or not set, Google Chrome will offer a post-quantum key agreement in TLS connections. User traffic will then be protected from quantum computers when communicating with compatible servers. If this policy is Disabled, Google Chrome will not offer a post-quantum key agreement in TLS connections. User traffic will then be unprotected from quantum computers. Offering a post-quantum key agreement is backwards-compatible. Existing TLS servers and networking middleware are expected to ignore the new option and continue selecting previous options. However, devices that do not correctly implement TLS may malfunction when offered the new option. For example, they may disconnect in response to unrecognized options or the resulting larger messages. Such devices are not post-quantum-ready and will interfere with an enterprise's post-quantum transition. If encountered, administrators should contact the vendor for a fix. This policy is a temporary measure and will be removed sometime after Google Chrome version 145. It may be Enabled to allow you to test for issues, and may be Disabled while issues are being resolved.</string>
    <string name="PostQuantumKeyAgreementEnabledTitle">Enable post-quantum key agreement for TLS</string>
    <string name="PrefetchWithServiceWorkerEnabledDesc">SpeculationRules prefetch can be issued to URLs that are controlled by ServiceWorker. However, legacy code did not allow it and canceled the prefetch requests. This policy enables to control the behavior. Setting this policy to Enabled or not set allows SpeculationRules prefetch to ServiceWorker-controlled URLs (if the PrefetchServiceWorker feature flag is enabled). This is the current default behavior and is aligned with the specifications. Setting this policy to Disabled disallows SpeculationRules prefetch to ServiceWorker-controlled URLs. This is the legacy behavior. This policy is intended to be temporary and will be removed in the future.</string>
    <string name="PrefetchWithServiceWorkerEnabledTitle">Allow SpeculationRules prefetch to ServiceWorker-controlled URLs</string>
    <string name="PrintingEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled or leaving it unset lets users print in Google Chrome, and users can't change this setting. Setting the policy to Disabled means users can't print from Google Chrome. Printing is off in the three dots menu, extensions, and JavaScript applications.</string>
    <string name="PrintingEnabledTitle">Enable printing</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxAdMeasurementEnabledDesc">A policy to control whether the Privacy Sandbox Ad measurement setting can be disabled for your users. If you set this policy to Disabled, then the Ad measurement setting will be turned off for your users. If you set this policy to Enabled or keep it unset, your users will be able to turn on or off the Privacy Sandbox Ad measurement setting on their device. Setting this policy requires setting the PrivacySandboxPromptEnabled policy to Disabled.</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxAdMeasurementEnabledTitle">Choose whether the Privacy Sandbox ad measurement setting can be disabled</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxAdTopicsEnabledDesc">A policy to control whether the Privacy Sandbox Ad topics setting can be disabled for your users. If you set this policy to Disabled, then the Ad topics setting will be turned off for your users. If you set this policy to Enabled or keep it unset, your users will be able to turn on or off the Privacy Sandbox Ad topics setting on their device. Setting this policy requires setting the PrivacySandboxPromptEnabled policy to Disabled.</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxAdTopicsEnabledTitle">Choose whether the Privacy Sandbox Ad topics setting can be disabled</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxFingerprintingProtectionEnabledDesc">A policy to control whether the Privacy Sandbox Fingerprinting Protection setting is to be enabled in Incognito mode or disabled for your users. If you set this policy to Disabled, then the Fingerprinting Protection feature setting will be turned off for your users. If you set this policy to Enabled, your users will have the Fingerprinting Protection feature setting turned on in Incognito mode. If the policy is not set, users will be able to turn on or off the Fingerprinting Protection feature for Incognito mode in their UI settings. The default state will be false or disabled, meaning the Fingerprinting Protection feature will be turned off.</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxFingerprintingProtectionEnabledTitle">Choose whether the Privacy Sandbox Fingerprinting Protection feature is to be enabled in Incognito mode.</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxIpProtectionEnabledDesc">A policy to control whether the Privacy Sandbox IP Protection feature should be enabled. IP Protection is a feature that limits availability of a user's original IP address for certain third-party network requests made while browsing in Incognito mode, enhancing protections against cross-site tracking during Incognito browsing sessions. If the policy is set to Disabled, then IP Protection will be disabled and users won't be able to enable the feature via UI settings. If the policy is set to Enabled, then IP Protection will be enabled and users won't be able to disable the feature via UI settings. If the policy is not set, IP Protection will be enabled by default and users will be able to control the feature on their device via UI settings. Some considerations regarding whether enterprises should disable IP Protection include: - DNS lookups won't be performed for requests that are proxied, which may impact DNS-based monitoring or filtering. - Enterprise applications may experience breakage when used in Incognito mode if they rely on requests to domains (or subdomains of those domains) on the Masked Domain List (Google Chrome) and require those requests to come from specific IP address ranges. - Traffic might not be proxied in Incognito mode under certain conditions, for example when users launch Incognito mode from a Chrome profile they aren't signed in to. In general the feature requires the user to have been signed in to Chrome with a personal Google account when launching Incognito mode. - The list of domains on the Masked Domain List may change over time, with new versions being pushed to users automatically. For more information on the Masked Domain List, see: Google Chrome. For more information on IP Protection, see: Google Chrome. IP Protection will be launched no sooner than M139.</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxIpProtectionEnabledTitle">Choose whether the Privacy Sandbox IP Protection feature should be enabled.</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxPromptEnabledDesc">A policy to control whether your users see the Privacy Sandbox prompt. The prompt is a user-blocking flow which informs your users of the Privacy Sandbox settings. See https://privacysandbox.com for details about Chrome’s effort to deprecate third-party cookies. If you set this policy to Disabled, then Google Chrome won’t show the Privacy Sandbox prompt. If you set this policy to Enabled or keep it unset, then Google Chrome determines whether the Privacy Sandbox prompt can be shown or not and then show it if possible. If any of the following policies are set, it’s required to set this policy to Disabled: PrivacySandboxAdTopicsEnabled PrivacySandboxSiteEnabledAdsEnabled PrivacySandboxAdMeasurementEnabled</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxPromptEnabledTitle">Choose whether the Privacy Sandbox prompt can be shown to your users</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxSiteEnabledAdsEnabledDesc">A policy to control whether the Privacy Sandbox Site-suggested ads setting can be disabled for your users. If you set this policy to Disabled, then the Site-suggested ads setting will be turned off for your users. If you set this policy to Enabled or keep it unset, your users will be able to turn on or off the Privacy Sandbox Site-suggested ads setting on their device. Setting this policy requires setting the PrivacySandboxPromptEnabled policy to Disabled.</string>
    <string name="PrivacySandboxSiteEnabledAdsEnabledTitle">Choose whether the Privacy Sandbox Site-suggested ads setting can be disabled</string>
    <string name="PromptForDownloadLocationDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled means users are asked where to save each file before downloading. Setting the policy to Disabled has downloads start immediately, and users aren't asked where to save the file. Leaving the policy unset lets users change this setting.</string>
    <string name="PromptForDownloadLocationTitle">Ask where to save each file before downloading</string>
    <string name="ProtectedContentIdentifiersAllowedDesc">If the policy is set to true or unset, the use of protected content identifiers is allowed, which can help enable higher quality of protected content playback. If the policy is set to false, protected content identifiers are not allowed to be used.</string>
    <string name="ProtectedContentIdentifiersAllowedTitle">Allows web pages to use identifiers for the purpose of protected content playback</string>
    <string name="ProxySettingsDesc">Setting the policy configures the proxy settings for Chrome and ARC-apps, which ignore all proxy-related options specified from the command line. Leaving the policy unset lets users choose their proxy settings. Setting the ProxySettings policy accepts the following fields: * ProxyMode, which lets you specify the proxy server Chrome uses and prevents users from changing proxy settings * ProxyPacUrl, a URL to a proxy .pac file, or a PAC script encoded as a data URL with MIME type application/x-ns-proxy-autoconfig * ProxyPacMandatory, which prevents the network stack from falling back to direct connections with invalid or unavailable PAC script * ProxyServer, a URL of the proxy server * ProxyBypassList, a list of hosts for which the proxy will be bypassed The ProxyServerMode field is deprecated in favor of the ProxyMode field. For ProxyMode, if you choose the value: * direct, a proxy is never used and all other fields are ignored. * system, the systems's proxy is used and all other fields are ignored. * auto_detect, all other fields are ignored. * fixed_servers, the ProxyServer and ProxyBypassList fields are used. * pac_script, the ProxyPacUrl, ProxyPacMandatory and ProxyBypassList fields are used. Note: For more detailed examples, visit The Chromium Projects ( https://www.chromium.org/developers/design-documents/network-settings/#command-line-options-for-proxy-settings ).</string>
    <string name="ProxySettingsTitle">Proxy settings</string>
    <string name="QRCodeGeneratorEnabledDesc">This policy enables the QR Code generator feature in Google Chrome. If you enable this policy or don't configure it, the QR Code Generator feature is enabled. If you disable this policy, the QR Code Generator feature is disabled.</string>
    <string name="QRCodeGeneratorEnabledTitle">Enable QR Code Generator</string>
    <string name="ReduceAcceptLanguageEnabledDesc">The Accept-Language HTTP request header and the JavaScript navigator.languages getter are planned for reduction for privacy reasons. To facilitate testing and ensure compatibility, this policy allows you to enable or disable the Accept-Language Reduction feature. If this policy is set to enabled or left unset, Accept-Language Reduction will be applied through field trials. If this policy is set to disabled, field trials will not be able to activate Accept-Language Reduction. For more information about this feature, please visit: https://github.com/explainers-by-googlers/reduce-accept-language. NOTE: Only newly-started renderer processes will reflect changes to this policy while the browser is running.</string>
    <string name="ReduceAcceptLanguageEnabledTitle">Control Accept-Language Reduction</string>
    <string name="RelatedWebsiteSetsEnabledDesc">This policy allows to control the Related Website Sets feature enablement. This policy overrides the FirstPartySetsEnabled policy. When this policy is unset or set to True, the Related Website Sets feature is enabled. When this policy is set to False, the Related Website Sets feature is disabled.</string>
    <string name="RelatedWebsiteSetsEnabledTitle">Enable Related Website Sets</string>
    <string name="RelatedWebsiteSetsOverridesDesc">This policy provides a way to override the list of sets the browser uses for Related Website Sets features. This policy overrides the FirstPartySetsOverrides policy. Each set in the browser's list of Related Website Sets must meet the requirements of a Related Website Set. A Related Website Set must contain a primary site and one or more member sites. A set can also contain a list of service sites that it owns, as well as a map from a site to all of its ccTLD variants. See https://github.com/WICG/first-party-sets for more information on how Google Chrome uses Related Website Sets. All sites in a Related Website Set must be a registrable domain served over HTTPS. Each site in a Related Website Set must also be unique, meaning a site cannot be listed more than once in a Related Website Set. When this policy is given an empty dictionary, the browser uses the public list of Related Website Sets. For all sites in a Related Website Set from the replacements list, if a site is also present on a Related Website Set in the browser's list, then that site will be removed from the browser's Related Website Set. After this, the policy's Related Website Set will be added to the browser's list of Related Website Sets. For all sites in a Related Website Set from the additions list, if a site is also present on a Related Website Set in the browser's list, then the browser's Related Website Set will be updated so that the new Related Website Set can be added to the browser's list. After the browser's list has been updated, the policy's Related Website Set will be added to the browser's list of Related Website Sets. The browser's list of Related Website Sets requires that for all sites in its list, no site is in more than one set. This is also required for both the replacements list and the additions list. Similarly, a site cannot be in both the replacements list and the additions list. Wildcards (*) are not supported as a policy value, nor within any Related Website Set in these lists. All sets provided by the policy must be valid Related Website Sets, if they aren't then an appropriate error will be outputted. On Microsoft® Windows®, this policy is only available on instances that are joined to a Microsoft® Active Directory® domain, joined to Microsoft® Azure® Active Directory® or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core. On macOS, this policy is only available on instances that are managed via MDM, joined to a domain via MCX or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core.</string>
    <string name="RelatedWebsiteSetsOverridesTitle">Override Related Website Sets.</string>
    <string name="RestrictAccountsToPatternsDesc">Contains a list of patterns which are used to control the visibility of accounts in Google Chrome. Each Google account on the device will be compared to patterns stored in this policy to determine the account visibility in Google Chrome. The account will be visible if its name matches any pattern on the list. Otherwise, the account will be hidden. Use the wildcard character '*' to match zero or more arbitrary characters. The escape character is '\\', so to match actual '*' or '\\' characters, put a '\\' in front of them. If this policy is not set, all Google accounts on the device will be visible in Google Chrome.</string>
    <string name="RestrictAccountsToPatternsTitle">Restrict accounts that are visible in Google Chrome</string>
    <string name="SDCardErrorNoSDMsg">Cannot findSDCard</string>
    <string name="SDCardErrorSDUnavailable">SDCard not available</string>
    <string name="SSLErrorOverrideAllowedDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled or leaving it unset lets users click through warning pages Google Chrome shows when users navigate to sites that have SSL errors. Setting the policy to Disabled prevent users from clicking through any warning pages.</string>
    <string name="SSLErrorOverrideAllowedForOriginsDesc">If SSLErrorOverrideAllowed is Disabled, setting the policy lets you set a list of origin patterns that specify the sites where a user can click through warning pages Google Chrome shows when users navigate to sites that have SSL errors. Users will not be able to click through SSL warning pages on origins that are not on this list. If SSLErrorOverrideAllowed is Enabled or unset, this policy does nothing. Leaving the policy unset means SSLErrorOverrideAllowed applies for all sites. For detailed information on valid input patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. * is not an accepted value for this policy. This policy only matches based on origin, so any path in the URL pattern is ignored.</string>
    <string name="SSLErrorOverrideAllowedForOriginsTitle">Allow proceeding from the SSL warning page on specific origins</string>
    <string name="SSLErrorOverrideAllowedTitle">Allow proceeding from the SSL warning page</string>
    <string name="SafeBrowsingAllowlistDomainsDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled means Safe Browsing will trust the domains you designate. It won't check them for dangerous resources such as phishing, malware, or unwanted software. Safe Browsing's download protection service won't check downloads hosted on these domains. Its password protection service won't check for password reuse. Leaving the policy unset means default Safe Browsing protection applies to all resources. This policy does not support regular expressions; however, subdomains of a given domain are allowlisted. Fully qualified domain names (FQDNs) are not required. On Microsoft® Windows®, this policy is only available on instances that are joined to a Microsoft® Active Directory® domain, joined to Microsoft® Azure® Active Directory® or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core. On macOS, this policy is only available on instances that are managed via MDM, joined to a domain via MCX or enrolled in Chrome Enterprise Core.</string>
    <string name="SafeBrowsingAllowlistDomainsTitle">Configure the list of domains on which Safe Browsing will not trigger warnings.</string>
    <string name="SafeBrowsingExtendedReportingEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled turns on Google Chrome's Safe Browsing Extended Reporting, which sends some system information and page content to Google servers to help detect dangerous apps and sites. Setting the policy to Disabled means reports are never sent. If you set this policy, users can't change it. If not set, users can decide whether to send reports or not. See more about Safe Browsing ( https://developers.google.com/safe-browsing ).</string>
    <string name="SafeBrowsingExtendedReportingEnabledTitle">Enable Safe Browsing Extended Reporting</string>
    <string name="SafeBrowsingProtectionLevelDesc">Allows you to control whether Google Chrome's Safe Browsing feature is enabled and the mode it operates in. If this policy is set to 'NoProtection' (value 0), Safe Browsing is never active. If this policy is set to 'StandardProtection' (value 1, which is the default), Safe Browsing is always active in the standard mode. If this policy is set to 'EnhancedProtection' (value 2), Safe Browsing is always active in the enhanced mode, which provides better security, but requires sharing more browsing information with Google. If you set this policy as mandatory, users cannot change or override the Safe Browsing setting in Google Chrome. If this policy is left not set, Safe Browsing will operate in Standard Protection mode but users can change this setting. See https://support.google.com/chrome?p=safe_browsing_preferences for more info on Safe Browsing.</string>
    <string name="SafeBrowsingProtectionLevelTitle">Safe Browsing Protection Level</string>
    <string name="SafeBrowsingProxiedRealTimeChecksAllowedDesc">This controls whether Safe Browsing's standard protection mode is allowed to send partial hashes of URLs to Google through a proxy via Oblivious HTTP in order to determine whether they are safe to visit. The proxy allows browsers to upload partial hashes of URLs to Google without them being linked to the user's IP address. The policy also allows browsers to upload the partial hashes of URLs with higher frequency for better Safe Browsing protection quality. This policy will be ignored if Safe Browsing is disabled or set to enhanced protection mode. Setting the policy to Enabled or leaving it unset allows the higher-protection proxied lookups. Setting the policy to Disabled disallows the higher-protection proxied lookups. Partial hashes of URLs will be uploaded to Google directly with much lower frequency, which will degrade protection.</string>
    <string name="SafeBrowsingProxiedRealTimeChecksAllowedTitle">Allow Safe Browsing Proxied Real Time Checks</string>
    <string name="SafeSitesFilterBehaviorDesc">Setting the policy controls the SafeSites URL filter, which uses the Google Safe Search API to classify URLs as pornographic or not. When this policy is set to: * Do not filter sites for adult content, or not set, sites aren't filtered * Filter sites for adult content, pornographic sites are filtered The policy applies to both the URL the user navigates to and to iframes. The URLAllowlist policy takes precedence over this policy and can be used to override verdicts from the Google Safe Search API.</string>
    <string name="SafeSitesFilterBehaviorTitle">Control SafeSites adult content filtering.</string>
    <string name="SameOriginTabCaptureAllowedByOriginsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that can capture tabs with their same Origin. Leaving the policy unset means that sites will not be considered for an override at this level of capture. Note that windowed Chrome Apps with the same origin as this site will still be allowed to be captured. If a site matches a URL pattern in this policy, the following policies will not be considered: TabCaptureAllowedByOrigins, WindowCaptureAllowedByOrigins, ScreenCaptureAllowedByOrigins, ScreenCaptureAllowed. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. This policy only matches based on origin, so any path in the URL pattern is ignored.</string>
    <string name="SameOriginTabCaptureAllowedByOriginsTitle">Allow Same Origin Tab capture by these origins</string>
    <string name="SavingBrowserHistoryDisabledDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled means browsing history is not saved, tab syncing is off and users can't change this setting. Setting the policy to Disabled or leaving it unset saves browsing history.</string>
    <string name="SavingBrowserHistoryDisabledTitle">Disable saving browser history</string>
    <string name="ScreenCaptureAllowedByOriginsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that can use Desktop, Window, and Tab Capture. Leaving the policy unset means that sites will not be considered for an override at this level of Capture. This policy is not considered if a site matches a URL pattern in any of the following policies: WindowCaptureAllowedByOrigins, TabCaptureAllowedByOrigins, SameOriginTabCaptureAllowedByOrigins. If a site matches a URL pattern in this policy, the ScreenCaptureAllowed will not be considered. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. This policy only matches based on origin, so any path in the URL pattern is ignored.</string>
    <string name="ScreenCaptureAllowedByOriginsTitle">Allow Desktop, Window, and Tab capture by these origins</string>
    <string name="ScreenCaptureAllowedDesc">If enabled or not configured (default), a Web page can use screen-share APIs (e.g., getDisplayMedia() or the Desktop Capture extension API) to prompt the user to select a tab, window or desktop to capture. When this policy is disabled, any calls to screen-share APIs will fail with an error; however this policy is not considered (and a site will be allowed to use screen-share APIs) if the site matches an origin pattern in any of the following policies: ScreenCaptureAllowedByOrigins, WindowCaptureAllowedByOrigins, TabCaptureAllowedByOrigins, SameOriginTabCaptureAllowedByOrigins.</string>
    <string name="ScreenCaptureAllowedTitle">Allow or deny screen capture</string>
    <string name="ScrollToTextFragmentEnabledDesc">This feature allows for hyperlinks and address bar URL navigations to target specific text within a web page, which will be scrolled to once the loading of the web page is complete. If you enable or don't configure this policy, web page scrolling to specific text fragments via URL will be enabled. If you disable this policy, web page scrolling to specific text fragments via URL will be disabled.</string>
    <string name="ScrollToTextFragmentEnabledTitle">Enable scrolling to text specified in URL fragments</string>
    <string name="SearchActivity_tip1">Coupon:</string>
    <string name="SearchActivity_tip2">Movie：</string>
    <string name="SearchActivity_tip3">Resource：</string>
    <string name="SearchActivity_tip4">Translat：</string>
    <string name="SearchSuggestEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to True turns on search suggestions in Google Chrome's address bar. Setting the policy to False turns off these search suggestions. Suggestions based on bookmarks or history are unaffected by the policy. If you set the policy, users can't change it. If not set, search suggestions are on at first, but users can turn them off any time.</string>
    <string name="SearchSuggestEnabledTitle">Enable search suggestions</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip1">custom interface</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip14">sniff download</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip18">please enter the correct link</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip2">link failed!</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip3">no play resource</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip4">player failed to load, appear a playback exception! Try reinstalling app</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip5">comes from the link</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip6">cache load error, please search again!</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip7">to sniff resource</string>
    <string name="SeeVipActivity_tip8">please enter custom interface URL</string>
    <string name="SensorsAllowedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify the sites that can access sensors like motion and light sensors. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultSensorsSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. If the same URL pattern exists in both this policy and the SensorsBlockedForUrls policy, the latter is prioritized and access to motion or light sensors will be blocked. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="SensorsAllowedForUrlsTitle">Allow access to sensors on these sites</string>
    <string name="SensorsBlockedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that specify the sites that can't access sensors like motion and light sensors. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultSensorsSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. If the same URL pattern exists in both this policy and the SensorsAllowedForUrls policy, this policy is prioritized and access to motion or light sensors will be blocked. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. Wildcards, *, are allowed.</string>
    <string name="SensorsBlockedForUrlsTitle">Block access to sensors on these sites</string>
    <string name="SerialAllowAllPortsForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy allows you to list sites which are automatically granted permission to access all available serial ports. The URLs must be valid, otherwise the policy is ignored. Only the origin (scheme, host and port) of the URL is considered. On Google ChromeOS, this policy only applies to affiliated users. This policy overrides DefaultSerialGuardSetting, SerialAskForUrls, SerialBlockedForUrls and the user's preferences.</string>
    <string name="SerialAllowAllPortsForUrlsTitle">Automatically grant permission to sites to connect all serial ports.</string>
    <string name="SerialAskForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you list the URL patterns that specify which sites can ask users to grant them access to a serial port. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultSerialGuardSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, users' personal settings apply. For URL patterns which do not match the policy SerialBlockedForUrls (if there is a match), DefaultSerialGuardSetting (if set), or the users' personal settings take precedence, in that order. If URL patterns conflict with SerialBlockedForUrls they will be ignored. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. * is not an accepted value for this policy.</string>
    <string name="SerialAskForUrlsTitle">Allow the Serial API on these sites</string>
    <string name="SerialBlockedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you list the URL patterns that specify which sites can't ask users to grant them access to a serial port. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultSerialGuardSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. For URL patterns which do not match the policy SerialAskForUrls (if there is a match), DefaultSerialGuardSetting (if set), or the users' personal settings take precedence, in that order. If URL patterns conflict with SerialAskForUrls this policy will take precedence. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. * is not an accepted value for this policy.</string>
    <string name="SerialBlockedForUrlsTitle">Block the Serial API on these sites</string>
    <string name="ServiceWorkerAutoPreloadEnabledDesc">https://github.com/WICG/service-worker-auto-preload The ServiceWorkerAutoPreload feature dispatches a network request for a main resource at the same time it begins the ServiceWorker bootstrap process. Setting the policy to Enabled or leaving it unset means Google Chrome enables ServiceWorkerAutoPreload. The navigation request is automatically dispatched while starting the ServiceWorker in some scenarios, e.g. ServiceWorker is not running, If it is disabled, Google Chrome will not enable ServiceWorkerAutoPreload. The navigation request is dispatched always after starting the ServiceWorker. This policy is a temporary measure to control the feature and will be removed in M144.</string>
    <string name="ServiceWorkerAutoPreloadEnabledTitle">Allow ServiceWorker to dispatch navigation requests without waiting for its startup</string>
    <string name="ServiceWorkerToControlSrcdocIframeEnabledDesc">https://github.com/w3c/ServiceWorker/issues/765 asks srcdoc iframe with the "allow-same-origin" sandbox attribute to be under ServiceWorker control. Setting the policy to Enabled or leaving it unset means Google Chrome makes srcdoc iframes with "allow-same-origin" sandbox attributes to be under ServiceWorker control. Setting the policy to Disabled leaves the srcdoc iframe not controlled by ServiceWorker. This policy is intended to be temporary and will be removed in 2026.</string>
    <string name="ServiceWorkerToControlSrcdocIframeEnabledTitle">Allow ServiceWorker to control srcdoc iframes</string>
    <string name="SharedClipboardEnabledDesc">Enable the Shared Clipboard feature which allows users to send text between Chrome Desktops and an Android device when Sync is enabled and the user is Signed-in. If this policy is set to true, the capability of sending text, cross device, for chrome user is enabled. If this policy is set to false, the capability of sending text, cross device, for chrome user is disabled. If you set this policy, users cannot change or override it. If this policy is left unset, the shared clipboard feature is enabled by default. It is up to the admins to set policies in all platforms they care about. It's recommended to set this policy to one value in all platforms.</string>
    <string name="SharedClipboardEnabledTitle">Enable the Shared Clipboard Feature</string>
    <string name="SharedWorkerBlobURLFixEnabledDesc">Upon https://w3c.github.io/ServiceWorker/#control-and-use-worker-client, workers should inherit controllers for the blob URL. However, existing code allows only DedicatedWorkers to inherit the controller, and SharedWorkers do not inherit the controller. Setting the policy to Enabled or leaving it unset means Google Chrome inherit the controller if a blob URL is used as a SharedWorker URL. Setting the policy to Disabled leaves the behavior not aligned with the specification as-is. This policy is intended to be temporary and will be removed in the future.</string>
    <string name="SharedWorkerBlobURLFixEnabledTitle">Make SharedWorker blob URL behavior aligned with the specification</string>
    <string name="ShoppingListEnabledDesc">This policy controls the availability of the shopping list feature. If enabled, users will be presented with UI to track the price of the product displayed on the current page. The tracked product will be shown in the bookmarks side panel. If this policy is set to Enabled or not set, the shopping list feature will be available to users. If this policy is set to Disabled, the shopping list feature will be unavailable.</string>
    <string name="ShoppingListEnabledTitle">Allow the shopping list feature to be enabled</string>
    <string name="Shortcut">Function settings</string>
    <string name="SitePerProcessAndroidDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled isolates all sites on Android, such that each site runs in its own process, and it prevents users from opting out. A site is a scheme plus eTLD+1 (e.g., https://example.com). Note that Android isolates certain sensitive sites by default starting in Google Chrome version 77, and this policy extends that default site isolation mode to apply to all sites. Setting the policy to Disabled turns off any form of site isolation, including isolation of sensitive sites and field trials of IsolateOriginsAndroid, SitePerProcessAndroid, and other site isolation modes. Users can still turn the policy on manually. Leaving the policy unset means users can change this setting. IsolateOriginsAndroid might also be useful for isolating specific origins at a finer granularity than site (e.g., https://a.example.com). Note: Support for isolating every site on Android will improve, but currently it may cause performance problems, especially on low-end devices. This policy applies only to Chrome on Android running on devices with strictly more than 1 GB of RAM. To isolate specific sites while limiting performance impact for users, use IsolateOriginsAndroid with a list of the sites you want to isolate. To apply the policy on non-Android platforms, use SitePerProcess.</string>
    <string name="SitePerProcessAndroidTitle">Enable Site Isolation for every site</string>
    <string name="StandardizedBrowserZoomEnabledDesc">This policy enables conformance to the newly-adopted specification of CSS zoom. When this policy is Enabled or unset, the CSS "zoom" property will adhere to the specification: https://drafts.csswg.org/css-viewport/#zoom-property When Disabled, the CSS "zoom" property will fall back to its legacy pre-standardized behavior. This policy is a temporary reprieve to allow time to migrate web content to the new behavior. There is also an origin trial ("DisableStandardizedBrowserZoom") that corresponds to the behavior when this policy is Disabled. This policy will be removed and the "Enabled" behavior made permanent in milestone 134.</string>
    <string name="StandardizedBrowserZoomEnabledTitle">Enable Standardized Browser Zoom Behavior</string>
    <string name="StrictMimetypeCheckForWorkerScriptsEnabledDesc">This policy enables strict MIME type checking for worker scripts. When enabled or unset, then worker scripts will use strict MIME type checking for JavaScript, which is the new default behaviour. Worker scripts with legacy MIME types will be rejected. When disabled, then worker scripts will use lax MIME type checking, so that worker scripts with legacy MIME types, e.g. text/ascii, will continue to be loaded and executed. Browsers traditionally used lax MIME type checking, so that resources with a number of legacy MIME types were supported. E.g. for JavaScript resources, text/ascii is a legacy supported MIME type. This may cause security issues, by allowing to load resources as scripts that were never intended to be used as such. Chrome will transition to use strict MIME type checking in the near future. The enabled policy will track the default behaviour. Disabling this policy allows administrators to retain the legacy behaviour, if desired. See https://html.spec.whatwg.org/multipage/scripting.html#scriptingLanguage for details about JavaScript / ECMAScript media types.</string>
    <string name="StrictMimetypeCheckForWorkerScriptsEnabledTitle">Enable strict MIME type checking for worker scripts</string>
    <string name="SuppressDifferentOriginSubframeDialogsDesc">As described in https://www.chromestatus.com/feature/5148698084376576 , JavaScript modal dialogs, triggered by window.alert, window.confirm, and window.prompt, will be blocked in Google Chrome if triggered from a subframe whose origin is different from the main frame origin. This policy allows overriding that change. If the policy is set to enabled or unset, JavaScript dialogs triggered from a different origin subframe will be blocked. If the policy is set to disabled, JavaScript dialogs triggered from a different origin subframe will not be blocked. This policy will be removed from Google Chrome in the future.</string>
    <string name="SuppressDifferentOriginSubframeDialogsTitle">Suppress JavaScript Dialogs triggered from different origin subframes</string>
    <string name="SyncTypesListDisabledDesc">If this policy is set all specified data types will be excluded from synchronization both for Chrome Sync as well as for roaming profile synchronization. This can be beneficial to reduce the size of the roaming profile or limit the type of data uploaded to the Chrome Sync Servers. The current data types for this policy are: "apps", "autofill", "bookmarks", "extensions", "preferences", "passwords", "payments", "productComparison", "readingList", "savedTabGroups", "tabs", "themes", "typedUrls", "wifiConfigurations". Those names are case sensitive! Notes: Dynamic Policy Refresh is supported only in Google Chrome version 123 and later. Disabling "autofill" also disables "payments". "typedUrls" refers to all browsing history.</string>
    <string name="SyncTypesListDisabledTitle">List of types that should be excluded from synchronization</string>
    <string name="TLS13EarlyDataEnabledDesc">TLS 1.3 Early Data is an extension to TLS 1.3 to send an HTTP request simultaneously with the TLS handshake. If this policy is not configured, Google Chrome will follow the default rollout process for TLS 1.3 Early Data. If it is enabled, Google Chrome will enable TLS 1.3 Early Data. If it is disabled, Google Chrome will not enable TLS 1.3 Early Data. When the feature is enabled, Google Chrome may or may not use TLS 1.3 Early Data depending on server support. TLS 1.3 Early Data is an established protocol. Existing TLS servers, middleboxes, and security software are expected to either handle or reject TLS 1.3 Early Data without dropping the connection. However, devices that do not correctly implement TLS may malfunction and disconnect when TLS 1.3 Early Data is in use. If this occurs, administrators should contact the vendor for a fix. This policy is a temporary measure to control the feature and will be removed afterwards. The policy may be enabled to allow you to test for issues and disabled while issues are being resolved.</string>
    <string name="TLS13EarlyDataEnabledTitle">Enable TLS 1.3 Early Data</string>
    <string name="TabCaptureAllowedByOriginsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that can use Tab Capture. Leaving the policy unset means that sites will not be considered for an override at this level of capture. Note that windowed Chrome Apps will still be allowed to be captured. This policy is not considered if a site matches a URL pattern in the SameOriginTabCaptureAllowedByOrigins policy. If a site matches a URL pattern in this policy, the following policies will not be considered: WindowCaptureAllowedByOrigins, ScreenCaptureAllowedByOrigins, ScreenCaptureAllowed. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. This policy only matches based on origin, so any path in the URL pattern is ignored.</string>
    <string name="TabCaptureAllowedByOriginsTitle">Allow Tab capture by these origins</string>
    <string name="ThirdPartyPasswordManagersAllowedDesc">Setting the policy to true lets users use a third-party password manager. That password manager will handle saving and filling for all password, payment and autofill data. When the policy is true or not set, a setting will allow to switch between Google Chrome's buit-in password manager and the password manager configured in Android settings. Since Google Chrome uses the same data as Autofill with Google, the setting can only be changed to use third-party password managers if a manager other than Autofill with Google is configured in Android's system settings. Setting the policy to false means Google Chrome will always use the built-in password manager. This policy doesn't affect third-party password managers that use accessibility APIs.</string>
    <string name="ThirdPartyPasswordManagersAllowedTitle">Allow using Third-Party Password Managers in Google Chrome on Android</string>
    <string name="Today">Today</string>
    <string name="ToolbarFolder">ToolbarFolder</string>
    <string name="TosDialogBehaviorDesc">By default the Terms of Service are shown when CCT is first-run. Setting this policy to SkipTosDialog will cause the Terms of Service dialog to not appear during the first-run-experience or subsequent runs. Setting this policy to StandardTosDialog or leaving it unset will cause the Terms of Service dialog to appear during the first-run-experience. The other caveats are: - This policy only works on fully managed Android devices that can be configured by Unified Endpoint Management vendors. - If this policy is SkipTosDialog the BrowserSignin policy will have no effect. - If this policy is SkipTosDialog metrics​ will not be sent to the server. - If this policy is SkipTosDialog the browser will have limited functionality. - If this policy is SkipTosDialog admins must communicate this to end users of the device.</string>
    <string name="TosDialogBehaviorTitle">Configuring the ToS behavior during first-run for CCT</string>
    <string name="TranslateEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to True provides translation functionality when it's appropriate for users by showing an integrated translate toolbar in Google Chrome and a translate option on the right-click context menu. Setting the policy to False shuts off all built-in translate features. If you set the policy, users can't change this function. Leaving it unset lets them change the setting.</string>
    <string name="TranslateEnabledTitle">Enable Translate</string>
    <string name="Translate_aim">aim:</string>
    <string name="Translate_et_fy_name">Input</string>
    <string name="Translate_tip1">Chinese</string>
    <string name="Translate_tip2">English</string>
    <string name="Translate_tip3">Japanese</string>
    <string name="Translate_tip4">French</string>
    <string name="Translate_tip5">Copied results</string>
    <string name="Translate_tip6">You haven not checked yet?</string>
    <string name="Translate_tip9">delete this one</string>
    <string name="URLAllowlistDesc">Setting the policy provides access to the listed URLs, as exceptions to URLBlocklist. See that policy's description for the format of entries of this list. For example, setting URLBlocklist to * will block all requests, and you can use this policy to allow access to a limited list of URLs. Use it to open exceptions to certain schemes, subdomains of other domains, ports, or specific paths, using the format specified at ( https://support.google.com/chrome/a?p=url_blocklist_filter_format ). The most specific filter determines if a URL is blocked or allowed. The URLAllowlist policy takes precedence over URLBlocklist. This policy is limited to 1,000 entries. This policy also allows enabling the automatic invocation by the browser of external application registered as protocol handlers for the listed protocols like "tel:" or "ssh:". Leaving the policy unset allows no exceptions to URLBlocklist. From Google Chrome version 92, this policy is also supported in the headless mode.</string>
    <string name="URLAllowlistTitle">Allow access to a list of URLs</string>
    <string name="URLBlocklistDesc">Setting the URLBlocklist policy stops web pages with prohibited URLs from loading. Administrators can specify the list of URL patterns to be blocked. If left unset, no URLs are blocked in the browser. Up to 1,000 exceptions can be defined in URLAllowlist. See how to format a URL pattern ( https://support.google.com/chrome/a?p=url_blocklist_filter_format ). Note: This policy does not apply to in-page JavaScript URLs with dynamically loaded data. If you blocked example.com/abc, then example.com could still load it using XMLHTTPRequest. Additionally, this policy does not prevent web pages from updating the URL shown in the omnibox to a blocked one using the JavaScript History API. From Google Chrome version 73, you can block javascript://* URLs. But, this only affects JavaScript entered in the address bar or, for example, bookmarklets. From Google Chrome version 92, this policy is also supported in the headless mode. Note: Blocking internal chrome://* and chrome-untrusted://* URLs can lead to unexpected errors or can be circumvented in some cases. Instead of blocking certain internal URLs, see if there are more specific policies available. For example: - Instead of blocking chrome://settings/certificates, use CACertificateManagementAllowed. - Instead of blocking chrome-untrusted://crosh, use SystemFeaturesDisableList.</string>
    <string name="URLBlocklistTitle">Block access to a list of URLs</string>
    <string name="UrlKeyedAnonymizedDataCollectionEnabledDesc">Setting the policy to Enabled means URL-keyed anonymized data collection, which sends URLs of pages the user visits to Google to make searches and browsing better, is always active. Setting the policy to Disabled results in no URL-keyed anonymized data collection. If this policy is left unset, the user will be able to change this setting manually. In Google ChromeOS Kiosk, this policy doesn't offer the option to "Allow the user to decide". If this policy is unset for Google ChromeOS Kiosk, URL-keyed anonymized data collection is always active. When set for Google ChromeOS Kiosk, this policy enables URL-keyed metrics collection for kiosk apps.</string>
    <string name="UrlKeyedAnonymizedDataCollectionEnabledTitle">Enable URL-keyed anonymized data collection</string>
    <string name="VirtualKeyboardResizesLayoutByDefaultDesc">Setting the policy to True causes the virtual keyboard to resize the layout viewport by default. Other states (False/unset) have no effect. Note that this only affects the default resizing behavior: if a page requests a specific behavior using a &amp;lt;meta&amp;gt; tag or the Virtual Keyboard API, then that requested behavior will still apply. Note also that this is an "escape hatch" policy that's intended to be short-lived.</string>
    <string name="VirtualKeyboardResizesLayoutByDefaultTitle">The virtual keyboard resizes the layout viewport by default</string>
    <string name="WebAuthenticationRemoteDesktopAllowedOriginsDesc">A list of origins of remote desktop client apps that may execute WebAuthn API requests that originate from a browsing session on a remote host. Any origin configured in this policy can make WebAuthn requests for Relying Party IDs (RP IDs) that it would normally not allowed to be able to claim. Only valid HTTPS origins are allowed. Wildcards are not supported. Any invalid entries are ignored.</string>
    <string name="WebAuthenticationRemoteDesktopAllowedOriginsTitle">Allowed Origins for Proxied WebAuthn Requests from Remote Desktop Applications.</string>
    <string name="WebRtcUdpPortRangeDesc">If the policy is set, the UDP port range used by WebRTC is restricted to the specified port interval (endpoints included). If the policy is not set, or if it is set to the empty string or an invalid port range, WebRTC is allowed to use any available local UDP port.</string>
    <string name="WebRtcUdpPortRangeTitle">Restrict the range of local UDP ports used by WebRTC</string>
    <string name="WebUsbAllowDevicesForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you list the URL patterns that specify which sites are automatically granted permission to access a USB device with the given vendor and product IDs. Each item in the list requires both devices and urls fields for the policy to be valid. Each item in the devices field can have a vendor_id and product_id field. Omitting the vendor_id field will create a policy matching any device. Omitting the product_id field will create a policy matching any device with the given vendor ID. A policy which has a product_id field without a vendor_id field is invalid. The USB permission model will grant the specified URL permission to access the USB device as a top-level origin. If embedded frames need to access USB devices, the 'usb' feature-policy header should be used to grant access. The URL must be valid, otherwise the policy is ignored. Deprecated: The USB permission model used to support specifying both the requesting and embedding URLs. This is deprecated and only supported for backwards compatibility in this manner: if both a requesting and embedding URL is specified, then the embedding URL will be granted the permission as top-level origin and the requesting URL will be ignored entirely. This policy overrides DefaultWebUsbGuardSetting, WebUsbAskForUrls, WebUsbBlockedForUrls and the user's preferences. This policy only affects access to USB devices through the WebUSB API. To grant access to USB devices through the Web Serial API see the SerialAllowUsbDevicesForUrls policy.</string>
    <string name="WebUsbAllowDevicesForUrlsTitle">Automatically grant permission to these sites to connect to USB devices with the given vendor and product IDs.</string>
    <string name="WebUsbAskForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you list the URL patterns that specify which sites can ask users to grant them access to a USB device. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultWebUsbGuardSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, users' personal settings apply. URL patterns must not conflict with WebUsbAskForUrls. Neither policy takes precedence if a URL matches with both. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. * is not an accepted value for this policy.</string>
    <string name="WebUsbAskForUrlsTitle">Allow WebUSB on these sites</string>
    <string name="WebUsbBlockedForUrlsDesc">Setting the policy lets you list the URL patterns that specify which sites can't ask users to grant them access to a USB device. Leaving the policy unset means DefaultWebUsbGuardSetting applies for all sites, if it's set. If not, the user's personal setting applies. URL patterns can't conflict with WebUsbAskForUrls. Neither policy takes precedence if a URL matches with both. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. * is not an accepted value for this policy.</string>
    <string name="WebUsbBlockedForUrlsTitle">Block WebUSB on these sites</string>
    <string name="WebXRImmersiveArEnabledDesc">Configures whether the sites that the user navigates to are allowed to create immersive Augmented Reality sessions using WebXR Device API. When this policy is unset or enabled, the WebXR Device API will accept "immersive-ar" during session creation, thus allowing the users to enter Augmented Reality experiences. When this policy is disabled, the WebXR Device API will reject requests to create sessions with mode set to "immersive-ar". The existing "immersive-ar" sessions (if any) will not be terminated. For more details about "immersive-ar" sessions, please see WebXR Augmented Reality Module specification.</string>
    <string name="WebXRImmersiveArEnabledTitle">Allow creating WebXR's "immersive-ar" sessions</string>
    <string name="WindowCaptureAllowedByOriginsDesc">Setting the policy lets you set a list of URL patterns that can use Window and Tab Capture. Leaving the policy unset means that sites will not be considered for an override at this level of Capture. This policy is not considered if a site matches a URL pattern in any of the following policies: TabCaptureAllowedByOrigins, SameOriginTabCaptureAllowedByOrigins. If a site matches a URL pattern in this policy, the following policies will not be considered: ScreenCaptureAllowedByOrigins, ScreenCaptureAllowed. For detailed information on valid url patterns, please see https://cloud.google.com/docs/chrome-enterprise/policies/url-patterns. This policy only matches based on origin, so any path in the URL pattern is ignored.</string>
    <string name="WindowCaptureAllowedByOriginsTitle">Allow Window and Tab capture by these origins</string>
    <string name="Yesterday">Yesterday</string>
    <string name="YunBookmarksListActivity_tip1">Error</string>
    <string name="YunBookmarksListActivity_tip3">You must log in first</string>
    <string name="_1_n2_n3_625197595_qq_com_chrome_n">You are about to enter the movie viewing mode. In order to provide better services and avoid some disputes, whether as an enterprise or an individual, you need to read the following usage agreement. 1. The video viewing mode is designed to give users a better experience in web video playback. The content comes from the web page you currently open without any processing.
2. The video viewing mode is a data stream pushed by the kernel, which only pushes unencrypted and technically public video information.
3. The purpose of the video viewing mode is to provide users with a better use experience. He will not exit or freeze the current web page, nor skip advertisements, If you feel that this function infringes your rights and interests, please contact us immediately by email 625197595@qq.com Yes, we have a perfect white list system to solve this problem. At the same time, it is also recommended that you encrypt your video, because being able to enter the viewing mode means that you can easily access your video in regular browsers such as chrome. N we have added a white list to well-known websites, but we can not exhaustive all the websites. I hope you can understand that this function is in the public interest. However, we fully respect the choice of each webmaster, and communication can quickly solve problems. I agree to abide by the agreement on behalf of you, and in case of disputes, we will give priority to contact you according to the agreement. Clicking reject will close this function.</string>
    <string name="__arcore_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="__arcore_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="__arcore_install_app">This application requires the latest version of Google Play Services for AR.</string>
    <string name="__arcore_install_feature">This feature requires the latest version of Google Play Services for AR.</string>
    <string name="__arcore_installing">Installing Google Play Services for AR…</string>
    <string name="a_files">files</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_home_description">Navigate home</string>
    <string name="abc_action_bar_up_description">Navigate up</string>
    <string name="abc_action_menu_overflow_description">More options</string>
    <string name="abc_action_mode_done">Done</string>
    <string name="abc_activity_chooser_view_see_all">See all</string>
    <string name="abc_activitychooserview_choose_application">Choose an app</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_off">OFF</string>
    <string name="abc_capital_on">ON</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_alt_shortcut_label">Alt+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_ctrl_shortcut_label">Ctrl+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_delete_shortcut_label">delete</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_enter_shortcut_label">enter</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_function_shortcut_label">Function+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_meta_shortcut_label">Meta+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_shift_shortcut_label">Shift+</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_space_shortcut_label">space</string>
    <string name="abc_menu_sym_shortcut_label">Sym+</string>
    <string name="abc_prepend_shortcut_label">Menu+</string>
    <string name="abc_search_hint">Search…</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_clear">Clear query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_query">Search query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_search">Search</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_submit">Submit query</string>
    <string name="abc_searchview_description_voice">Voice search</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with">Share with</string>
    <string name="abc_shareactionprovider_share_with_application">Share with %s</string>
    <string name="abc_toolbar_collapse_description">Collapse</string>
    <string name="about">"Related</string>
    <string name="about_ad">About ADBlocker</string>
    <string name="about_his">Relevant history</string>
    <string name="about_history_intro">History related to current webpage</string>
    <string name="about_us">With regard to</string>
    <string name="academic">Academic</string>
    <string name="access_loss_update_gms_title">Update Google Play services</string>
    <string name="accessibility_account_management_row_account_error">Google Account error</string>
    <string name="accessibility_archived_tabs_dialog">Inactive tabs dialog</string>
    <string name="accessibility_archived_tabs_dialog_back_button">Hide inactive tabs dialog</string>
    <string name="accessibility_bottom_tab_grid_close_tab_sheet">Hide fullscreen grid</string>
    <string name="accessibility_bottom_tab_strip_expand_tab_sheet">Show group's tabs in fullscreen grid</string>
    <string name="accessibility_btn_extensions">Extensions</string>
    <string name="accessibility_btn_lens_camera">Search with your camera using Google Lens</string>
    <string name="accessibility_btn_refresh">Reload this page</string>
    <string name="accessibility_btn_stop_loading">Stop page loading</string>
    <string name="accessibility_cancel_selection">Cancel selection</string>
    <string name="accessibility_captions_title">Captions</string>
    <string name="accessibility_collapse_section_header">Tap to collapse</string>
    <string name="accessibility_collapsed">Collapsed</string>
    <string name="accessibility_collapsed_group">Collapsed - click to expand.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_content_view">Web View</string>
    <string name="accessibility_cross_device_tabs">Tabs from other devices</string>
    <string name="accessibility_custom_tab_collapsed">Tab is back to initial height</string>
    <string name="accessibility_custom_tab_drag_handle">Drag handle</string>
    <string name="accessibility_custom_tab_expanded">Tab is expanded</string>
    <string name="accessibility_custom_tab_menu_item_highlight">%1$s menu is highlighted.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_custom_tab_menu_with_dot">Customize and control Google Chrome with a highlighted item</string>
    <string name="accessibility_date_picker_month">Month</string>
    <string name="accessibility_date_picker_week">Week</string>
    <string name="accessibility_date_picker_year">Year</string>
    <string name="accessibility_datetime_picker_date">Date</string>
    <string name="accessibility_datetime_picker_time">Time</string>
    <string name="accessibility_default_app_label">Application</string>
    <string name="accessibility_exit_full_screen">Exit full screen</string>
    <string name="accessibility_expand_button">Expand</string>
    <string name="accessibility_expand_section_header">Tap to expand</string>
    <string name="accessibility_expanded">Expanded</string>
    <string name="accessibility_expanded_group">Expanded - click to collapse.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_feed_swipe_refresh_iph">To refresh the feed content, pull down the page</string>
    <string name="accessibility_find_toolbar_btn_next">Next</string>
    <string name="accessibility_find_toolbar_btn_prev">Previous</string>
    <string name="accessibility_follow_accelerator_iph">Adds the current web site to the list of web sites that you are following.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_full_screen">Full screen</string>
    <string name="accessibility_google_doodle">Google doodle: %1$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_hang_up">Hang up</string>
    <string name="accessibility_incognito_badge">Incognito mode</string>
    <string name="accessibility_incognito_tab">Incognito Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_list_menu_button">%1$s Options</string>
    <string name="accessibility_list_remove_button">%1$s Remove</string>
    <string name="accessibility_menu_bookmark">Bookmark this page</string>
    <string name="accessibility_menu_forward">Go forward</string>
    <string name="accessibility_menu_info">View site information</string>
    <string name="accessibility_menu_share_via">Share via %s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_merchant_viewer_message_announcement">View store info, option available near top of the screen</string>
    <string name="accessibility_mute_microphone">Mute microphone</string>
    <string name="accessibility_mute_video">Mute video</string>
    <string name="accessibility_new_incognito_tab_page">New Incognito tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_next_slide">Next slide</string>
    <string name="accessibility_next_track">Next track</string>
    <string name="accessibility_ntp_feed_menu_button">Options for Discover</string>
    <string name="accessibility_ntp_feed_menu_iph">Control your stories from the Options for Discover button</string>
    <string name="accessibility_ntp_following_unread_content">Unread stories ready</string>
    <string name="accessibility_ntp_offline_badge">Available offline</string>
    <string name="accessibility_ntp_pinned_shortcut_badge">Pinned shortcut</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_btn_copy_srp">Copy link to search results page for: %1$s. Source: %2$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_btn_copy_url">Copy link to webpage %1$s. Source: %2$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_btn_edit_query">Edit search query: %1$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_btn_edit_url">Edit URL pointing to page on: %1$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_btn_refine">Refine: %1$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_btn_share_srp">Share link to search results page for: %1$s. Source: %2$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_btn_share_url">Share link to webpage %1$s. Source: %2$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_conceal_button_announcement">Clipboard contents hidden</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_conceal_clipboard_contents">Hide clipboard contents</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_most_visited_list">Most visited sites</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_most_visited_tile_add_new_shortcut">Add new shortcut.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_most_visited_tile_navigate">%1$s: %2$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_most_visited_tile_search">Search: %s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_reveal_button_announcement">Clipboard contents shown</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_reveal_clipboard_contents">Show clipboard contents</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_showing_suggestions_for_website">Showing suggestions for %1$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_suggested_items">%d suggested items in list below.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_omnibox_switch_to_tab">Switch To Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_open_shared_tab_group_overflow_menu_with_group_name_with_color">Open the tab group action menu for shared tab group %1$s, color %2$s.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_open_tab_group_overflow_menu_with_group_name_with_color">Open the tab group action menu for tab group %1$s, color %2$s.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_partial_custom_tab_bottom_sheet">Bottom sheet</string>
    <string name="accessibility_partial_custom_tab_full_sheet">Full-size sheet</string>
    <string name="accessibility_partial_custom_tab_side_sheet">Side sheet</string>
    <string name="accessibility_pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="accessibility_pause_video">Pause video</string>
    <string name="accessibility_play">Play</string>
    <string name="accessibility_play_video">Play video</string>
    <string name="accessibility_playback_time">Elapsed time %1$s of %2$s.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_previous_slide">Previous slide</string>
    <string name="accessibility_previous_track">Previous track</string>
    <string name="accessibility_quick_action_search_widget_start_dino_game">Start Dino Game</string>
    <string name="accessibility_replay">Play from the beginning</string>
    <string name="accessibility_restore_tab">Restore and open %1$s tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_search_loupe_tooltip_text">Open tab search</string>
    <string name="accessibility_security_btn_dangerous">This page is dangerous</string>
    <string name="accessibility_security_btn_secure">Connection is secure</string>
    <string name="accessibility_security_btn_warn">Your connection to this site is not secure</string>
    <string name="accessibility_seek_backward">Seek backward</string>
    <string name="accessibility_seek_forward">Seek forward</string>
    <string name="accessibility_single_tab_module_see_more">See more recent tabs</string>
    <string name="accessibility_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="accessibility_swipe_refresh">Refreshing page</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_grid_dialog">Tab group expanded</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_group_color_icon_description">%1$s tab group color icon</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_group_color_picker_color_item_not_selected_description">%1$s Not selected</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_group_color_picker_color_item_selected_description">%1$s Selected</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_group_removed_dismiss_button">Dismiss the card.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_group_suggestion_description">Open %1$s tab group, color %2$s, with sites %3$s.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_groups">Tab groups</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_movement_down">Move tab down</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_movement_left">Move tab left</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_movement_right">Move tab right</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_movement_up">Move tab up</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_price_card">The price of this item recently dropped from %1$s to %2$s</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_selection_editor">Multi-select mode</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_selection_editor_back_button">Hide multi-select mode</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_suggestion_close_stale_message">Suggestion: %1$s of your tabs haven't been used lately. Close them?</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_suggestion_dismiss_button">Dismiss the suggestions.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_suggestion_group_tabs_message">Suggestion: %1$s tabs seem related. Group them?</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_suggestion_review_button">Review the suggestions.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_switcher">Tab Switcher</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_switcher_incognito_stack">Incognito tabs</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_switcher_title">All tabs</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tab_switcher_toolbar_btn_menu">Manage open tabs</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_btn_close_tab">Close %1$s tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_btn_incognito_toggle_incognito">Leave Incognito mode</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_btn_incognito_toggle_standard">Enter Incognito mode</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_group">%1$s tab group</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_group_multiple_tabs">%1$s and %2$d other tabs</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_shared_group">Shared %1$s tab group</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_shared_group_with_new_activity">Shared %1$s tab group with new activity</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab">%1$s, Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab_incognito">%1$s, Incognito Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab_notification">%1$s, New or Updated Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab_pinned">%1$s, Pinned Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab_pinned_incognito">%1$s, Pinned Incognito Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab_pinned_selected">%1$s, Pinned Selected Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab_pinned_selected_incognito">%1$s, Pinned Selected Incognito Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab_selected">%1$s, Selected Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_tabstrip_tab_selected_incognito">%1$s, Selected Incognito Tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_time_picker_ampm">AM/PM</string>
    <string name="accessibility_time_picker_hour">Hour</string>
    <string name="accessibility_time_picker_milli">Millisecond</string>
    <string name="accessibility_time_picker_minute">Minute</string>
    <string name="accessibility_time_picker_second">Second</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_back">Go back</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_composeplate">Start search</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_delete_url">Clear input</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_forward">Go forward</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_home">Open the home page</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_identity_disc">Manage account</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_identity_disc_error_with_name">Signed in as %s. Google Account error. Opens settings.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_identity_disc_error_with_name_and_email">Signed in as %1$s. %2$s. Google Account error. Opens settings.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_identity_disc_with_name">Signed in as %s. Opens settings.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_identity_disc_with_name_and_email">Signed in as %1$s. %2$s. Opens settings.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_menu">Customize and control Google Chrome</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_menu_os_version_unsupported">Chrome can’t update. More options</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_menu_update">Update available. More options</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_mic">Start voice search</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_new_incognito_tab">New Incognito tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_new_tab">New tab</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_signed_out_identity_disc">Signed out. Opens options to sign in.</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_btn_site_info">Site information</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_exit_hub_search">Exit hub search</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_exit_select">Exited selection mode</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_multi_select">%1$s selected</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_screen_position">%1$s selected.  Options available near top of the screen</string>
    <string name="accessibility_toolbar_view_site_info">View site information</string>
    <string name="accessibility_turn_off_camera">Turn off camera</string>
    <string name="accessibility_turn_on_camera">Turn on camera</string>
    <string name="accessibility_unmute_microphone">Unmute microphone</string>
    <string name="accessibility_unmute_video">Unmute video</string>
    <string name="accessibility_video_player">Video player</string>
    <string name="accessible_find_in_page_count">Result %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="accessible_find_in_page_no_results">No results</string>
    <string name="account_0">International Version Account</string>
    <string name="account_1">Chinese Version Account</string>
    <string name="account_3">Server Partition Selection Explanation Document</string>
    <string name="account_advanced_header">Control your data &amp; account</string>
    <string name="account_android_device_accounts">Manage accounts on this device</string>
    <string name="account_bookmark_save_flow_subtitle_local">On this device</string>
    <string name="account_bookmark_save_flow_title">Saved in %1$s</string>
    <string name="account_bookmarks_section_header">In your Google Account</string>
    <string name="account_data_dashboard_subtitle">Review your account data</string>
    <string name="account_data_dashboard_title">Chrome data in your account</string>
    <string name="account_management_header_no_parental_data">If you need help, ask your parent</string>
    <string name="account_management_header_one_parent_name">If you need help, ask your parent (%1$s)</string>
    <string name="account_management_header_two_parent_names">If you need help, ask your parent (%1$s or %2$s)</string>
    <string name="account_management_sign_out">Sign out of Chrome</string>
    <string name="account_management_title">Signed in to Google as</string>
    <string name="account_picker_bottom_sheet_accessibility_closed">Sign in to Chrome, closed.</string>
    <string name="account_picker_bottom_sheet_accessibility_opened">Sign in to Chrome, opened.</string>
    <string name="account_pw">Account Password</string>
    <string name="account_section_addresses_toggle">Addresses and more</string>
    <string name="account_section_bookmarks_toggle">Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="account_section_extensions_toggle">Extensions</string>
    <string name="account_section_footer">When on, use and save data in your Google Account. When off, data is saved only to this device.</string>
    <string name="account_section_header">In your Google Account</string>
    <string name="account_section_history_toggle">History and tabs</string>
    <string name="account_section_passwords_toggle">Passwords</string>
    <string name="account_section_payments_and_info_toggle">Payment methods and other info from Google Wallet</string>
    <string name="account_section_payments_toggle">Payment methods, offers, and addresses using Google Pay</string>
    <string name="account_section_reading_list_toggle">Reading list</string>
    <string name="account_section_settings_toggle">Settings</string>
    <string name="account_selection_add_account">Use a different account</string>
    <string name="account_selection_add_account_opens_in_new_tab">%1$s, opens in a new tab</string>
    <string name="account_selection_add_account_with_origin">Use your %1$s account</string>
    <string name="account_selection_button_mode_sheet_choose_an_account">Choose an account to continue on %1$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_button_mode_sheet_title_explicit_continue">Continue with %1$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_button_mode_sheet_title_explicit_signin">Sign in with %1$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_button_mode_sheet_title_explicit_signup">Sign up with %1$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_button_mode_sheet_title_explicit_use">Use with %1$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_content_description">Sign in bottom sheet</string>
    <string name="account_selection_continue">Continue as %1$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_data_sharing_consent">To continue, %1$s will share your %2$s with this site. See this site's &lt;link_privacy_policy&gt;privacy policy&lt;/link_privacy_policy&gt; and &lt;link_terms_of_service&gt;terms of service&lt;/link_terms_of_service&gt;.</string>
    <string name="account_selection_data_sharing_consent_no_pp">To continue, %1$s will share your %2$s with this site. See this site's &lt;link_terms_of_service&gt;terms of service&lt;/link_terms_of_service&gt;.</string>
    <string name="account_selection_data_sharing_consent_no_pp_or_tos">To continue, %1$s will share your %2$s with this site.</string>
    <string name="account_selection_data_sharing_consent_no_tos">To continue, %1$s will share your %2$s with this site. See this site's &lt;link_privacy_policy&gt;privacy policy&lt;/link_privacy_policy&gt;.</string>
    <string name="account_selection_data_sharing_email">email address</string>
    <string name="account_selection_data_sharing_name">name</string>
    <string name="account_selection_data_sharing_phone">phone number</string>
    <string name="account_selection_data_sharing_picture">profile picture</string>
    <string name="account_selection_data_sharing_username">username</string>
    <string name="account_selection_multi_idp_sheet_title_explicit_signin">Sign in to %1$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_returning_account_message">%1$s • You used on this site</string>
    <string name="account_selection_sheet_closed">Sign in bottom sheet is closed</string>
    <string name="account_selection_sheet_full_height">Sign in bottom sheet opened at full height</string>
    <string name="account_selection_sheet_half_height">Sign in bottom sheet opened at half height</string>
    <string name="account_selection_sheet_subtitle_for_embed">%1$s embeds content from %2$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_sheet_title_explicit_continue">Continue to %1$s with %2$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_sheet_title_explicit_signin">Sign in to %1$s with %2$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_sheet_title_explicit_signup">Sign up to %1$s with %2$s</string>
    <string name="account_selection_sheet_title_explicit_use">Use %1$s with %2$s</string>
    <string name="account_settings_promo_description_bookmarks">To get your bookmarks on all your devices, turn on “Bookmarks” in settings</string>
    <string name="account_settings_sign_out_snackbar_message_sync_disabled">Signed out</string>
    <string name="account_settings_title">Account</string>
    <string name="ack_grouped_cred_sheet_closed">Password suggestion is closed.</string>
    <string name="ack_grouped_cred_sheet_desc">&lt;b1&gt;%1$s&lt;/b1&gt; and &lt;b2&gt;%2$s&lt;/b2&gt; seem to be related. Make sure you trust &lt;b3&gt;%2$s&lt;/b3&gt; before using your password.</string>
    <string name="ack_grouped_cred_sheet_opened">Password suggestion confirmation</string>
    <string name="ack_grouped_cred_sheet_title">Use your %1$s password?</string>
    <string name="action">Action</string>
    <string name="action_edit">Edit file</string>
    <string name="action_search">Search file</string>
    <string name="actionbar_share">Share</string>
    <string name="actionbar_textselection_title">Text selection</string>
    <string name="actionbar_web_search">Web search</string>
    <string name="active_time_c">Expiration Stop Active</string>
    <string name="activity_book_shelf_text_0">You have no reading record. Please go to the novel website and start reading mode first</string>
    <string name="activity_capture_text_0">scan</string>
    <string name="activity_drag_gridview_layout_text_0">Please enter a title</string>
    <string name="activity_drag_gridview_layout_text_1">Upload Icon</string>
    <string name="activity_drag_gridview_layout_text_2">Custom Icon</string>
    <string name="activity_drag_gridview_layout_text_3">More beautification</string>
    <string name="activity_drag_gridview_layout_text_4">Light application recommended Click to install</string>
    <string name="activity_drag_gridview_layout_text_5">Cloud services</string>
    <string name="activity_drag_gridview_layout_text_6">Synchronized at 19:00, November 12, 2021</string>
    <string name="activity_drag_gridview_layout_text_7">Light applications do not support defining icons</string>
    <string name="activity_drag_gridview_layout_text_8">Complete</string>
    <string name="activity_guide_text_0">skip</string>
    <string name="activity_hwtxtpaly_text_0">Chapter I</string>
    <string name="activity_hwtxtpaly_text_1">Select 0 words</string>
    <string name="activity_hwtxtpaly_text_2">copy</string>
    <string name="activity_light_resour_main_text_0">Search for video / pictures / music and other resources</string>
    <string name="activity_login_text_0">right:</string>
    <string name="activity_login_text_1">four thousand and eight hundred</string>
    <string name="activity_power_text_0">There is currently no content</string>
    <string name="activity_read_fullscreen_text_0">Original web page</string>
    <string name="activity_read_fullscreen_text_1">search</string>
    <string name="activity_read_fullscreen_text_2">poster</string>
    <string name="activity_supportjsactivity_text_0">Custom script</string>
    <string name="activity_supportjsactivity_text_1">Leaving a message.</string>
    <string name="activity_test_text_0">go</string>
    <string name="ad_bottom">we put the advertisement at the end, hoping to bring you a good playing experience and let the author have dinner. If I can get your support, I will be very grateful. Click to close the advertisement</string>
    <string name="ad_error_tosu">please be sure to enter your website address. If you leave an email, we will reply to you after processing</string>
    <string name="ad_filter">Ad Filter</string>
    <string name="ad_please_go_web">Please enter the page first</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_link_row_label">Ad privacy</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_link_row_sub_label">Customize the info used by sites to show you ads</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_ad_measurement_link_row_label">Ad measurement</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_ad_measurement_link_row_sub_label_disabled">Sites and advertisers can understand how ads perform. This setting is off.</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_ad_measurement_link_row_sub_label_enabled">Sites and advertisers can understand how ads perform. This setting is on.</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_fledge_link_row_label">Site-suggested ads</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_fledge_link_row_sub_label_disabled">Based on your activity on a site. This setting is off.</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_fledge_link_row_sub_label_enabled">Based on your activity on a site. This setting is on.</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_title">Ad privacy</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_topics_link_row_label">Ad topics</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_topics_link_row_sub_label_disabled">Based on your browsing history. This setting is off.</string>
    <string name="ad_privacy_page_topics_link_row_sub_label_enabled">Based on your browsing history. This setting is on.</string>
    <string name="ad_s_0">Logs</string>
    <string name="ad_s_1">Rule subscription</string>
    <string name="ad_s_2">Custom rules</string>
    <string name="ad_s_3">White list</string>
    <string name="ad_s_4">Turn on AdBlocker</string>
    <string name="ad_settle">admanage</string>
    <string name="ad_tip_1">About advertising interception</string>
    <string name="ad_tip_2">Intercept log</string>
    <string name="ad_tip_3">Rule file</string>
    <string name="ad_tip_4">Custom rules</string>
    <string name="ad_tip_5">White list</string>
    <string name="ad_tip_6">Turn on ad interception</string>
    <string name="adapter_chapterlist_text_0">one</string>
    <string name="adapter_chapterlist_text_1">23%</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_add_to_bookmarks_iph">Quickly bookmark this page. To edit this shortcut, touch and hold.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_new_tab_iph">Quickly open a new tab. To edit this shortcut, touch and hold.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_new_tab_iph_settings">Quickly open a new tab. To edit this shortcut, go to Settings.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_open_in_browser_iph">Quickly open in browser. To edit this shortcut, touch and hold.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_page_summary_iph">Summarize page with AI</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_add_to_bookmarks">Add to bookmarks</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_based_on_window_width_description">Only available for small windows</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_based_on_your_usage">Based on your usage</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_based_on_your_usage_description">Current recommendation:  %1$s</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_new_tab">New tab</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_page_summary">Summarize this page</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_page_summary_description">Invokes AI Assistant</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_read_aloud">Listen to this page</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_share">Share this page</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_translate">Translate</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_preference_voice_search">Voice search</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_read_aloud_iph">Listen to this page. To edit this shortcut, touch and hold.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_review_pdf_iph">Review PDF with AI</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_share_iph">Quickly share this page. To edit this shortcut, touch and hold.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_share_iph_settings">Quickly share this page. To edit this shortcut, go to Settings.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_translate_iph">Quickly translate this page. To edit this shortcut, touch and hold.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_voice_search_iph">Quickly search with your voice. To edit this shortcut, touch and hold.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_button_voice_search_iph_settings">Quickly search with your voice. To edit this shortcut, go to Settings.</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_edit_shortcut">Edit toolbar shortcut</string>
    <string name="adaptive_toolbar_menu_edit_shortcut">Edit shortcut</string>
    <string name="adblock">Adblock</string>
    <string name="adblock_adblock">allow Adblock plug-in or not, the advertising shielding effect is very good but increase the power consumption and memory consumption of the device. If stuck, uninstall it in the sidebar Adblock management</string>
    <string name="adblock_black_suc">added to video replacement blacklist successfully</string>
    <string name="adblock_open">You are turning on the ad filtering function. Please read the user agreement. Ad blocking is implemented through filtering rules. Built-in filtering rules come from common network rules. If you are an individual, advertisement filtering will reduce the speed of web page opening and may also cause some web pages to be inaccessible normally. If you are a company and your website has no malicious advertisements but is blocked, please contact the author 625197595@qq.com to whitelist first. This browser is developed for individuals, hoping to get humanitarian sympathy. Malicious advertisement interception is for the protection of users, not subjectively can affect the normal operation of the website. Click OK to represent your consent and compliance with the above agreement.</string>
    <string name="adblockcurrent">Current page screen log</string>
    <string name="adblockopen">Enable Adblock rule?</string>
    <string name="adblockopenall">After the advertisement is turned on, the browser will block the webpage advertisement according to the rules provided by the Adblock party, which may cause some webpages to load slowly / display incompletely / the video cannot be played, etc. We will not bear any legal liability if you force us to open the advertisement filter. Are you sure you want to turn it on?</string>
    <string name="add">Add</string>
    <string name="add_book">Add bookmark</string>
    <string name="add_book_success">bookshelf added successfully</string>
    <string name="add_bookmark">Bookmark</string>
    <string name="add_bookmark_success">Bookmark added successfully</string>
    <string name="add_button">Add Button</string>
    <string name="add_classification">add classification</string>
    <string name="add_classificationname">add classification name</string>
    <string name="add_component_desc">Add Component</string>
    <string name="add_err_report">Please describe the issue below. If you want to receive follow-up updates, leave your email address.</string>
    <string name="add_language">Add language</string>
    <string name="add_pw">Encryption</string>
    <string name="add_size">Enlarge</string>
    <string name="add_talk">Add more speakers.</string>
    <string name="add_task">Add task</string>
    <string name="add_to_bookmarks">Add to bookmarks</string>
    <string name="add_to_dictionary">Add to dictionary</string>
    <string name="add_to_home">Add to Home Screen</string>
    <string name="add_to_mine">Add to desktop shortcut</string>
    <string name="add_username_dialog_add_username">Add username</string>
    <string name="add_username_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="add_username_dialog_text">To help Google Password Manager save your sign-in info, add your username for this site</string>
    <string name="add_username_dialog_title">Add your username</string>
    <string name="add_zl">Add Command</string>
    <string name="addcut">Please go to the application rights management first - turn on the create desktop shortcut permission, otherwise the icon cannot be generated</string>
    <string name="adddingyue">direct search results</string>
    <string name="added_to_homescreen">%1$s was added to your Home screen</string>
    <string name="addfall">Add failure</string>
    <string name="addhavahost">Add keywords containing domain names</string>
    <string name="addhome">add to the main page</string>
    <string name="address_accessory_sheet_content_description">Address</string>
    <string name="address_accessory_sheet_title">Addresses</string>
    <string name="address_accessory_sheet_toggle">Show saved addresses</string>
    <string name="address_bar_settings">Address bar</string>
    <string name="address_bar_settings_bottom">Bottom</string>
    <string name="address_bar_settings_currently_on_bottom">Address bar currently on bottom</string>
    <string name="address_bar_settings_currently_on_top">Address bar currently on top</string>
    <string name="address_bar_settings_description">You can also touch and hold the address bar to change the position.</string>
    <string name="address_bar_settings_description_foldable">When your device is folded, you can choose an option or touch and hold the address bar to change the position</string>
    <string name="address_bar_settings_top">Top</string>
    <string name="address_info">Addresses and More</string>
    <string name="addscreen">install to desktop shortcut</string>
    <string name="addsuccess">Add success</string>
    <string name="addtolauncher">introduction：Add Icon to system desktop</string>
    <string name="addtowhite">Add this site to the white list</string>
    <string name="addwhite">Join the white list</string>
    <string name="addyiyan">introduction：add a sentence to the system desktop</string>
    <string name="admark">Admark</string>
    <string name="adriji">Advertisement interception log</string>
    <string name="ads">ads</string>
    <string name="ads_0">ad blocking settings</string>
    <string name="ads_1">intercept log</string>
    <string name="ads_2">rule subscription</string>
    <string name="ads_3">white list of advertisements</string>
    <string name="ads_4">custom rules</string>
    <string name="adwhite">white list</string>
    <string name="agentweb_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="agentweb_download">Download</string>
    <string name="agentweb_honeycomblow">Wi-Fi disconnected. Continue the download via mobile data network?</string>
    <string name="agentweb_leave">Go away</string>
    <string name="agentweb_leave_app_and_go_other_page">leaving %1$s and opening another app?</string>
    <string name="agentweb_tips">Note</string>
    <string name="agree_audio">allow microphone request or not
</string>
    <string name="agree_cameta">allow camera requests or not
</string>
    <string name="agree_this">Agree</string>
    <string name="agreethii_yin">Login with agree</string>
    <string name="agreethis">is allowed</string>
    <string name="ai_assistant_service_error_toast">Couldn’t open AI assistant. Try again.</string>
    <string name="ai_error">Due to legal requirements, the current question cannot be answered.</string>
    <string name="ai_help">AIHelp</string>
    <string name="ai_mode_entrypoint_label">AI Mode</string>
    <string name="ai_search_hint">Enter a URL or your question</string>
    <string name="ai_search_mode_speed">⚡ Speed Mode</string>
    <string name="ai_search_mode_thinking">🧠 Thinking Mode</string>
    <string name="ai_search_type_all">🌐 All</string>
    <string name="ai_search_type_image">🖼️ Image</string>
    <string name="ai_search_type_pdf">📚 Library</string>
    <string name="ai_search_type_podcast">🎧 Podcast</string>
    <string name="ai_search_type_scholar">🎓 Scholar</string>
    <string name="ai_search_type_video">🎬 Video</string>
    <string name="ai_search_type_webpage">📄 Webpage</string>
    <string name="ai_tip">AI may make errors, please verify important information.</string>
    <string name="ai_tousu">AI Assistant aims to provide a powerful search experience by combining artificial intelligence and search engines. We have integrated Tencent sensitive word detection. If there is still illegal content, please report it to us, and we will handle it within 24 hours.</string>
    <string name="ai_txt">AITxT</string>
    <string name="ai_web">Intelligent selection</string>
    <string name="ai_web_intro">【Experimental】When double-tapping/long-pressing to select text, if it is a website URL, automatically expand the selection</string>
    <string name="ai_xieyi">AITxT allows AI to access the text of the webpage you are accessing, and AI will answer your questions based on the current text content. You need to know that the content answered by AI is based on the webpage, and the viewpoint is also based on the webpage. All statements do not represent our viewpoint; You are not allowed to inquire about any information that violates national laws from AI, and you will be responsible for any consequences arising from this.</string>
    <string name="aim_position">has located the corresponding result for you</string>
    <string name="albo_trans">Arabic</string>
    <string name="all">all</string>
    <string name="all_network_hot_search">Trending Online</string>
    <string name="all_noimg">don not show pictures</string>
    <string name="all_passwords_bottom_sheet_closed">List of credentials to be filled on touch is closed.</string>
    <string name="all_passwords_bottom_sheet_content_description">List of credentials to be filled on touch.</string>
    <string name="all_passwords_bottom_sheet_full_height">List of credentials to be filled on touch opened at full height.</string>
    <string name="all_passwords_bottom_sheet_half_height">List of credentials to be filled on touch opened at half height.</string>
    <string name="all_passwords_bottom_sheet_no_password">No password</string>
    <string name="all_passwords_bottom_sheet_search_hint">Search</string>
    <string name="all_passwords_bottom_sheet_subtitle">If you trust %s, you can use a saved password to sign in</string>
    <string name="all_passwords_bottom_sheet_title">Select password</string>
    <string name="all_plug">All</string>
    <string name="all_reovery_plug">Restore expansion and its data</string>
    <string name="all_sites">All sites</string>
    <string name="all_toast_use_sys">All bubble prompts use system styles</string>
    <string name="all_web">All Web</string>
    <string name="allow_chrome_signin_summary">Shows prompts to sign in to Chrome</string>
    <string name="allow_chrome_signin_title">Allow Chrome sign-in</string>
    <string name="allow_notify_download">Do you want to allow notification access to display your download progress in the notification bar?</string>
    <string name="allow_plug_menu_inject">Allow expand/plug-in injection long press menu</string>
    <string name="alwaylight_shut">screen always on mode is off</string>
    <string name="always">Always</string>
    <string name="android.credentials.TYPE_PASSWORD_CREDENTIAL">Password</string>
    <string name="android_app_history_open_full">Some of your history might not show up here. To see all your Chrome history, open full Chrome history.</string>
    <string name="android_app_history_open_full_other_forms">Some of your history might not show up here. To see all your Chrome history, open full Chrome history. Also, your Google Account may have other forms of browsing history at &lt;link&gt;myactivity.google.com&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_ar_camera_permission_off">To let %1$s use AR, also turn on camera in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_camera_permission_off">To let %1$s access your camera, also turn on camera in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_extensions_summary">Enable experimental support for extensions in Android</string>
    <string name="android_extensions_title">Enable Extensions</string>
    <string name="android_hand_tracking_permission_off">To let %1$s use hand tracking, also turn on hand tracking in &lt;link&gt;system settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_history_blocked_site">Blocked site</string>
    <string name="android_history_from_other_apps">You may see the history from other apps that open links in Chrome.</string>
    <string name="android_history_from_other_apps_other_forms_of_history">You may see the history from other apps that open links in Chrome. Your Google Account may have other forms of browsing history at &lt;link&gt;myactivity.google.com&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_history_other_forms_of_history">Your Google Account may have other forms of browsing history at &lt;link&gt;myactivity.google.com&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_location_also_off_globally">Location access is also off for this device. Turn it on in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_location_off_globally">Location access is off for this device. Turn it on in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_location_permission_off">To let %1$s access your location, also turn on location in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_low">Android version too low!</string>
    <string name="android_microphone_permission_off">To let %1$s access your microphone, also turn on microphone in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_nfc_off_globally">NFC is off for this device. Turn it on in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_nfc_unsupported">This device can't read NFC</string>
    <string name="android_notifications_permission_off">To let %1$s send you notifications, also turn on notifications in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_permission_off">Turn on permission for %1$s in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="android_permission_off_plural">Turn on permissions for %1$s in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="androidx.credentials.TYPE_PUBLIC_KEY_CREDENTIAL">Passkey</string>
    <string name="androidx_startup">androidx.startup</string>
    <string name="anim_alpha">Transparent gradient</string>
    <string name="anim_circle">Circular wave</string>
    <string name="anim_left">Left thrust</string>
    <string name="anim_right">Starboard propulsion</string>
    <string name="anim_vertical">Push up and down</string>
    <string name="animing">Animation</string>
    <string name="ans_third_app">Request to launch a third-party application</string>
    <string name="anti_abuse_description">Sites you visit can verify that you're a real person and not a bot</string>
    <string name="anti_abuse_permission_title">Auto-verify</string>
    <string name="anti_abuse_things_to_consider_header">Things to consider</string>
    <string name="anti_abuse_things_to_consider_section_one">This setting works without identifying you or allowing sites to see your browsing history, though sites can share a small amount of info as part of the verification</string>
    <string name="anti_abuse_when_on_header">When on</string>
    <string name="anti_abuse_when_on_section_one">A site you visit can save a small amount of info with Chrome, mainly to validate you're not a bot</string>
    <string name="anti_abuse_when_on_section_three">Browsing is faster because a site is less likely to ask you to verify you're a real person</string>
    <string name="anti_abuse_when_on_section_two">As you keep browsing, sites can check with Chrome and verify with a previous site you've visited that you're likely a real person</string>
    <string name="apk_1">apk.1安装器</string>
    <string name="app_banner_add">Add</string>
    <string name="app_banner_install">Install</string>
    <string name="app_banner_view_native_app_install_accessibility">Get the app from the Google Play Store: %s</string>
    <string name="app_color">menufont-color</string>
    <string name="app_down">[application]</string>
    <string name="app_language_title">%1$s’s language</string>
    <string name="app_list_permission">, or you may not give permission to read the application list, Android system design defects, will judge whether the application exists with the permission to read the application list mixed</string>
    <string name="app_name">RainCore</string>
    <string name="app_name_my">雨见cBeta</string>
    <string name="app_name_read">Reading mode</string>
    <string name="app_no_newtab">Do not create a new tab when launched externally</string>
    <string name="app_path">App Address</string>
    <string name="app_search">&lt;font color="#03A9F4"&gt;【App】&lt;/font&gt;</string>
    <string name="appbar_scrolling_view_behavior">com.google.android.material.appbar.AppBarLayout$ScrollingViewBehavior</string>
    <string name="appearance_settings">Appearance</string>
    <string name="application_version_title">Application version</string>
    <string name="apply">Apply</string>
    <string name="ar_module_title">Augmented Reality</string>
    <string name="ar_permission_title">Augmented reality</string>
    <string name="archive_dialog_close_all_inactive_tabs_confirmation">Close all</string>
    <string name="archive_dialog_close_all_inactive_tabs_confirmation_description">You can always get them back in history</string>
    <string name="archive_settings_allow_autodelete_title">Automatically close inactive items</string>
    <string name="archive_settings_archive_duplicate_tabs_summary">All duplicate tabs will now also be archived, with the exception of the most recently used copy.</string>
    <string name="archive_settings_archive_duplicate_tabs_title">Archive duplicate tabs</string>
    <string name="archive_settings_description_section">Choose when tabs and tab groups are automatically moved to the inactive section.</string>
    <string name="archive_settings_section_title">Move to inactive section</string>
    <string name="archive_settings_time_delta_never">Never</string>
    <string name="archive_settings_title">Inactive</string>
    <string name="archived_tab_iph_card_subtitle">Tabs you haven’t used for %1$d days are moved here%2$s. You can change this anytime in %3$s.</string>
    <string name="archived_tab_iph_card_subtitle_autodelete_section"> and closed after %1$d months</string>
    <string name="archived_tab_iph_card_subtitle_settings_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="archived_tab_iph_card_subtitle_with_tab_groups">Tabs and tab groups you haven’t used for %1$d days are moved here%2$s. You can change this anytime in %3$s.</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_auto_delete_promo_closed">Notice about Tabs Auto Delete changes closed.</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_auto_delete_promo_full_height">Notice about Tabs Auto Delete at full height</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_auto_delete_promo_half_height">Notice about Tabs Auto Delete at half height.</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_auto_delete_promo_no_button">Go to settings</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_auto_delete_promo_title">Your inactive items won’t pile up</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_auto_delete_promo_yes_button">Got it</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_dialog_close_all_button">Close all</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_dialog_restore_all_action">Restore all</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_dialog_select_action">Select items</string>
    <string name="archived_tabs_dialog_settings_action">Settings</string>
    <string name="are_you_quit">Are you sure you want to exit the browser?</string>
    <string name="areyoublock">you want to block</string>
    <string name="aria_download">Aria-based open source downloader</string>
    <string name="as_other">opens as</string>
    <string name="ask">ask</string>
    <string name="atomic_component_load_failed">Failed to load atomic component. Please check your network connection.</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_btn_experience">Sure</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_btn_later">Later</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_btn_never">Never</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_desc_1">A brand new visual experience with modern design concepts</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_desc_2">Atom-level refined UI elements</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_desc_3">Polymorphic interactive animations</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_desc_4">Folder support</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_desc_5">Enhanced browsing efficiency and aesthetics</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_fallback_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_fallback_experience">Try</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_fallback_message">The new theme Atomic Polymorphism is available. Would you like to try it?</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_fallback_title">New Theme Discovered</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_fallback_toast">Welcome to the new theme!</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_guide_title">New Theme Invitation</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_name">Atomic Polymorphism</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_never_remind_toast">Theme recommendations have been disabled</string>
    <string name="atomic_theme_tip">Click the button below to start a new browsing journey</string>
    <string name="audio_capture_notification_title">A site is using your microphone</string>
    <string name="auth_error_card_button">Sign in again</string>
    <string name="auth_tab_secured_by_chrome_template">Secured by %1$s</string>
    <string name="auto_clear_same">Automatic Deduplication</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_dialog_message">Tell us about your experience. Or &lt;link&gt;change your settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_dialog_no_feedback_message">You can turn off dark theme for sites in your settings.</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_dialog_no_feedback_positive_button">Open settings</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_dialog_no_feedback_title">Change your dark theme settings?</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_dialog_positive_button">Share feedback</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_dialog_title">Share feedback on dark theme for sites?</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_message_button">Open settings</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_message_opt_in_body">You can turn it on or off in settings</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_message_opt_in_button">Turn on</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_message_opt_in_title">Dark theme for sites is available</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_message_title">Dark theme for sites is on in Chrome</string>
    <string name="auto_dark_web_content_title">Dark theme for sites</string>
    <string name="auto_float_mode">Automatically enter into hovering playback</string>
    <string name="auto_fresh">auto refresh</string>
    <string name="auto_game_mode">Automatic entry into gaming (full-screen) mode</string>
    <string name="auto_go">Automation</string>
    <string name="auto_hide_func">Auto-Hide Toolbar</string>
    <string name="auto_install_app">Automatic installation</string>
    <string name="auto_open_pdf_enabled_description">Downloaded PDFs automatically open with one of the PDF viewers on your device</string>
    <string name="auto_open_pdf_enabled_title">Automatically open PDFs</string>
    <string name="auto_open_pdf_enabled_with_app_description">Downloaded PDFs automatically open with %1$s</string>
    <string name="auto_open_synced_tab_groups_summary">Automatically open tab groups from other devices</string>
    <string name="auto_pc_mode">Automatically enter desktop mode (UA)</string>
    <string name="auto_picture_in_picture_permission_title">Automatic picture-in-picture</string>
    <string name="auto_player">Automatically Invoke Smart Player</string>
    <string name="auto_preview">Auto preview</string>
    <string name="auto_show">auto display</string>
    <string name="auto_update">Automatic update</string>
    <string name="auto_updateyiyan">Automatic update</string>
    <string name="autofill_add_local_iban">Add IBAN</string>
    <string name="autofill_address_already_saved_in_account_record_type_notice">You can use saved addresses across Google products. This address is saved in your Google Account, $1.</string>
    <string name="autofill_address_edit_dialog_required_field_content_description">%1$s, required</string>
    <string name="autofill_address_home_and_work_record_type_notice">Info from your Google Account $1 can help you fill forms faster in Chrome</string>
    <string name="autofill_address_summary_separator">, </string>
    <string name="autofill_address_will_be_saved_in_account_record_type_notice">You can use saved addresses across Google products. This address will be saved in your Google Account, $1.</string>
    <string name="autofill_addresses_settings_title">Addresses and more</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_issuer_bottom_sheet_closed">List of Buy-Now-Pay-Later issuers is closed.</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_issuer_bottom_sheet_content_description">Buy-Now-Pay-Later issuers available for pay over time. Keyboard hidden.</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_issuer_bottom_sheet_full_height">Buy-Now-Pay-Later issuers available for pay over time opened at full height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_issuer_bottom_sheet_half_height">Buy-Now-Pay-Later issuers available for pay over time opened at half height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_pay_later_options_text">Pay later options</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_progress_sheet_closed">Buy-Now-Pay-Later progress screen is closed.</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_progress_sheet_content_description">Buy-Now-Pay-Later progress screen. Keyboard hidden.</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_progress_sheet_full_height">Buy-Now-Pay-Later progress screen opened at full height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_progress_sheet_half_height">Buy-Now-Pay-Later progress screen opened at half height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_bnpl_suggestion_label_for_unavailable_purchase">Unavailable for this purchase</string>
    <string name="autofill_bottom_sheet_all_loyalty_cards_screen_title">Your loyalty cards</string>
    <string name="autofill_bottom_sheet_all_your_loyalty_cards">All your loyalty cards</string>
    <string name="autofill_bottom_sheet_back_button_description">Back</string>
    <string name="autofill_bottom_sheet_expand_all_loyalty_cards_description">Change to all loyalty cards under this menu item.</string>
    <string name="autofill_bottom_sheet_manage_loyalty_cards">Manage loyalty cards</string>
    <string name="autofill_bottom_sheet_manage_payment_methods">Manage payment methods</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_auth_selection_dialog_title_multiple_options">Choose how you'll verify it's you</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_benefits_settings_page_title">Card benefits</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_bnpl_linked_issuer_pill_label">Linked</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_editor_virtual_card_turn_off_button_label">Turn off</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_editor_virtual_card_turn_on_button_label">Turn on</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_holder_name">Cardholder name</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_authentication_selection_dialog_current_info_not_seen_text">Not seeing your current info? Contact your provider to update it.</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_authentication_selection_dialog_issuer_confirmation_text">Your card provider wants to make sure it's you</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_authentication_selection_dialog_ok_button_label_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_authentication_selection_dialog_ok_button_label_send">Send</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_new_card_link">Update card</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_otp_input_dialog_pending_message">Verifying code…</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_otp_input_dialog_title">Enter code</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_progress_bar_message">Connecting to your card provider…</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_prompt_enable_fido_auth_checkbox">Use screen lock to confirm cards from now on</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_prompt_error_try_again_cvc">Check your CVC and try again</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_prompt_error_try_again_cvc_and_expiration">Check your expiration date and CVC and try again</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_prompt_error_try_again_expiration_date">Check your expiration date and try again</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_prompt_error_try_again_expiration_month">Check your expiration month and try again</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_prompt_error_try_again_expiration_year">Check your expiration year and try again</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_verification_in_progress">Confirming card…</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_verification_success">Your card is confirmed</string>
    <string name="autofill_card_unmask_verification_title">Verify it's you</string>
    <string name="autofill_create_credit_card">Add card</string>
    <string name="autofill_create_first_credit_card_button_text">Add payment method</string>
    <string name="autofill_create_first_credit_card_summary">Save a payment method in your Google Account to autofill it for purchases made in Chrome</string>
    <string name="autofill_create_first_credit_card_title">Check out faster with autofill</string>
    <string name="autofill_create_profile">Add address</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_delete_confirmation_title">Delete card</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_billing_address">Billing address</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_expiration_date">Expiration date*</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_expiration_date_content_description">Expiration date, required</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_expiration_date_hint">MM / YY</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_expired_card">Card expired</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_invalid_expiration_date">Invalid date</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_invalid_nickname">Nickname can’t include numbers</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_name">Name on card</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_nickname">Card nickname</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_number">Card number*</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_number_content_description">Card number, required</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_security_code">Security code</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_virtual_card_unenroll_dialog_message">You’ll no longer be able to use your virtual card with Google Pay. &lt;link1&gt;Learn more about virtual cards&lt;/link1&gt;</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_virtual_card_unenroll_dialog_positive_button_label">Remove</string>
    <string name="autofill_credit_card_editor_virtual_card_unenroll_dialog_title">Remove your virtual card?</string>
    <string name="autofill_delete_account_address_record_type_notice">This address will be deleted from your Google Account, $1</string>
    <string name="autofill_delete_address_confirmation_dialog_title">Delete address</string>
    <string name="autofill_delete_local_address_record_type_notice">This address will be deleted from this device</string>
    <string name="autofill_delete_saved_cvcs_confirmation_dialog_delete_button_label">Delete</string>
    <string name="autofill_delete_saved_cvcs_confirmation_dialog_message">All security codes saved on your device and in your Google Account will be deleted</string>
    <string name="autofill_delete_saved_cvcs_confirmation_dialog_title">Delete saved security codes?</string>
    <string name="autofill_delete_suggestion_button">Delete</string>
    <string name="autofill_delete_sync_address_record_type_notice">This address will be deleted from this and your other signed-in devices</string>
    <string name="autofill_disable_settings_button_label">Autofill services settings</string>
    <string name="autofill_disable_settings_explanation">To enable these settings and use payment info from your Google Account, visit autofill services settings.</string>
    <string name="autofill_disable_settings_explanation_title">Google isn’t your autofill provider</string>
    <string name="autofill_edit_address_dialog_title">Edit address</string>
    <string name="autofill_edit_address_label">Edit</string>
    <string name="autofill_edit_address_label_content_description">Edit, opens a new window</string>
    <string name="autofill_edit_address_required_field_error">Enter $1</string>
    <string name="autofill_edit_credit_card">Edit card</string>
    <string name="autofill_edit_local_iban">Edit IBAN</string>
    <string name="autofill_enable_credit_cards_toggle_label">Save and fill payment methods</string>
    <string name="autofill_enable_credit_cards_toggle_sublabel">Fills in payment forms with your saved payment methods</string>
    <string name="autofill_enable_profiles_toggle_label">Save and fill addresses</string>
    <string name="autofill_enable_profiles_toggle_sublabel">Includes information like phone numbers, email addresses, and shipping addresses</string>
    <string name="autofill_expiration_date_month_hint">MM</string>
    <string name="autofill_expiration_date_separator">/</string>
    <string name="autofill_expiration_date_year_hint">YY</string>
    <string name="autofill_fix_flow_prompt_save_card_label">Save card</string>
    <string name="autofill_from_google_account">Google Pay</string>
    <string name="autofill_from_google_account_long">From Google Pay</string>
    <string name="autofill_home_profile_icon_accessibility_label">Home address</string>
    <string name="autofill_iban_delete_confirmation_title">Delete IBAN</string>
    <string name="autofill_iban_editor_local_save_footer">This IBAN will be saved to this device only</string>
    <string name="autofill_iban_editor_nickname">Nickname</string>
    <string name="autofill_iban_editor_value">IBAN</string>
    <string name="autofill_iban_generic">Iban</string>
    <string name="autofill_iph_external_account_profile_suggestion">You can now use addresses from your Google Account</string>
    <string name="autofill_keyboard_accessory_content_description">Autofill suggestions available above the keyboard</string>
    <string name="autofill_keyboard_accessory_content_fallback_description">Alternative filling options available above the keyboard</string>
    <string name="autofill_local_profile_icon_accessibility_label">Local address</string>
    <string name="autofill_long_press_passkey_option">Use a passkey</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_autofill_button">Autofill</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_bottom_sheet_closed">List of loyalty cards is closed.</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_bottom_sheet_content_description">Loyalty cards available to be filled on touch. Keyboard hidden.</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_bottom_sheet_full_height">Loyalty cards available to be filled on touch opened at full height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_bottom_sheet_half_height">Loyalty cards available to be filled on touch opened at half height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_bottom_sheet_title">Autofill loyalty card</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_first_time_usage_bottom_sheet_subtitle">Manage loyalty cards or turn these suggestions off in Google Wallet</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_first_time_usage_bottom_sheet_title">Now you can autofill loyalty cards from Google Wallet</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_generic">Loyalty card</string>
    <string name="autofill_loyalty_card_wallet_settings_button">Wallet settings</string>
    <string name="autofill_mandatory_reauth_opt_in_accept">Turn on</string>
    <string name="autofill_mandatory_reauth_opt_in_closed">Alert about new payment setting is closed</string>
    <string name="autofill_mandatory_reauth_opt_in_content_description">Alert about new payment setting</string>
    <string name="autofill_mandatory_reauth_opt_in_explanation">For added protection, always use your fingerprint, face, or other screen lock when you pay using autofill</string>
    <string name="autofill_mandatory_reauth_opt_in_no_thanks">No thanks</string>
    <string name="autofill_mandatory_reauth_opt_in_opened_full">Alert about new payment setting is opened</string>
    <string name="autofill_mandatory_reauth_opt_in_title">Verify it's you to autofill payment methods?</string>
    <string name="autofill_optional_tag">Optional</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_change_autofill_service_title">Change autofill service?</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_confirm_restart">Restart Chrome</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_hint_3p_setting_disabled">To set your preferred service for autofill, first add the service in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt; .</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_hint_3p_setting_ready">Autofill services are also managed in &lt;link&gt;Android Settings&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_hint_policy">Your administrator manages this setting.</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_restart_prompt_paragraph_1_text">After Chrome restarts, your info saved from your new provider will be used to autofill passwords, passkeys, addresses, payment methods, and other info.</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_restart_prompt_paragraph_2_text">Restart Chrome to finish this change. Tabs automatically reopen when you restart.</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_restart_prompt_text">To finish setting up autofill, restart Chrome now. Your tabs will automatically reopen.</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_restart_prompt_title">Restart Chrome?</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_title">Autofill services</string>
    <string name="autofill_options_undo_toggle_change">Cancel</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_method_a11y_item_collection_info">%1$s, %2$s of %3$s.</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_method_bottom_sheet_benefits_terms_label">Terms apply for card benefits</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_method_bottom_sheet_closed">List of payment methods is closed.</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_method_bottom_sheet_content_description">Payment methods available to be filled on touch. Keyboard hidden.</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_method_bottom_sheet_full_height">Payment methods available to be filled on touch opened at full height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_method_bottom_sheet_half_height">Payment methods available to be filled on touch opened at half height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_method_bottom_sheet_title">Autofill payment info</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_method_continue_button">Continue</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_method_delete_confirmation_description">This payment method will be deleted from this device</string>
    <string name="autofill_payment_methods">Payment methods</string>
    <string name="autofill_payments_authenticator_selection_dialog_negative_button_label">Cancel</string>
    <string name="autofill_payments_otp_verification_dialog_cant_find_code_message">Didn’t receive your code? &lt;link&gt;Get new code&lt;/link&gt;</string>
    <string name="autofill_payments_otp_verification_dialog_negative_button_label">Cancel</string>
    <string name="autofill_payments_otp_verification_dialog_otp_input_hint">Enter %1$s-digit verification code</string>
    <string name="autofill_payments_otp_verification_dialog_positive_button_label">Confirm</string>
    <string name="autofill_pending_dialog_loading_accessibility_description">Loading</string>
    <string name="autofill_popup_content_description">Showing Autofill popup</string>
    <string name="autofill_profile_editor_country">Country/Region</string>
    <string name="autofill_profile_editor_email_address">Email</string>
    <string name="autofill_profile_editor_phone_number">Phone</string>
    <string name="autofill_remove_account_name_and_email_profile_suggestion_confirmation_body">You can edit your name &lt;link&gt;in your Google Account $1&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="autofill_remove_account_name_and_email_profile_suggestion_confirmation_title">Remove this info from Chrome autofill?</string>
    <string name="autofill_remove_home_profile_suggestion_confirmation_body">Your home address can help you get things done across Google services, like more relevant Search results and directions in Google Maps. You can edit or delete your address &lt;link&gt;in your Google Account $1&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="autofill_remove_home_profile_suggestion_confirmation_title">Remove home address from Chrome autofill?</string>
    <string name="autofill_remove_suggestion_button">Remove</string>
    <string name="autofill_remove_work_profile_suggestion_confirmation_body">Your work address can help you get things done across Google services, like more relevant Search results and directions in Google Maps. You can edit or delete your address &lt;link&gt;in your Google Account $1&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="autofill_remove_work_profile_suggestion_confirmation_title">Remove work address from Chrome autofill?</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_address_prompt_edit_button_tooltip">Edit address</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_card_prompt_bottom_sheet_closed">Save card closed.</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_card_prompt_bottom_sheet_content_description">Save card</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_card_prompt_bottom_sheet_full_height">Save card opened at full height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_card_prompt_cardholder_name_tooltip">This name is from your Google Account</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_card_prompt_confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_iban_bottom_sheet_nickname_hint">Nickname (optional)</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_iban_prompt_bottom_sheet_closed">Save IBAN closed.</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_iban_prompt_bottom_sheet_content_description">Save IBAN</string>
    <string name="autofill_save_iban_prompt_bottom_sheet_full_height">Save IBAN opened at full height.</string>
    <string name="autofill_scan_credit_card">Scan new card</string>
    <string name="autofill_scan_credit_card_button">Scan card</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_bulk_remove_cvc_label">Delete saved security codes</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_card_benefits_issuer_term_text">See terms here</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_card_benefits_label">Card benefits</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_card_benefits_learn_about_link_text">&lt;link&gt;Learn more&lt;/link&gt; about card benefits</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_card_benefits_preference_summary">Choose whether you see your card benefits at checkout (bank terms apply)</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_card_benefits_toggle_summary">Show which rewards and benefits are available for your cards at checkout</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_card_benefits_toggle_summary_with_issuer_terms_apply_text">Show available card benefits and rewards at checkout. Issuer terms apply.</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_cvc_saved_label">CVC saved</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_enable_cvc_storage_label">Save security codes</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_enable_cvc_storage_sublabel">Check out faster when your CVCs are saved</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_enable_payment_method_mandatory_reauth_label">Verify it's you to autofill payment methods</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_enable_payment_method_mandatory_reauth_sublabel">For added protection, always use your fingerprint, face, or other screen lock when you pay using autofill</string>
    <string name="autofill_settings_page_summary_separated_by_pipe">%1$s | %2$s</string>
    <string name="autofill_third_party_filling_default">Autofill with Google</string>
    <string name="autofill_third_party_filling_default_description">Use Google Password Manager and Chrome Autofill to save and fill passwords, payment methods, and addresses</string>
    <string name="autofill_third_party_filling_default_description_new">Use info saved in your Google Account to autofill passwords, passkeys, addresses, payment methods, and other info</string>
    <string name="autofill_third_party_filling_opt_in">Autofill using another service</string>
    <string name="autofill_third_party_filling_opt_in_description">To use another autofill service in Chrome, turn it on in Android settings and here</string>
    <string name="autofill_third_party_filling_opt_in_description_new">To use another autofill service in Chrome, choose your autofill provider in Android settings</string>
    <string name="autofill_update_address_prompt_new_values_section_label">New</string>
    <string name="autofill_update_address_prompt_old_values_section_label">Old</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_container_accessibility_description">%1$s, virtual card</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_enroll_closed_description">Virtual card enrollment closed</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_enroll_content_description">Virtual card enrollment</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_enroll_full_height_content_description">Virtual card enrollment opened at full height</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_enroll_loading_throbber_accessible_name">Turning on virtual card</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_enrolled_text">Virtual card turned on</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_enrollment_accept_button_label">Yes</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_enrollment_dialog_card_container_title">Virtual card</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_enrollment_dialog_education_text">A virtual card hides your actual card to help protect you from potential fraud. &lt;link1&gt;Learn more about virtual cards&lt;/link1&gt;</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_enrollment_dialog_title_label">Make it more secure with a virtual card next time?</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_entry_prefix">Virtual card</string>
    <string name="autofill_virtual_card_number_switch_label">Virtual card</string>
    <string name="autofill_wallet_management_link_text">Edit</string>
    <string name="autofill_work_profile_icon_accessibility_label">Work address</string>
    <string name="automatic_downloads_permission_title">Automatic downloads</string>
    <string name="automatically_blocked">Automatically blocked</string>
    <string name="autotip">he automation function can only be implemented in the web page!</string>
    <string name="auxiliary_search_module_button_go_to_settings">Go to settings</string>
    <string name="auxiliary_search_module_button_got_it">Got it</string>
    <string name="auxiliary_search_module_button_no_thanks">No thanks</string>
    <string name="auxiliary_search_module_button_turn_on">Turn on</string>
    <string name="auxiliary_search_module_content">Chrome now shares your recent tabs with your device. You’ll see them in your device’s app list and search results. You can turn this off anytime in Chrome settings.</string>
    <string name="auxiliary_search_module_content_default_off">Let Chrome share your recent tabs with your device to see them in your device's app list and search results. You can turn this on or off in Chrome settings.</string>
    <string name="auxiliary_search_module_context_menu_hide">Hide View tabs in your app list</string>
    <string name="auxiliary_search_module_name">View tabs in your app list</string>
    <string name="avatar_upload_failed">Avatar upload failed</string>
    <string name="avatar_upload_success">Avatar uploaded successfully</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="back_ai">Back to AI Assistant</string>
    <string name="back_ation_allow">Enable BackwardGesture (considering want ForwardGesture only)</string>
    <string name="back_auto_close">Auto Stop in Background</string>
    <string name="back_button_content_description">back</string>
    <string name="back_color">Background Color</string>
    <string name="back_geo">Disallow Web Page Location Requests While App is in Background</string>
    <string name="back_pace">Background Open Webpage</string>
    <string name="back_play">playback</string>
    <string name="back_play_settle">By default, the browser is enabled to enter the background and still play audio. If you need to modify this configuration, please click OK</string>
    <string name="back_register">Back Subscription</string>
    <string name="back_runing">background</string>
    <string name="back_settle">Back to settings</string>
    <string name="back_stil_active">Keep the web page active (floating window permission is required)</string>
    <string name="back_sttle2">Exit setup</string>
    <string name="back_title">Backup/Recovery</string>
    <string name="back_up">Backup</string>
    <string name="backend">Software background activities</string>
    <string name="background_settings">Background Settings</string>
    <string name="background_sync_permission_title">Background sync</string>
    <string name="backnofresh">return no overload</string>
    <string name="backopen">Open in background</string>
    <string name="baidu">Baidu</string>
    <string name="baidu_origin">Baidu station fuzzy source</string>
    <string name="baidujubao">This result is from Baidu search, and will go to Baidu report center soon</string>
    <string name="baidumsg2">*Please confirm Baidu cloud has been downloaded to facilitate File Transfer</string>
    <string name="baidushibie">Baidu map recognition</string>
    <string name="bank_account_type_checking">Checking</string>
    <string name="bank_account_type_current">Current</string>
    <string name="bank_account_type_salary">Salary</string>
    <string name="bank_account_type_savings">Savings</string>
    <string name="bank_account_type_transacting">Account</string>
    <string name="baozha_copy_tip">Why jump here? 
 you clicked free copy, but the page was de copied or the copy failed. We help you extract the text near the click area; This function can be used for document text copying and even picture text extraction. It is an experimental function.</string>
    <string name="batch_upload_card_save_button">Save in account</string>
    <string name="batch_upload_dialog_cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="batch_upload_dialog_description">You can choose what data to save in your Google Account, %1$s.
You can also view and manage these items in your bookmarks, reading list, or password manager.</string>
    <string name="batch_upload_dialog_description_non_displayable_profile_data">You can choose what data to save in your Google Account.
You can also view and manage these items in your bookmarks, reading list, or password manager.</string>
    <string name="batch_upload_dialog_save_button">Save in account</string>
    <string name="batch_upload_dialog_title">Save data in your Google Account</string>
    <string name="bbtz">Extensions</string>
    <string name="bcz_fx_tip">You are about to enable violence without overloading. This function is not mature at present, which will lead to exceptions in many web pages, such as unable to log in and upload files. Please make sure you understand this risk</string>
    <string name="become_vip">Become a Donor</string>
    <string name="before_unload_leave_page">Leave Page</string>
    <string name="before_unload_message">This page is asking you to confirm that you want to leave - data you have entered may not be saved</string>
    <string name="before_unload_stay">Stay on Page</string>
    <string name="before_unload_title">Are you sure?</string>
    <string name="beian_number">备案号</string>
    <string name="below">Below the status bar</string>
    <string name="biaoti_width">Title Bar Width</string>
    <string name="big">big</string>
    <string name="big_txt">Enlarge Text</string>
    <string name="bigbang_">Fried words</string>
    <string name="bigbong_so">search by pic</string>
    <string name="bigbong_sot">search by text</string>
    <string name="bind_motation">Binding gesture</string>
    <string name="bind_qq">bound QQ</string>
    <string name="bind_success">Binding succeeded</string>
    <string name="bind_wx">bound wechat</string>
    <string name="bing_wallpaper">Bing Wallpaper</string>
    <string name="biometric_or_screen_lock_prompt_message">Use your biometric or screen lock to continue</string>
    <string name="biometric_prompt_message">Use your biometric to continue</string>
    <string name="bky_0">Resolve to</string>
    <string name="bky_1">Bookmark data, add</string>
    <string name="black_full">has been successfully added to the full screen blacklist</string>
    <string name="blackwhite">black and white</string>
    <string name="blank">Blank Page</string>
    <string name="blob_alert">Blob files can only be downloaded through the built-in downloader, adjustments have been made automatically</string>
    <string name="block">block</string>
    <string name="block_">kill</string>
    <string name="block_access">Disable Accessibility Service</string>
    <string name="block_app">prohibit evoking applications</string>
    <string name="block_copy">disable writing to the clipboard</string>
    <string name="block_download">Block download</string>
    <string name="block_error">Prevent page jumping caused by accessibility software like Li TiaoTiao. This feature has not been fully tested and may lead to various issues such as crashes. If any abnormalities occur, please close immediately.</string>
    <string name="block_go_host">prohibit URL from jumping to external host</string>
    <string name="block_js_alert">prohibit JS pop-up</string>
    <string name="block_longpress_menu">Disable Long-Press Menu</string>
    <string name="block_player">do not replace player</string>
    <string name="block_redirect_alert">Redirection blocked. Please go to Menu - Site Settings - External Link Redirection to change this setting.</string>
    <string name="blockcopy_suc">Intercept clipboard request</string>
    <string name="blockdom">Block element</string>
    <string name="blocked_ads_dialog_always_allow">Allow for this site</string>
    <string name="blocked_ads_dialog_learn_more">Learn more</string>
    <string name="blocked_ads_dialog_message">This site shows intrusive or misleading ads. ^1</string>
    <string name="blocked_ads_dialog_title">Ads blocked</string>
    <string name="blocked_navigation_warning">Navigation is blocked: %1$s</string>
    <string name="blockhost">Block host</string>
    <string name="blocking_choice_dialog_first_message">Based on a law in your region, you need to choose your browser and search engine</string>
    <string name="blocking_choice_dialog_first_title">Choose your default apps</string>
    <string name="blocking_choice_dialog_second_message">The apps you chose will be used by default. If an app isn’t already on this device, it’ll be downloaded shortly.</string>
    <string name="blocking_choice_dialog_second_title">Choices saved</string>
    <string name="blockurl">Block the link</string>
    <string name="blog">Blog</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_adapter_off">&lt;link&gt;Turn on Bluetooth&lt;/link&gt; to allow pairing</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_adapter_off_help">&lt;link&gt;Get help&lt;/link&gt;</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_confirm_button">Pair</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_device_connected">Connected Device</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_dialog_title">%1$s wants to pair</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_need_location_permission">Chrome needs location access to scan for devices. &lt;permission_link&gt;Update permissions&lt;/permission_link&gt;</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_need_location_permission_and_services_on">Chrome needs location access to scan for devices. &lt;permission_link&gt;Update permissions&lt;/permission_link&gt;. Location access is also &lt;services_link&gt;turned off for this device&lt;/services_link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_need_location_permission_help">&lt;link&gt;Get help&lt;/link&gt;</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_need_location_services_on">Chrome needs location access to scan for devices. Location access is &lt;services_link&gt;turned off for this device&lt;/services_link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_need_nearby_devices_permission">Chrome needs permission to scan for nearby devices. &lt;permission_link&gt;Update permissions&lt;/permission_link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_not_found">No compatible devices found</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_not_seeing_it_idle">&lt;link1&gt;Get help&lt;/link1&gt; or &lt;link2&gt;re-scan&lt;/link2&gt;</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_notification_content_text">Tap to return to %1$s</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_notification_content_text_incognito">Tap to return to the site</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_scanning_device_unknown">Unknown or unsupported device (%1$s)</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_scanning_prompt_allow_button_text">Allow</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_scanning_prompt_block_button_text">Block</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_scanning_prompt_no_devices_found_prompt">No nearby devices found.</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_scanning_prompt_origin">%1$s wants to scan for nearby Bluetooth devices. The following devices have been found:</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_searching">&lt;link&gt;Get help&lt;/link&gt; while scanning for devices…</string>
    <string name="bluetooth_unable_to_turn_on_adapter">Chrome is unable to turn on Bluetooth adapter</string>
    <string name="book_circle_intro">Yujian and Circle joint plug-in, powerful</string>
    <string name="book_error">Bookmark data verification failed, please check whether the file content is encrypted</string>
    <string name="book_history_settle">Bookmark/History Settings</string>
    <string name="book_history_style">Bookmark/History Management Style</string>
    <string name="book_import_error">Bookmark import encountered some exceptions</string>
    <string name="book_intro">Local bookmarks do not sync directly with Firefox bookmarks. Only when local bookmarks are empty, will Bookmarks on Mobile Devices be downloaded; synchronized bookmarks are stored in Bookmarks on Desktop Devices.</string>
    <string name="book_m_0">Previous chapter</string>
    <string name="book_m_1">Next chapter</string>
    <string name="book_m_10">Du Xiaoyao</string>
    <string name="book_m_11">Du yaya</string>
    <string name="book_m_12">Du Bowen</string>
    <string name="book_m_13">Du Xiaotong</string>
    <string name="book_m_14">Du Xiaomeng</string>
    <string name="book_m_15">Dumido</string>
    <string name="book_m_16">Du Xiaojiao</string>
    <string name="book_m_17">typeface</string>
    <string name="book_m_18">Slide cover</string>
    <string name="book_m_19">translation</string>
    <string name="book_m_2">function</string>
    <string name="book_m_20">shear</string>
    <string name="book_m_21">style</string>
    <string name="book_m_5">Speed of speech</string>
    <string name="book_m_6">reader</string>
    <string name="book_m_7">Female voice</string>
    <string name="book_m_8">Male voice</string>
    <string name="book_m_9">Special male voice</string>
    <string name="book_rule_error">In order to adapt to the latest bookmarks manager, your bookmarks have been upgraded and transferred. However, due to some reasons, your sorting records may be lost. We are very sorry for the inconvenience</string>
    <string name="book_settle">Collection Settings</string>
    <string name="book_tip1">mismatch feedback</string>
    <string name="book_tip2">you can leave your email and we will inform you by email when the adaptation is completed</string>
    <string name="book_yujian">Rain See Reading</string>
    <string name="book_yujian_intro">Original reading mode, limited energy, no longer maintained</string>
    <string name="book_yun_service">Bookmark Cloud Service</string>
    <string name="bookemark_input_adddesk">To Homepage</string>
    <string name="bookemark_input_database">To Cloud</string>
    <string name="bookmark">Bookmark</string>
    <string name="bookmark_bar_all_bookmarks_button_title">All bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmark_bar_content_description">Bookmarks Bar</string>
    <string name="bookmark_bar_folder_content_description">%1$s folder</string>
    <string name="bookmark_bar_overflow_button_content_description">More bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmark_bar_setting">Show bookmarks bar</string>
    <string name="bookmark_bar_setting_subtitle">Hidden on narrow screens</string>
    <string name="bookmark_choose_folder">Choose folder</string>
    <string name="bookmark_folder">Folder</string>
    <string name="bookmark_item_delete">Delete</string>
    <string name="bookmark_item_edit">Edit</string>
    <string name="bookmark_item_move">Move to…</string>
    <string name="bookmark_item_select">Select</string>
    <string name="bookmark_manager_back_to_page_by_adding_bookmark">You can get back to a page that’s important to you by adding a bookmark</string>
    <string name="bookmark_manager_empty_state">You’ll find your bookmarks here</string>
    <string name="bookmark_missing_title">Title required</string>
    <string name="bookmark_missing_url">URL required</string>
    <string name="bookmark_name">Name</string>
    <string name="bookmark_page_failed">Failed to add bookmark.</string>
    <string name="bookmark_page_moved_location">to %1$s</string>
    <string name="bookmark_page_saved">Bookmarked in %1$s</string>
    <string name="bookmark_page_saved_default">Bookmarked</string>
    <string name="bookmark_page_saved_folder">Bookmarked to %1$s</string>
    <string name="bookmark_page_saved_location">in %1$s</string>
    <string name="bookmark_parent_folder">Parent folder</string>
    <string name="bookmark_s">Bookmark</string>
    <string name="bookmark_save_flow_title">Bookmark saved</string>
    <string name="bookmark_settle">Bookmark management</string>
    <string name="bookmark_show_in_folder">Show in folder</string>
    <string name="bookmark_toolbar_close">Close dialog</string>
    <string name="bookmark_toolbar_delete">Delete bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmark_toolbar_move">Move bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmark_toolbar_search">Search your bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmark_toolbar_search_title">Search</string>
    <string name="bookmark_url">URL</string>
    <string name="bookmark_widget_description">Easily access your bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmark_widget_empty_msg">Nothing to show yet</string>
    <string name="bookmark_widget_title">Chromium bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmarks">Bookmarks</string>
    <string name="bookmarks_bar_empty_message">This folder is empty</string>
    <string name="bookmarks_bar_iph_message">You can turn on the bookmarks bar in Settings &gt; Appearance</string>
    <string name="bookmarks_save_flow_closed_description">Bookmark save flow closed</string>
    <string name="bookmarks_save_flow_content_description">Bookmark saved to %1$s</string>
    <string name="bookmarks_save_flow_opened_full">Bookmark save flow folders opened at full height</string>
    <string name="bookmarks_save_flow_opened_half">Bookmark save flow opened at half height</string>
    <string name="bookmarks_sync_promo_enable_sync">Bookmarks saved on your other devices will appear here.</string>
    <string name="bottom">Bottom</string>
    <string name="bottom_ball_settle">Floating ball gesture settings</string>
    <string name="bottom_bar_screen_position">Options available near bottom of the screen</string>
    <string name="bottom_color">Bottom Text Color</string>
    <string name="bottom_horozon">Quick horizontal swipe on the bottom half of the screen</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_accessibility_description">Swipe down to close.</string>
    <string name="bottom_sheet_behavior">com.google.android.material.bottomsheet.BottomSheetBehavior</string>
    <string name="bottom_tab_grid_new_tab">Add new tab to group</string>
    <string name="bottom_title_content">Content displayed in the title bar</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_action_collapse">Collapse</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_action_collapse_description">Collapse the bottom sheet</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_action_expand">Expand</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_action_expand_description">Expand the bottom sheet</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_action_expand_halfway">Expand halfway</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_action_half_expand_description">Half expand the bottom sheet</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_drag_handle_content_description">Drag handle</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_state_collapsed">Collapsed</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_state_expanded">Expanded</string>
    <string name="bottomsheet_state_half_expanded">Half expanded</string>
    <string name="browser_back_tip1">Browser Background Power Saving Optimization</string>
    <string name="browser_back_tip2">The browser is running in the background and has entered power saving mode</string>
    <string name="browser_back_tip3">Will run according to the configured Auto Stop in Background settings</string>
    <string name="browser_js">Browser script</string>
    <string name="browser_with_color">Change toolbar color</string>
    <string name="btn_cast_video">投屏</string>
    <string name="btn_exit">Exit</string>
    <string name="build_short_url">Generate Short Link</string>
    <string name="build_single_icon">You are adding a separate button to the extension, which will be more conducive to opening the extension quickly. We do not recommend that you add too many independent buttons, which will cause the interface to be untidy. Are you sure you add?</string>
    <string name="burger_emoji">🍔</string>
    <string name="burger_text">Burger</string>
    <string name="button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="button_new_incognito_tab">New Incognito tab</string>
    <string name="button_new_tab">New tab</string>
    <string name="button_new_tab_group">New tab group</string>
    <string name="button_open">Open</string>
    <string name="by_browser_crx">By using the browser extension</string>
    <string name="by_login_firefox">By logging in to Firefox Account</string>
    <string name="cache_clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="cache_dialog">This feature requires storage permission to continue. Please grant the permission first</string>
    <string name="cache_settle">Auto-Clean on Exit</string>
    <string name="caidan_0">coexistence of menu and text selection</string>
    <string name="caidan_1">text selection after free copy</string>
    <string name="caidan_2">using textselect only</string>
    <string name="call_notification_answer_action">Answer</string>
    <string name="call_notification_answer_video_action">Video</string>
    <string name="call_notification_decline_action">Decline</string>
    <string name="call_notification_hang_up_action">Hang Up</string>
    <string name="call_notification_incoming_text">Incoming call</string>
    <string name="call_notification_ongoing_text">Ongoing call</string>
    <string name="call_notification_screening_text">Screening an incoming call</string>
    <string name="camera">camera</string>
    <string name="can_insert">% clicking on an ad will increase progress</string>
    <string name="can_make_payment_title">Access payment methods</string>
    <string name="can_no_back">I really can't step back anymore</string>
    <string name="can_not_add">the current program cannot add</string>
    <string name="can_not_be_reg">This picture is not recognized</string>
    <string name="can_not_daan">You cannot open it. The answer has been shown</string>
    <string name="can_not_output">The current page does not support export</string>
    <string name="can_not_string">Unable to recognize text</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cancel_white">cancel whitelist</string>
    <string name="cancelsearch">cancel search</string>
    <string name="cancleFail">Cancel failed</string>
    <string name="cancleSuccess">Successful Cancellation</string>
    <string name="cancle_collect">Cancel collection</string>
    <string name="cancle_no_fresh">Cancel forced return no overloading</string>
    <string name="cancle_top">If you cancel the top, the tablet mode will not be displayed in the shortcut in the upper right corner.</string>
    <string name="canclead_tip">Cancellation of ad white list succeeded</string>
    <string name="canclechangliang">Cancel regular lighting</string>
    <string name="cannot_find_symbol">Can't find this symbol?</string>
    <string name="cannotnull">can not br null</string>
    <string name="capture">intercepting</string>
    <string name="capture_all">Click me to intercept full screen</string>
    <string name="capture_cap">Intercept search</string>
    <string name="capture_fail">the current kernel failed to get the long screenshot. Do you want to switch to the X5 kernel to get the long screenshot again</string>
    <string name="capture_long_pic">Truncated Figure</string>
    <string name="capture_poster">Screenshot Poster</string>
    <string name="capture_qrcode">Scan QR code</string>
    <string name="capture_tips">Draw the area range on the screen</string>
    <string name="capture_type_free">Curve Selection</string>
    <string name="capture_type_rect">Rectangular Box Selection</string>
    <string name="card_layout_text_0">Aggregate Videos &gt;</string>
    <string name="card_unmask_input_hint">CVC</string>
    <string name="cardboard_product_safety">Product safety</string>
    <string name="cast_ad_label">Ad</string>
    <string name="cast_casting_to_device">Casting to %1$s</string>
    <string name="cast_casting_video">Casting to %1$s</string>
    <string name="cast_closed_captions">Closed captions</string>
    <string name="cast_closed_captions_unavailable">Closed captions unavailable</string>
    <string name="cast_connecting_to_device">Connecting to %1$s</string>
    <string name="cast_disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="cast_dynamic_group_name_format">%1$s + %2$d</string>
    <string name="cast_expanded_controller_ad_image_description">Image displayed while the cast receiver is playing an ad</string>
    <string name="cast_expanded_controller_ad_in_progress">Ad in progress…</string>
    <string name="cast_expanded_controller_background_image">Album art</string>
    <string name="cast_expanded_controller_live_head_description">Current position is at the head of the live stream</string>
    <string name="cast_expanded_controller_live_stream_indicator">Live stream</string>
    <string name="cast_expanded_controller_loading">Loading…</string>
    <string name="cast_expanded_controller_skip_ad_label">Skip Ad</string>
    <string name="cast_expanded_controller_skip_ad_text">You can skip ad in %1$d…</string>
    <string name="cast_forward">Forward</string>
    <string name="cast_forward_10">Forward ten seconds</string>
    <string name="cast_forward_30">Forward thirty seconds</string>
    <string name="cast_intro_overlay_button_text">@android:string/ok</string>
    <string name="cast_invalid_stream_duration_text">--:--</string>
    <string name="cast_invalid_stream_position_text">--:--</string>
    <string name="cast_live_label">LIVE</string>
    <string name="cast_mute">Mute</string>
    <string name="cast_notification_connected_message">Connected to %1$s</string>
    <string name="cast_notification_connecting_message">Connecting to %1$s</string>
    <string name="cast_notification_default_channel_name">Cast</string>
    <string name="cast_notification_disconnect">Disconnect</string>
    <string name="cast_pause">Pause</string>
    <string name="cast_play">Play</string>
    <string name="cast_rewind">Rewind</string>
    <string name="cast_rewind_10">Rewind ten seconds</string>
    <string name="cast_rewind_30">Rewind thirty seconds</string>
    <string name="cast_seek_bar">Playback seek control</string>
    <string name="cast_skip_next">Skip to next item</string>
    <string name="cast_skip_prev">Skip to previous item</string>
    <string name="cast_stop">Stop</string>
    <string name="cast_stop_live_stream">Stop live stream</string>
    <string name="cast_tracks_chooser_dialog_audio">Audio</string>
    <string name="cast_tracks_chooser_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cast_tracks_chooser_dialog_closed_captions">Closed Captions</string>
    <string name="cast_tracks_chooser_dialog_default_track_name">Track %1$d</string>
    <string name="cast_tracks_chooser_dialog_none">None</string>
    <string name="cast_tracks_chooser_dialog_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="cast_tracks_chooser_dialog_subtitles">Subtitles</string>
    <string name="cast_unmute">Unmute</string>
    <string name="ceian_book_tip">You are switching side bookmarks. It is detected that you have opened the homepage. The homepage may conflict with the side bookmarks. Would you like to disable side bookmarks</string>
    <string name="center_color">Center Text Color</string>
    <string name="center_text">Center Text</string>
    <string name="certtitle">Certificate viewer</string>
    <string name="chanecoreto">Currently, only the system kernel is supported. Do you want to switch to the kernel</string>
    <string name="chanecoretoother">This kernel is not supported temporarily. switch to another kernel</string>
    <string name="change_ball_tip">If you have OCD and don not like to expand the running ball, you can adjust its position.</string>
    <string name="change_next">Change</string>
    <string name="change_pw">Modify encryption password</string>
    <string name="change_style">Click here to modify the list style</string>
    <string name="change_success">The switch is successful. Please restart the app</string>
    <string name="change_success2">Successful switching</string>
    <string name="change_success_app">The switch setting was successful. Please restart APP because this setting has a wide impact.</string>
    <string name="change_tip_ok">Switching will clear the current tabs. Are you sure you want to switch?</string>
    <string name="changed_normal_mode">Compatibility mode has been automatically switched</string>
    <string name="changemycore">Switch kernel</string>
    <string name="changemycore2">Download standalone kernel version</string>
    <string name="changemycore3">Web page rendering crashed. The error log has been sent to the author. Please browse other web pages first</string>
    <string name="changesuccess">The player switch is successful, please click the left play arrow to play</string>
    <string name="character_counter_content_description">Characters entered %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_overflowed_content_description">Character limit exceeded %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="character_counter_pattern">%1$d/%2$d</string>
    <string name="chat_1">How can I help you today?</string>
    <string name="chat_2">What can you do?</string>
    <string name="chat_3">What is the principle of a web browser?</string>
    <string name="chat_4">Plan a study schedule for advanced mathematics for me.</string>
    <string name="check_accout">verify the existence of account</string>
    <string name="check_connect_success">Connectivity status check completed</string>
    <string name="check_fail">parsing failed, next interface</string>
    <string name="check_success">verification successfully joined the interface</string>
    <string name="check_test">Connectivity status check in progress</string>
    <string name="check_url">Analytic validity</string>
    <string name="checkxunlei_success">Failed to open Xunlei. Please confirm that it has been downloaded</string>
    <string name="chime_module_title">Google Notifications Platform</string>
    <string name="chip_remove_icon_content_description">Remove '%1$s'</string>
    <string name="choise_to">Prompt selection</string>
    <string name="choose">Choose</string>
    <string name="choose_path_error">Path selection error. Please follow the instructions as shown in the picture to access the document path. Usually, it is the last one!!!</string>
    <string name="chosen_object_website_reset_confirmation_for">Are you sure you want to reset all site permissions for %1$s?</string>
    <string name="chrome_additional_terms_of_service_title">Chrome &amp; ChromeOS Additional Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="chrome_additional_terms_of_service_url">https://www.google.com/chrome/terms/</string>
    <string name="chrome_dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="chrome_download">Chrome Downloader</string>
    <string name="chrome_history">Chrome history</string>
    <string name="chrome_notification_settings_for_price_tracking">settings</string>
    <string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_1_description">Articles on your interests on Chrome</string>
    <string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_1_title">Read today's news 📰</string>
    <string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_2_description">Use Lite mode on Google Chrome</string>
    <string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_2_title">Save up to 60% data</string>
    <string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_3_description">Save up to 60% data, read today's news</string>
    <string name="chrome_reengagement_notification_3_title">Google recommends Chrome</string>
    <string name="chrome_survey_message_button">Take survey</string>
    <string name="chrome_survey_message_title">Help improve Chrome?</string>
    <string name="chromium_noable">Chromium engine failed to start. Your device is no longer supported. The Blue Version of Rain is still compatible with older systems; you may try that instead.</string>
    <string name="circle_error">Currently, TTS cannot be used for Circle reading. Please exit reading mode first.</string>
    <string name="city_label">City:</string>
    <string name="ciyao_allow">Allow Unimportant Permissions by Default</string>
    <string name="cl0">Video cache</string>
    <string name="cl1">Webpage cache</string>
    <string name="cl2">Cookie</string>
    <string name="cl3">History</string>
    <string name="cl4">search record</string>
    <string name="cl6">configure exit auto clean up</string>
    <string name="clean_cookie_storage">Clear cookies and website data</string>
    <string name="clean_screen">Cscreen</string>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="clear_all_tab">Clear all tabs in the menu bar and keep the current one</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_history_dialog_data_text">The selected data has been removed from Chrome and your synced devices.

Your Google account may have other forms of browsing history like searches and activity from other Google services at &lt;link&gt;myactivity.google.com&lt;/link&gt;.</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_history_dialog_title">Deleted Chrome data</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_important_dialog_button">Delete</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_important_dialog_text">These sites seem important to you:</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_important_dialog_text_with_app">These sites and apps seem important to you:</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_link">Delete browsing data…</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_progress_message">Please wait…</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_progress_title">Deleting browsing data</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_summary">Delete history, cookies, site data, cache…</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_15_minutes">Last 15 minutes</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_24_hours">Last 24 hours</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_7_days">Last 7 days</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_everything">All time</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_four_weeks">Last 4 weeks</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_hour">Last hour</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_tab_period_title">Time range</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_data_title">Delete browsing data</string>
    <string name="clear_browsing_history_summary">Deletes history, including in the search box</string>
    <string name="clear_cache">Clean Cache</string>
    <string name="clear_cache_title">Cached images and files</string>
    <string name="clear_chat">Clear Chat</string>
    <string name="clear_collect">Clear collection</string>
    <string name="clear_cookies_and_site_data_summary_basic">Signs you out of most sites</string>
    <string name="clear_cookies_and_site_data_title">Cookies and site data</string>
    <string name="clear_copy_board">Are you sure you want to clear your clipboard?</string>
    <string name="clear_data_delete">Delete data</string>
    <string name="clear_db_cache">Clear the bookmark database table (developer function, please do not litter it)</string>
    <string name="clear_field">Clear</string>
    <string name="clear_form_data_title">Autofill form data</string>
    <string name="clear_history">Delete overdue history (days)</string>
    <string name="clear_history_title">Browsing history</string>
    <string name="clear_passwords_title">Saved passwords</string>
    <string name="clear_pw">clear password</string>
    <string name="clear_same">Remove Duplicates</string>
    <string name="clear_same_hi">Removing history records with the same URL for you</string>
    <string name="clear_status">Clear status records (hide status indicators)</string>
    <string name="clear_tabs_disabled_summary">Can’t be closed across multiple windows</string>
    <string name="clear_tabs_title">Tabs</string>
    <string name="clear_text_end_icon_content_description">Clear text</string>
    <string name="clear_tip2">This will clear your search records and history. Do you want to continue</string>
    <string name="clear_today">Delete all history records under the current date</string>
    <string name="clear_window">Clear</string>
    <string name="cleared">Cleared</string>
    <string name="clearread">Clear read cache</string>
    <string name="clearrhis">cleanup</string>
    <string name="cleracookie">clear cookies</string>
    <string name="clickTranslate">Click translate</string>
    <string name="click_close_hand">Click here to close one-handed mode</string>
    <string name="click_hide_dialog">Click to hide the popup</string>
    <string name="click_photo">qrcode/click take photos search</string>
    <string name="click_retry">please wait</string>
    <string name="click_retry2">retry</string>
    <string name="click_say">click I start talking</string>
    <string name="click_to_call_dialer_absent_notification_text">Make sure a phone app is enabled on this device</string>
    <string name="click_to_call_dialer_absent_notification_title">Can't make calls</string>
    <string name="click_to_call_notification_text">Tap to make call</string>
    <string name="click_to_edit">modifying the content, then press or click the word to start the Word Segmentation</string>
    <string name="click_to_sort">Drag and hold to sort, click Edit</string>
    <string name="clickpath">click the left to be edited</string>
    <string name="clicksettle">click on the gear</string>
    <string name="client_cert_unsupported_message">Client side certificate selection is not supported by the operating system.</string>
    <string name="client_cert_unsupported_title">Unable to select certificate.</string>
    <string name="client_out_of_date_error_card_button">Update %1$s</string>
    <string name="clip_help">Webpage Clipboard Write Protection</string>
    <string name="clipboard_permission_title">Clipboard</string>
    <string name="cloe_hulian_tip">You are about to shut down the Internet service, your browser data will not be shared with the computer, and all logins on the computer are invalid. Are you sure you want to do this?</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <string name="closeYeJian">Close night</string>
    <string name="close_about_his">close about history</string>
    <string name="close_all_incognito_notification">Close all Incognito tabs</string>
    <string name="close_all_incognito_notification_title">Incognito Tabs</string>
    <string name="close_all_tab">Close all labels</string>
    <string name="close_all_tabs_and_groups_action">Close all tabs and groups</string>
    <string name="close_all_tabs_and_groups_dialog_message">Your closed tabs and groups can be reopened from the Recent tabs section and the Tab groups section.</string>
    <string name="close_all_tabs_dialog_message_incognito">Your activity in these Incognito tabs will be removed from this device</string>
    <string name="close_all_tabs_dialog_title">Close all tabs?</string>
    <string name="close_all_tabs_dialog_title_incognito">Close all Incognito tabs?</string>
    <string name="close_ball_tip">After closing the prompt of plug-in operation, you will not be able to see the plug-in ball in the web browsing interface. You cannot quickly run / disable / view plug-ins. Are you sure to close it?</string>
    <string name="close_book">Turn off bookmark cloud service</string>
    <string name="close_button_description">Close</string>
    <string name="close_copy_tip">You are turning off clipboard management, which will cause web pages to be written to your phone clipboard without your permission. Are you sure you want to manipulate this</string>
    <string name="close_current_page">Close current tab</string>
    <string name="close_desc">Close</string>
    <string name="close_from_group_description">This will delete the group from all devices signed into %1$s</string>
    <string name="close_from_group_dialog_title">Close tab and delete group?</string>
    <string name="close_may_pic_no">Close may result in the gallery not displaying</string>
    <string name="close_pad_mode">Close the tablet UI</string>
    <string name="close_pc">Close desktop</string>
    <string name="close_qp">Turn off bubble reminder</string>
    <string name="close_settle">Close - restart in settings</string>
    <string name="close_tab">Close tab</string>
    <string name="close_tab_group_menu_item">Close</string>
    <string name="close_tag">Closed tag-</string>
    <string name="close_video">turn off popular short videos</string>
    <string name="close_video_check">Turning off the check means that many unplayable videos will automatically pop up. Although turning off this function can speed up the response speed of the smart player, we do not recommend you to do this. Confirm to turn it off</string>
    <string name="closefhtip">you have turned off return non overloading, which makes the function unable to start. Do you want to resume return non overloading</string>
    <string name="closethisfun">turn off this function</string>
    <string name="cloud_builtin_desc">Server connected, encrypted storage activated.</string>
    <string name="cloud_builtin_title">Use Built-in Server</string>
    <string name="cloud_private_desc">Your family data and photos are stored on your private server.</string>
    <string name="cloud_private_enabled">Private Cloud Enabled</string>
    <string name="cloudy">Cloudy</string>
    <string name="clseyulan">the web page has been turned off. Long press preview mode [Rainsee search remains], long press again to try</string>
    <string name="code_error">Verification code error, please check</string>
    <string name="code_get_right">Success</string>
    <string name="code_home">Code Home</string>
    <string name="code_review">If your extension list has been emptied, please click OK, and data recovery will be performed for you.</string>
    <string name="colip_msg">This page will access your clipboard for intelligent analysis</string>
    <string name="collaboration_block_leave_dialog_body">You’ll immediately lose access to the “%1$s” tab group, and %1$s (%2$s) will no longer be able to interact with you across Google services.</string>
    <string name="collaboration_block_leave_dialog_confirm">Block and leave</string>
    <string name="collaboration_block_leave_dialog_title">Block and leave group?</string>
    <string name="collaboration_block_leave_learn_more">Learn about blocked accounts</string>
    <string name="collaboration_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="collaboration_chrome_out_of_date_error_dialog_continue_body">To continue using your shared tab groups, update Chrome</string>
    <string name="collaboration_chrome_out_of_date_error_dialog_header">Chrome is out of date</string>
    <string name="collaboration_chrome_out_of_date_error_dialog_not_now_button">Not now</string>
    <string name="collaboration_chrome_out_of_date_error_dialog_update_button">Update Chrome</string>
    <string name="collaboration_delete_last_tab_cancel">Keep group</string>
    <string name="collaboration_delete_last_tab_title">Keep tab group?</string>
    <string name="collaboration_entreprise_sharing_off_header">Your organization limits what you can share</string>
    <string name="collaboration_group_is_full_description">Your tab group is full, new members can't join with the link</string>
    <string name="collaboration_group_is_full_error_dialog_body">Contact the person who sent this link</string>
    <string name="collaboration_group_is_full_error_dialog_header">This tab group is full</string>
    <string name="collaboration_join_group_as">Join as %1$s</string>
    <string name="collaboration_learn_about_shared_groups">Learn about shared tab groups</string>
    <string name="collaboration_leave_dialog_body">You’ll immediately lose access to the “%1$s” tab group, and it will be deleted from all your devices</string>
    <string name="collaboration_leave_dialog_confirm">Leave</string>
    <string name="collaboration_leave_dialog_title">Leave tab group?</string>
    <string name="collaboration_link_edit_access">Anyone with the link can edit all tabs</string>
    <string name="collaboration_link_join_toggle">Let anyone with the link join</string>
    <string name="collaboration_loading_button">Loading</string>
    <string name="collaboration_manage_group_description">Anyone with the link can edit all tabs.</string>
    <string name="collaboration_manage_group_title">Manage access</string>
    <string name="collaboration_manage_icon">Manage icon</string>
    <string name="collaboration_manage_share_wisely">Always share wisely. Links expire in 48 hours.</string>
    <string name="collaboration_manage_stop_sharing_option">Stop sharing</string>
    <string name="collaboration_member_delete_last_tab_body">Keep this group to add tabs later, or leave it if you no longer want access to it</string>
    <string name="collaboration_member_delete_last_tab_confirm">Leave group</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_block_dialog_body">%1$s (%2$s) will immediately lose access to the “%3$s” tab group, and will no longer be able to interact with you across Google services.</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_block_dialog_confirm">Block</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_block_dialog_title">Block %1$s?</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_delete_dialog_body">Everyone will immediately lose access to the “%1$s” tab group, and it will be deleted from all devices</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_delete_dialog_confirm">Delete</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_delete_dialog_title">Delete tab group?</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_delete_last_tab_body">Keep this group to add tabs later, or delete it if you no longer need it.</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_delete_last_tab_body_2">If you delete it, everyone will immediately lose access to the "%1$s" tab group, and it will be deleted from all devices.</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_delete_last_tab_confirm">Delete group</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_remove_member_dialog_body">%1$s (%2$s) will immediately lose access to the “%3$s” tab group</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_remove_member_dialog_confirm">Remove</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_remove_member_dialog_title">Remove %1$s?</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_stop_sharing_dialog_body">Everyone will immediately lose access to the “%1$s” tab group, and all invitation links will be turned off</string>
    <string name="collaboration_owner_stop_sharing_dialog_title">Stop sharing?</string>
    <string name="collaboration_people_with_access">People with access</string>
    <string name="collaboration_preview_dialog_body">%1$s (%2$s) wants you to join a tab group. Anyone with the link can edit all tabs, so join with care. Link expires in 48 hr.</string>
    <string name="collaboration_preview_dialog_confirm">Join and open</string>
    <string name="collaboration_preview_dialog_details_tabs_in_group">Tabs in group</string>
    <string name="collaboration_preview_dialog_details_title">Tab group details</string>
    <string name="collaboration_preview_dialog_title_single">Join tab group with %1$s</string>
    <string name="collaboration_recent_activity_menu_option">Sharing options</string>
    <string name="collaboration_share_group_body">Anyone with the link can edit all tabs, so share wisely. Link expires in 48 hours.</string>
    <string name="collaboration_share_group_share_as">Share as %1$s</string>
    <string name="collaboration_share_group_title">Share “%1$s” tab group</string>
    <string name="collaboration_share_sheet_message">%1$s link expires in 48 hours</string>
    <string name="collaboration_share_sheet_tab_group_fallback_name">Shared tab group</string>
    <string name="collaboration_share_sheet_title">Collaborate on tab group</string>
    <string name="collaboration_shared_tab_groups_available_again_iph_message">Your shared tab groups are available again</string>
    <string name="collaboration_shared_tab_groups_panel_out_of_date_message_cell_text">Update Chrome to continue using your shared tab groups</string>
    <string name="collaboration_signed_out_body">To share, join, and collaborate in tab groups, open settings and turn on Allow Chrome sign-in</string>
    <string name="collaboration_signed_out_header">You're signed out</string>
    <string name="collaboration_signed_out_positive_button">Settings</string>
    <string name="collaboration_signin_bottom_sheet_description">You’ll get to share, join, and collaborate in tab groups</string>
    <string name="collaboration_signin_bottom_sheet_title">Sign in to Chrome</string>
    <string name="collaboration_signin_description">Sign in to Chrome to share and join tab groups, and work together on ideas</string>
    <string name="collaboration_signin_sync_dismiss">Cancel</string>
    <string name="collaboration_signin_title">Collaborate in tab groups</string>
    <string name="collaboration_sync_description">To share, join, and collaborate in tab groups, sync your history and tabs</string>
    <string name="collaboration_sync_title">Sync tabs and history to continue</string>
    <string name="collect">Collect</string>
    <string name="collect_s">Collect</string>
    <string name="collect_type">Open in New Page</string>
    <string name="color_333333">#333333</string>
    <string name="color_button_show">Colorful shortcut button display</string>
    <string name="color_change">Page infiltration - status bar discoloration</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_black">Black</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_blue">Blue</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_custom">Custom</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_cyan">Cyan</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_green">Green</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_magenta">Magenta</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_red">Red</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_set">Set</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_suggestions">Suggestions</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_white">White</string>
    <string name="color_picker_button_yellow">Yellow</string>
    <string name="color_picker_dialog_title">Select color</string>
    <string name="color_picker_hue">Hue</string>
    <string name="color_picker_label_chosen_color">Chosen color</string>
    <string name="color_picker_saturation">Saturation</string>
    <string name="color_picker_value">Value</string>
    <string name="color_tip">Colorful bookmarks, downloads, history, and other buttons. If turned off, please manually add the corresponding functions in the menu</string>
    <string name="colorful">Multicolor</string>
    <string name="combine_tip">Successfully imported %1$d bookmarks,%2$d folders;</string>
    <string name="combine_ts">Combine Shards</string>
    <string name="comfirm_clear_web">Are you sure you want to clean up all tags</string>
    <string name="comment_msg">tel me you want</string>
    <string name="comments">Update and suggestion</string>
    <string name="commerce_bottom_sheet_content_closed">Commerce bottom sheet closed</string>
    <string name="commerce_bottom_sheet_content_description">Commerce bottom sheet</string>
    <string name="commerce_bottom_sheet_content_opened_full">Commerce bottom sheet opened at full height</string>
    <string name="commerce_bottom_sheet_content_opened_half">Commerce bottom sheet opened at half height</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_button">Enable</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_text">%1$s won't work unless you enable Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_enable_title">Enable Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_button">Install</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_text">%1$s won't run without Google Play services, which are missing from your device.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_install_title">Get Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_channel_name">Google Play services availability</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_notification_ticker">Google Play services error</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unknown_issue">%1$s is having trouble with Google Play services. Please try again.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_unsupported_text">%1$s won't run without Google Play services, which are not supported by your device.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_button">Update</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_text">%1$s won't run unless you update Google Play services.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_update_title">Update Google Play services</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_updating_text">%1$s won't run without Google Play services, which are currently updating.</string>
    <string name="common_google_play_services_wear_update_text">New version of Google Play services needed. It will update itself shortly.</string>
    <string name="common_icons">Common Icons</string>
    <string name="common_open_on_phone">Open on phone</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text">Sign in</string>
    <string name="common_signin_button_text_long">Sign in with Google</string>
    <string name="compact_view">Compact view</string>
    <string name="compact_view_announcement">Showing compact view</string>
    <string name="component_name">Component Name</string>
    <string name="component_placeholder">Component</string>
    <string name="component_settings">Component Settings</string>
    <string name="conbin_doc">Merge folders with the same name</string>
    <string name="conbine">Merger</string>
    <string name="conbine_bookmark">Merge folders with the same name and delete bookmarks with the same directory and URL</string>
    <string name="conbine_local_book">Merge with local bookmarks</string>
    <string name="concat_two_strings_with_comma">%1$s, %2$s</string>
    <string name="confirm">Confirm</string>
    <string name="confirm_delete_message">Do you want to delete %1$s?</string>
    <string name="confirm_device_credential_password">Use password</string>
    <string name="confirm_username_dialog_title">Confirm your username</string>
    <string name="confirmation_stop_showing">Don't ask again</string>
    <string name="connect_refused">Your request is denied, usually due to server issues, or possibly because access is blocked in your area</string>
    <string name="connected_to_bluetooth_device_notification_title">Connected to a Bluetooth device</string>
    <string name="connected_to_serial_port_notification_title">Connected to a serial port</string>
    <string name="connected_to_usb_device_notification_title">Connected to a USB device</string>
    <string name="connecterror">Connectivity difference</string>
    <string name="connection_error">Connection error</string>
    <string name="contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="contacts_picker_all_contacts">All contacts</string>
    <string name="contacts_picker_no_contacts_found">No contacts found</string>
    <string name="contacts_picker_search">Search your contacts</string>
    <string name="contacts_picker_select_contact">Select a contact</string>
    <string name="contacts_picker_select_contacts">Select contacts</string>
    <string name="contain_tip">It's already on the record</string>
    <string name="content_provider_search_description">Bookmarks and web history</string>
    <string name="content_view_more_options_button_clicked">More options button in the content view is clicked.</string>
    <string name="context_search_panel">Tap and select text on the webpage to display the tap search panel</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_add_to_contacts">Add to contacts</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_call">Call</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_copy">Copy</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_copy_image">Copy image</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_copy_link_address">Copy link address</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_copy_link_text">Copy link text</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_edit_shortcut">Edit shortcut</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_exit_picture_in_picture">Exit Picture in Picture</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_inspect_element">Inspect</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_learn_more">Learn more…</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_load_original_image">Load image</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_open_image">Open image</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_open_image_in_ephemeral_tab">Preview image &lt;new&gt;New&lt;/new&gt;</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_open_image_in_new_tab">Open image in new tab</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_open_in_chrome_incognito_tab">Open in Incognito tab</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_open_in_ephemeral_tab">Preview page &lt;new&gt;New&lt;/new&gt;</string>
    <string name="contextmenu_open_in_incognito_tab">Open in Incognito tab</string>